5 WORDTAG O whales
10 WORDTAG O extra
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
5 WORDTAG O 83rd
6 WORDTAG O mind
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Missionaries
19 WORDTAG O bad
9 WORDTAG O delivered
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
7 WORDTAG O 47th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Colombia
293 WORDTAG O year
10 WORDTAG O delay
439 WORDTAG O who
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vale
33 WORDTAG O declared
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Roosevelt
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
10 WORDTAG I-PER Armstrong
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Financial
5 WORDTAG O collision
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Johnson
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
35 WORDTAG O me
19 WORDTAG O verified
42 WORDTAG I-PER Lebed
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Western
13 WORDTAG I-PER Malik
52 WORDTAG I-ORG St
199 WORDTAG O new
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
5 WORDTAG O semifinalist
39 WORDTAG I-LOC Ukraine
4 WORDTAG I-MISC County
5 WORDTAG O applications
25 WORDTAG O health
8 WORDTAG O task
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Swansea
71 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgium
14 WORDTAG O though
18 WORDTAG O stop
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mohamed
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Roman
1496 WORDTAG O 's
7 WORDTAG I-PER Teutenberg
6 WORDTAG O briefing
47 WORDTAG I-PER Yeltsin
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
10 WORDTAG O effort
5 WORDTAG O partnership
8 WORDTAG O Date
6 WORDTAG O 1980s
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Press
5 WORDTAG O sports
38 WORDTAG O own
8 WORDTAG O abortion
1 WORDTAG O Federal
2 WORDTAG I-ORG School
14 WORDTAG O different
9 WORDTAG O maybe
5 WORDTAG O crowds
30 WORDTAG O estimated
6 WORDTAG O 1995/96
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rican
5 WORDTAG O procedure
10 WORDTAG O necessary
7 WORDTAG O street
5 WORDTAG O compromise
12 WORDTAG O minority
7 WORDTAG O occurred
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Ajax
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
9 WORDTAG O aid
8 WORDTAG O recovered
13 WORDTAG O four-day
7 WORDTAG O language
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Africa
8 WORDTAG O wait
18 WORDTAG O presidential
14 WORDTAG O enough
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonds
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Partizan
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Islamic
687 WORDTAG O :
21 WORDTAG O negotiations
23 WORDTAG O firm
18 WORDTAG O secretary
55 WORDTAG O city
8 WORDTAG O prompt
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ischinger
6 WORDTAG I-PER Justin
106 WORDTAG O expected
11 WORDTAG O registration
3 WORDTAG O Port
7 WORDTAG O Of
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
13 WORDTAG O raised
4 WORDTAG I-PER Abu
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Atletico
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hussein
16 WORDTAG O media
12 WORDTAG O father
37 WORDTAG O hold
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Wigan
9 WORDTAG O field
7 WORDTAG O Most
5 WORDTAG O bright
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Egyptian
15 WORDTAG O championships
9 WORDTAG O Following
5 WORDTAG O fours
17 WORDTAG O With
12 WORDTAG O immediate
18 WORDTAG O rounds
8 WORDTAG O unc
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Syria
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boston
12 WORDTAG O cow
95 WORDTAG O 3.
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
5 WORDTAG O 19th
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Airbus
10 WORDTAG O beaten
6 WORDTAG O oppose
14 WORDTAG O students
22 WORDTAG O young
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sunday
44 WORDTAG O return
18 WORDTAG O soldiers
12 WORDTAG I-PER Davis
20 WORDTAG O ethnic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Poland
53 WORDTAG O weekend
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Frenchman
2 WORDTAG I-PER Paulo
6 WORDTAG O events
8 WORDTAG O produced
12 WORDTAG O thing
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayern
6 WORDTAG O getting
1 WORDTAG I-PER West
9 WORDTAG O According
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Texas
15 WORDTAG O ruled
5 WORDTAG O showers
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamilton
5 WORDTAG O roads
82 WORDTAG O tonnes
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chelsea
64 WORDTAG O 6.
19 WORDTAG O sides
106 WORDTAG O spokesman
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mubarak
7 WORDTAG O prix
5 WORDTAG O green
5 WORDTAG O voter
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
19 WORDTAG O allowing
21 WORDTAG I-PER Lewis
9 WORDTAG O reduce
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Slough
7 WORDTAG I-PER K.
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Arnhem
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Telekom
1 WORDTAG I-PER North
40 WORDTAG O much
6 WORDTAG O develop
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Oklahoma
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Sydney
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hospital
11 WORDTAG O scandal
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
62 WORDTAG O same
9 WORDTAG O reduced
10 WORDTAG O spring
5 WORDTAG I-PER Stefano
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stenning
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arequipa
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
7 WORDTAG O confirm
8 WORDTAG O grade
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cozma
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Street
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Venezuela
6 WORDTAG O seemed
216 WORDTAG O second
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Volendam
10 WORDTAG O decide
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Taibe
30 WORDTAG O date
5 WORDTAG O commentary
13 WORDTAG O changed
5 WORDTAG O 1-106
6 WORDTAG O churches
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cea
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bistrita
8 WORDTAG I-MISC HK$
8 WORDTAG O places
12 WORDTAG O defending
7 WORDTAG O column
22 WORDTAG O As
6 WORDTAG O deposed
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fogarty
2 WORDTAG I-MISC 's
8 WORDTAG O eating
17 WORDTAG I-PER Wayne
7 WORDTAG O shots
6 WORDTAG O jewelry
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
84 WORDTAG O half
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
5 WORDTAG O changing
23 WORDTAG O continued
13 WORDTAG O revised
4 WORDTAG O Four
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Japan
7 WORDTAG O chief-of-staff
36 WORDTAG O wickets
38 WORDTAG O On
52 WORDTAG O record
7 WORDTAG O putting
8 WORDTAG O serving
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Switzerland
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
7 WORDTAG O communist
20 WORDTAG O involved
15 WORDTAG O shooting
10 WORDTAG O employee
2 WORDTAG I-LOC County
10 WORDTAG O crashed
16 WORDTAG O vouch
6 WORDTAG O Affairs
13 WORDTAG O cuts
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
8 WORDTAG O Eight
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Slovak
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbs
127 WORDTAG I-PER _CAP_
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Havre
37 WORDTAG O seen
9 WORDTAG O stopped
1846 WORDTAG O said
9 WORDTAG O jet
5 WORDTAG O effects
10 WORDTAG O reason
6 WORDTAG O retailer
11 WORDTAG O spent
314 WORDTAG O up
28 WORDTAG O force
12 WORDTAG O winners
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Team
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Birmingham
1 WORDTAG I-PER Post
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bridge
2 WORDTAG I-MISC North
2 WORDTAG I-MISC de
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Division
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bordeaux
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Airways
51 WORDTAG O start
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
108 WORDTAG O she
35 WORDTAG O started
5 WORDTAG O Among
20 WORDTAG O question
6 WORDTAG O difference
11 WORDTAG O Three
16 WORDTAG O entered
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Sofia
37 WORDTAG O again
5 WORDTAG O .470
54 WORDTAG O leaders
536 WORDTAG O not
13 WORDTAG O Scores
5 WORDTAG I-PER Preston
56 WORDTAG O issue
109 WORDTAG O official
6 WORDTAG O mayor
8 WORDTAG O seedings
7 WORDTAG O improvement
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Seattle
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
31 WORDTAG I-MISC Democratic
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mexican
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Irish
13 WORDTAG O finally
22 WORDTAG O problems
49 WORDTAG O those
24 WORDTAG O system
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bratislava
13 WORDTAG I-LOC House
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Basque
13 WORDTAG O delivery
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurd
15 WORDTAG O others
11 WORDTAG O residents
80 WORDTAG O during
15 WORDTAG O beginning
7 WORDTAG O justice
6 WORDTAG O size
7 WORDTAG O smaller
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Huddersfield
58 WORDTAG O runs
22 WORDTAG O Some
84 WORDTAG O still
55 WORDTAG O ended
32 WORDTAG O must
22 WORDTAG O chance
20 WORDTAG O summer
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Power
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
13 WORDTAG O 6-
10 WORDTAG O powers
30 WORDTAG O *
14 WORDTAG O abroad
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
29 WORDTAG O figures
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
6 WORDTAG O radical
7 WORDTAG O confessed
9 WORDTAG O receiving
22 WORDTAG O unit
44 WORDTAG O ...
17 WORDTAG O once
24 WORDTAG O less
9 WORDTAG O shipment
9 WORDTAG O especially
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Peace
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Thomson
7 WORDTAG I-PER Evert
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bossi
11 WORDTAG O expressed
23 WORDTAG I-PER Steve
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Cup
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
5 WORDTAG O 3.2
44 WORDTAG O parliament
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Rwandan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Santos
8 WORDTAG I-PER Juppe
25 WORDTAG O able
6 WORDTAG O unnamed
553 WORDTAG O it
5 WORDTAG O tested
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Football
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
14 WORDTAG O large
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
5 WORDTAG O commitment
5 WORDTAG O swimming
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sudan
6 WORDTAG I-PER Vladimir
45 WORDTAG O election
31 WORDTAG O charges
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Civil
9 WORDTAG O balance
5 WORDTAG O spying
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinians
5 WORDTAG O 4.4
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Nepal
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pot
8 WORDTAG O 54th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Saudi
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Rwanda
5 WORDTAG O pinch-hitter
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Iraqi
2 WORDTAG O High
4 WORDTAG O Series
5 WORDTAG O mining
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Grimsby
8 WORDTAG O link
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Moscow
5 WORDTAG O 1.2
23 WORDTAG O pounds
14 WORDTAG O white
1 WORDTAG I-LOC High
5 WORDTAG O attributable
1 WORDTAG I-LOC School
4 WORDTAG I-PER Kan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Padres
76 WORDTAG O game
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
6 WORDTAG O protesters
10 WORDTAG O owns
15 WORDTAG O invited
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Warwickshire
9 WORDTAG I-PER Sarah
12 WORDTAG O employees
19 WORDTAG O midfielder
20 WORDTAG O currency
39 WORDTAG O nine
19 WORDTAG I-LOC Oval
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Oxford
128 WORDTAG O played
18 WORDTAG O territory
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Stoke
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Lodz
24 WORDTAG O bond
6 WORDTAG O magazine
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Seoul
2 WORDTAG I-LOC State
6 WORDTAG O bpd
10 WORDTAG O fear
21 WORDTAG O open
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
35 WORDTAG O long
7 WORDTAG O liquidity
16 WORDTAG O bus
5 WORDTAG O 4-95
1 WORDTAG I-ORG vehicles
8 WORDTAG O decree
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dole
43 WORDTAG O plans
7 WORDTAG O overseas
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Stuttgart
32 WORDTAG O trying
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cedric
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Iraqi
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brugge
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northampton
25 WORDTAG O based
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gerhard
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovakia
6 WORDTAG I-ORG VfB
12 WORDTAG O drop
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
13 WORDTAG I-PER Thorpe
27 WORDTAG O playing
5 WORDTAG O containing
11 WORDTAG I-PER Andre
11 WORDTAG O draft
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Hill
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Hapoel
5 WORDTAG O Many
40 WORDTAG I-ORG U.N.
9 WORDTAG O .496
18 WORDTAG O feed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC News
6 WORDTAG I-PER King
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Algeria
9 WORDTAG O determined
1 WORDTAG I-MISC S&P
19 WORDTAG O rupees
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
6 WORDTAG O explain
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
18 WORDTAG O move
8 WORDTAG O confident
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
13 WORDTAG O hurdles
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hamilton
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Stansted
48 WORDTAG O office
23 WORDTAG O low
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Samsung
6 WORDTAG O die
5 WORDTAG O insisted
9 WORDTAG O inflation
13 WORDTAG O ransom
25 WORDTAG O areas
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Schalke
51 WORDTAG O want
17 WORDTAG O qualifier
8 WORDTAG I-PER Petr
26 WORDTAG O position
2 WORDTAG O Agriculture
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cannes
17 WORDTAG O blamed
10 WORDTAG I-PER Jan
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
7 WORDTAG O regarding
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamils
31 WORDTAG O death
9 WORDTAG O driving
22 WORDTAG O western
1093 WORDTAG O The
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spring
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Angels
53 WORDTAG O near
1 WORDTAG O Van
1 WORDTAG I-PER Polonia
2 WORDTAG I-PER )
7 WORDTAG O quality
9 WORDTAG O department
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
6 WORDTAG O attention
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pakistan
260 WORDTAG O one
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
5 WORDTAG O experts
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
12 WORDTAG O reform
53 WORDTAG O security
2846 WORDTAG O (
5 WORDTAG I-MISC ADRs
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Brussels
8 WORDTAG O person
38 WORDTAG O previous
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Capital
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
5 WORDTAG O container
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bochum
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Subaru
83 WORDTAG O set
27 WORDTAG O violence
18 WORDTAG O paid
10 WORDTAG O project
10 WORDTAG O investigating
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Vitesse
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Arkansas
12 WORDTAG O something
19 WORDTAG O career
1 WORDTAG I-ORG self-rule
7 WORDTAG O firing
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrat
9 WORDTAG O reasons
209 WORDTAG O He
6 WORDTAG O 64th
17 WORDTAG O terms
11 WORDTAG O neighbouring
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
17 WORDTAG I-PER Russell
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Zealand
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Nigerian
5 WORDTAG O noon
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
13 WORDTAG O thousands
17 WORDTAG O spokeswoman
19 WORDTAG O car
18 WORDTAG O hand
5 WORDTAG I-ORG ministry
5 WORDTAG O exclusive
31 WORDTAG O coach
7 WORDTAG O forest
5 WORDTAG O 57th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Palkhivala
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nice
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
9 WORDTAG O demanded
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stadler
8 WORDTAG O blow
10 WORDTAG O care
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interpol
14 WORDTAG I-PER Brown
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Add
44 WORDTAG O vs
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northampton
9 WORDTAG O scientific
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Committee
20 WORDTAG O become
19 WORDTAG O traded
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rio
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Office
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sporting
8 WORDTAG O search
5 WORDTAG O edition
6 WORDTAG O pilot
5 WORDTAG I-PER Andreas
7 WORDTAG O virus
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Israel
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sierra
77 WORDTAG O elections
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
12 WORDTAG O history
50 WORDTAG O chief
18 WORDTAG O exchange
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bordeaux
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sheffield
14 WORDTAG O look
10 WORDTAG O build
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Birmingham
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lanusse
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Thai
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Dutch
15 WORDTAG O mostly
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chorzow
11 WORDTAG O 8-6
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
5 WORDTAG O aiming
6 WORDTAG O speaking
7 WORDTAG O consider
6 WORDTAG O box
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Ecuador
7 WORDTAG O addressed
85 WORDTAG O division
18 WORDTAG O key
1 WORDTAG I-MISC program
9 WORDTAG I-PER der
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Metz
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Jamaica
33 WORDTAG O children
17 WORDTAG O thought
13 WORDTAG O crime
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
7 WORDTAG O suspicion
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
7 WORDTAG O attacked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Singer
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Freiburg
5 WORDTAG O sectors
9 WORDTAG O Did
14 WORDTAG O ministers
10 WORDTAG O operations
54 WORDTAG O Women
5 WORDTAG O nominated
15 WORDTAG O boy
6 WORDTAG O allow
10 WORDTAG O jobs
52 WORDTAG O top
2 WORDTAG O Street
65 WORDTAG O 4.
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Indians
28 WORDTAG O pay
5 WORDTAG O caps
23 WORDTAG O seeded
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Kashmir
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Prague
25 WORDTAG O civil
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Tokyo
18 WORDTAG O rival
13 WORDTAG O lines
6 WORDTAG O majors
8 WORDTAG O extradition
6 WORDTAG O affair
23 WORDTAG O fall
14 WORDTAG O interim
17 WORDTAG O survey
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
9 WORDTAG O social
8 WORDTAG I-PER Tapie
6 WORDTAG O ancient
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Monde
5 WORDTAG O achieve
6 WORDTAG I-PER Juha
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kornblum
8 WORDTAG O headed
15 WORDTAG O am
21 WORDTAG O appeal
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangladesh
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chesterfield
14 WORDTAG O Yellow
34 WORDTAG O production
5 WORDTAG O medicine
7 WORDTAG O escape
7 WORDTAG O age
5 WORDTAG O insistence
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ibrahim
220 WORDTAG O /
1 WORDTAG I-MISC General
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bombay
5 WORDTAG O taka
6 WORDTAG O forecasts
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kurdistan
13 WORDTAG O nil
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Old
17 WORDTAG O track
102 WORDTAG O them
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Morocco
14 WORDTAG I-ORG for
13 WORDTAG O conflict
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Afghan
26 WORDTAG O homer
14 WORDTAG O boat
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
23 WORDTAG O broke
10 WORDTAG I-PER Raymond
17 WORDTAG O losing
6 WORDTAG O scientists
5 WORDTAG O import
2 WORDTAG O Supreme
8 WORDTAG O possibility
8 WORDTAG O controllers
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Universe
2 WORDTAG I-PER Power
8 WORDTAG O finance
33 WORDTAG O short
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
346 WORDTAG O are
11 WORDTAG O considered
7 WORDTAG O benefit
7 WORDTAG O journalists
19 WORDTAG O 10th
5 WORDTAG O isolated
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nancy
32 WORDTAG O stock
10 WORDTAG O flights
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Systems
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
15 WORDTAG O travel
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatian
54 WORDTAG O tournament
5 WORDTAG O intercepted
3617 WORDTAG O of
45 WORDTAG I-MISC African
5 WORDTAG O recalled
5 WORDTAG O links
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Charleroi
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Winners
31 WORDTAG I-ORG European
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Office
14 WORDTAG I-PER Andrea
10 WORDTAG O considering
12 WORDTAG O While
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Leon
11 WORDTAG O airports
22 WORDTAG I-PER Sohail
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Jose
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Corporation
9 WORDTAG O resolution
5 WORDTAG O breaking
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
18 WORDTAG O defender
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Surrey
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
6 WORDTAG O gain
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Bradford
5 WORDTAG O legs
5 WORDTAG O plantation
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Graafschap
13 WORDTAG I-ORG The
8 WORDTAG O connection
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chesterfield
1 WORDTAG I-PER Durham
5 WORDTAG O asking
41 WORDTAG O taken
32 WORDTAG O further
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Two
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Avonex
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Park
24 WORDTAG O break
15 WORDTAG O sex
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Yemen
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Toronto
10 WORDTAG O lending
7 WORDTAG O commercial
71 WORDTAG O can
21 WORDTAG O food
1 WORDTAG I-LOC W.
5 WORDTAG O contest
1 WORDTAG I-PER Island
8 WORDTAG O 13.
91 WORDTAG O billion
1 WORDTAG B-LOC Israel
5 WORDTAG O adopted
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
7 WORDTAG O **
20 WORDTAG O tonne
5 WORDTAG O criticised
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
5 WORDTAG O strikes
5 WORDTAG O pullout
46 WORDTAG O ahead
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Beirut
84 WORDTAG I-MISC German
5 WORDTAG O assistant
6 WORDTAG O critics
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kabul
93 WORDTAG I-PER Clinton
1 WORDTAG I-ORG do
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Shanghai
22 WORDTAG O banks
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
9 WORDTAG I-PER Perot
6 WORDTAG O global
9 WORDTAG O hitting
12 WORDTAG O Summary
38 WORDTAG O draw
9 WORDTAG O carried
10 WORDTAG O generally
5 WORDTAG O bulk
8 WORDTAG O showing
26 WORDTAG O south
5 WORDTAG O Up
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Conference
282 WORDTAG O last
31 WORDTAG I-ORG Ltd
9 WORDTAG O federation
7 WORDTAG O owner
14 WORDTAG O Year
17 WORDTAG O deputy
15 WORDTAG O wounded
30 WORDTAG O private
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Johnson
20 WORDTAG O weapons
13 WORDTAG I-LOC America
14 WORDTAG O unrest
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Wales
9 WORDTAG O slow
5 WORDTAG O supported
6 WORDTAG O Match
17 WORDTAG O development
1 WORDTAG O Community
8 WORDTAG O stores
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Jakarta
49 WORDTAG O allowed
7 WORDTAG O refugee
7 WORDTAG I-PER Luis
17 WORDTAG O seek
6 WORDTAG O sparked
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Cuban
7 WORDTAG I-ORG de
45 WORDTAG O hours
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rosati
3 WORDTAG I-PER Field
21 WORDTAG I-PER Teresa
14 WORDTAG O victims
8 WORDTAG O cleared
7 WORDTAG O 15th
11 WORDTAG O turn
5 WORDTAG O diesel
25 WORDTAG O aggregate
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Times
8 WORDTAG O stood
5 WORDTAG I-PER Strang
9 WORDTAG O guards
9 WORDTAG O lawsuit
5 WORDTAG O Fax
91 WORDTAG O reported
11 WORDTAG O speaker
11 WORDTAG O promised
5 WORDTAG O pipes
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisconsin
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
5 WORDTAG O strongly
5 WORDTAG O boats
5 WORDTAG O stations
6 WORDTAG O edge
8 WORDTAG O network
7 WORDTAG O review
16 WORDTAG I-LOC California
13 WORDTAG O book
40 WORDTAG O past
4 WORDTAG O My
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesia
9 WORDTAG O conservative
19 WORDTAG O For
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vermont
18 WORDTAG O suffered
17 WORDTAG O drove
6 WORDTAG O Soccer
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bolton
10 WORDTAG I-ORG the
13 WORDTAG O unq
10 WORDTAG B-MISC _RARE_
13 WORDTAG O +31
10 WORDTAG O Other
6 WORDTAG O questions
15 WORDTAG O sought
19 WORDTAG O offered
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Japanese
180 WORDTAG O about
6 WORDTAG I-PER Giles
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Saudi
169 WORDTAG O her
26 WORDTAG O know
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Soccer
7 WORDTAG O trouble
6 WORDTAG I-PER W.
75 WORDTAG O soccer
8 WORDTAG O transport
6 WORDTAG I-PER Korda
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrats
15 WORDTAG O Second
2 WORDTAG I-PER Diego
6 WORDTAG O accuses
8 WORDTAG I-PER Collinelli
8 WORDTAG O doubt
29 WORDTAG I-PER Robert
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Nyva
1 WORDTAG I-ORG affairs
42 WORDTAG O asked
5 WORDTAG O painted
12 WORDTAG O evidence
346 WORDTAG O their
22 WORDTAG O radio
21 WORDTAG O fire
12 WORDTAG I-PER Levy
20 WORDTAG O girls
5 WORDTAG O therapy
27 WORDTAG O today
35 WORDTAG O period
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Rangers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frederic
11 WORDTAG O Both
9 WORDTAG O cycling
11 WORDTAG O cannot
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Sussex
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cyprus
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
5 WORDTAG O prisoners
6 WORDTAG O understanding
6 WORDTAG O chains
11 WORDTAG O flew
17 WORDTAG O looked
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Yamaha
1 WORDTAG I-PER Florence
5 WORDTAG O Chairman
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Korean
5 WORDTAG O aggressive
12 WORDTAG O funds
1 WORDTAG I-PER Park
2 WORDTAG I-ORG office
6 WORDTAG O behalf
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Melbourne
1 WORDTAG B-MISC World
51 WORDTAG O miles
7 WORDTAG O newsdesk
17 WORDTAG O one-day
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
5 WORDTAG O loans
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
236 WORDTAG O against
7 WORDTAG I-PER Colonna
11 WORDTAG O barley
9 WORDTAG O coast
6 WORDTAG O concrete
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
6 WORDTAG O airliner
6 WORDTAG O renewed
13 WORDTAG I-PER White
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
9 WORDTAG I-PER Owens
6 WORDTAG I-PER Zhirinovsky
23 WORDTAG O talk
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Willem
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taiwan
12 WORDTAG O assault
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
26 WORDTAG O 'S
9 WORDTAG O planning
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
2 WORDTAG I-PER Villa
5 WORDTAG O Interior
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Spartak
6 WORDTAG O retain
75 WORDTAG O minutes
9 WORDTAG O gone
5 WORDTAG O rubber
6 WORDTAG O surge
9 WORDTAG O 4-2
17 WORDTAG O More
18 WORDTAG O management
2 WORDTAG B-MISC Hutu
27 WORDTAG O making
19 WORDTAG O overnight
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Edouard
9 WORDTAG O established
15 WORDTAG O followed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cubs
10 WORDTAG O longer
12 WORDTAG I-PER Stephen
12 WORDTAG O cattle
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Brisbane
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Commercial
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Revolutionary
8 WORDTAG O lived
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Escort
46 WORDTAG O may
7 WORDTAG O doctor
42 WORDTAG O head
18 WORDTAG O positive
220 WORDTAG O when
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cofinec
1 WORDTAG O Bank
6 WORDTAG O franc
3 WORDTAG I-LOC the
5 WORDTAG I-MISC East
14 WORDTAG O unchanged
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
1 WORDTAG B-LOC High
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroleum
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fischler
1 WORDTAG I-MISC n't
5 WORDTAG O bureau
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Detroit
85 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistan
20 WORDTAG O expect
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Faulding
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
5 WORDTAG O boxcar
11 WORDTAG O organisers
7 WORDTAG O revenues
6 WORDTAG O vowed
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Eindhoven
8 WORDTAG O absence
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Prize
36 WORDTAG I-PER Dutroux
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Spaniard
10 WORDTAG O Traders
85 WORDTAG O news
40 WORDTAG O signed
7 WORDTAG O Princess
46 WORDTAG O forces
5 WORDTAG O communications
5 WORDTAG I-PER Goran
5 WORDTAG O posts
10 WORDTAG O ran
10 WORDTAG O suspects
6 WORDTAG I-PER Abdul
8 WORDTAG O proposals
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Net
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Crystal
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Tilburg
10 WORDTAG O wrote
6 WORDTAG O 56th
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Kuwait
16 WORDTAG O books
9 WORDTAG I-PER Davies
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jayasuriya
7 WORDTAG O discussions
9 WORDTAG O dollars
6 WORDTAG O arrests
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Central
2 WORDTAG I-PER Golf
109 WORDTAG O former
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Palace
11 WORDTAG I-ORG South
10 WORDTAG O All
23 WORDTAG O compared
6 WORDTAG O picture
55 WORDTAG O minister
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lloyd
18 WORDTAG O stated
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
13 WORDTAG O imports
20 WORDTAG O domestic
11 WORDTAG O written
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
16 WORDTAG I-PER Stewart
8 WORDTAG O conducted
5 WORDTAG O apiece
12 WORDTAG O score
16 WORDTAG O biggest
2 WORDTAG O National
108 WORDTAG O home
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sachs
35 WORDTAG O least
9 WORDTAG O homered
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberation
1 WORDTAG I-MISC for
8 WORDTAG O magazines
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Sierra
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Geneva
8 WORDTAG O gathering
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CAC-40
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
73 WORDTAG O results
6 WORDTAG O fighters
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Taiwan
8 WORDTAG I-ORG McLaren
8 WORDTAG O negative
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
5 WORDTAG O climb
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Singer
7 WORDTAG O wounds
9 WORDTAG O counterpart
20 WORDTAG O mark
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Sparta
8 WORDTAG O lunch
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chorzow
8 WORDTAG I-PER Javier
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Leicester
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicester
258 WORDTAG O government
8 WORDTAG O homers
85 WORDTAG O 1996-08-25
5 WORDTAG O camps
67 WORDTAG O minute
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Aberdeen
56 WORDTAG O behind
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jason
9 WORDTAG O Qualifier
35 WORDTAG O champions
10 WORDTAG O speculation
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Diego
5 WORDTAG O settlements
47 WORDTAG O km
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
9 WORDTAG O About
52 WORDTAG O players
7 WORDTAG O nations
5 WORDTAG O Q2
5 WORDTAG I-PER Herbert
1 WORDTAG O Union
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Front
6 WORDTAG O involves
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sauber
5 WORDTAG O filled
12 WORDTAG O weather
8 WORDTAG O idea
171 WORDTAG O In
7 WORDTAG I-PER Barbara
8 WORDTAG I-PER Davenport
2 WORDTAG I-LOC and
22 WORDTAG O increase
18 WORDTAG O sources
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
5 WORDTAG I-PER Headley
75 WORDTAG O lead
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lynch
6 WORDTAG O Analysts
30 WORDTAG O likely
7 WORDTAG I-PER Volkova
48 WORDTAG O several
2846 WORDTAG O )
24 WORDTAG O according
9 WORDTAG O shipments
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magdalena
6 WORDTAG O mountain
36 WORDTAG O give
7 WORDTAG O finding
5 WORDTAG O prayer
212 WORDTAG O Tuesday
12 WORDTAG I-PER Tsang
23 WORDTAG O never
13 WORDTAG O handed
14 WORDTAG O noted
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Former
6 WORDTAG O related
42 WORDTAG O trading
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Association
13 WORDTAG O ruling
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
43 WORDTAG O went
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Berlex
10 WORDTAG O effective
6 WORDTAG O highway
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Celica
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Brewers
47 WORDTAG I-PER Arafat
25 WORDTAG I-PER Khan
8 WORDTAG O produce
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jordan
15 WORDTAG O nothing
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Cambridge
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Western
7 WORDTAG O transition
10 WORDTAG O clearly
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
16 WORDTAG O event
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Jerusalem
13 WORDTAG O pressure
6 WORDTAG O replacement
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechen
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Africa
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
19 WORDTAG O sixth
6 WORDTAG O climbed
49 WORDTAG I-ORG New
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bombay
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Melbourne
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St
33 WORDTAG O 10.
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
2 WORDTAG O Court
5 WORDTAG O kerosene
30 WORDTAG O small
45 WORDTAG O reporters
6 WORDTAG O neither
2 WORDTAG I-ORG W.
13 WORDTAG O unable
11 WORDTAG O friendly
18 WORDTAG O truck
12 WORDTAG O customs
105 WORDTAG O statement
7 WORDTAG O weight
6 WORDTAG O split
11 WORDTAG O violations
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Algiers
8 WORDTAG I-PER Brian
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Nicaraguan
9 WORDTAG O southeast
13 WORDTAG I-ORG ,
7 WORDTAG O reserves
9 WORDTAG O base
7 WORDTAG O signs
12 WORDTAG I-PER Inzamam-ul-Haq
9 WORDTAG O makes
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Democrat
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Florida
3 WORDTAG O International
19 WORDTAG O 've
40 WORDTAG O hits
5 WORDTAG O listed
95 WORDTAG I-LOC New
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Luxembourg
71 WORDTAG I-MISC Open
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Centre
15 WORDTAG O giving
12 WORDTAG O bit
23 WORDTAG O house
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
50 WORDTAG O 8.
7 WORDTAG O labour
12 WORDTAG O Although
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Paris
29 WORDTAG O policy
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Germain
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Georgia
8 WORDTAG O Oct
1 WORDTAG O Hamlet
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rapid
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pioline
2 WORDTAG I-PER (
42 WORDTAG O few
5 WORDTAG O aide
8 WORDTAG O noise
17 WORDTAG O form
5 WORDTAG I-PER Howard
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Latvia
86 WORDTAG O June
81 WORDTAG O now
10 WORDTAG O opens
8 WORDTAG O scene
7 WORDTAG O faced
5 WORDTAG O perhaps
106 WORDTAG O do
67 WORDTAG I-MISC French
6 WORDTAG O qualified
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kim
9 WORDTAG O prompted
54 WORDTAG O report
9 WORDTAG O document
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dundee
85 WORDTAG O added
6 WORDTAG O pleased
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Club
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Auckland
5 WORDTAG O parents
10 WORDTAG O fraud
37 WORDTAG O these
37 WORDTAG O 9.
5 WORDTAG O cold
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ford
5 WORDTAG O narrow
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Valletta
201 WORDTAG O three
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Somerset
22 WORDTAG O ninth
65 WORDTAG O league
24 WORDTAG O 2-6
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joseph
61 WORDTAG O run
28 WORDTAG I-PER Croft
11 WORDTAG O mixed
18 WORDTAG I-PER Bob
100 WORDTAG O world
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
8 WORDTAG O manage
21 WORDTAG O traders
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Rating
5 WORDTAG O roubles
5 WORDTAG I-PER Phan
5 WORDTAG O everyone
38 WORDTAG O campaign
12 WORDTAG O questioned
16 WORDTAG O feel
10 WORDTAG O vice
19 WORDTAG O rest
7 WORDTAG O popular
3 WORDTAG I-ORG African
6 WORDTAG O kilometre
25 WORDTAG O kept
6 WORDTAG B-ORG Greens
13 WORDTAG O picked
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Wall
62 WORDTAG O go
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Commission
10 WORDTAG O clocked
12 WORDTAG O opinion
37 WORDTAG O high
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Auxerre
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dublin
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bremen
47 WORDTAG O television
8 WORDTAG O militia
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Heerenveen
6 WORDTAG O Security
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Gencor
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Public
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indian
5 WORDTAG O shelling
5 WORDTAG O provided
5 WORDTAG O letters
5 WORDTAG O By
31 WORDTAG O clear
16 WORDTAG O measures
6 WORDTAG O nun
60 WORDTAG O called
24 WORDTAG O director
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dhaka
9 WORDTAG O prepared
7 WORDTAG O selling
10 WORDTAG O advertising
1 WORDTAG O Airways
18 WORDTAG O debt
4 WORDTAG I-MISC :
5 WORDTAG O placed
13 WORDTAG O speak
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
5 WORDTAG O ranked
7 WORDTAG O backed
5 WORDTAG O routine
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Brooks
21 WORDTAG I-PER Jim
5 WORDTAG O pills
12 WORDTAG O 15-6
33 WORDTAG O given
26 WORDTAG O charged
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Worcestershire
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Columbia
25 WORDTAG O centre
20 WORDTAG O overall
8 WORDTAG O king
10 WORDTAG O star
11 WORDTAG O fishermen
14 WORDTAG O filed
5 WORDTAG O ONE-DAY
8 WORDTAG O casualties
2 WORDTAG O Peace
20 WORDTAG O value
4 WORDTAG I-LOC 's
7 WORDTAG O hundreds
7 WORDTAG O 16.
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
4 WORDTAG I-PER Christopher
5 WORDTAG O appearance
8 WORDTAG O firms
29 WORDTAG O level
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
13 WORDTAG O wins
6 WORDTAG O education
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fernandez
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Cologne
9 WORDTAG O standing
8 WORDTAG O Amount
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trafford
13 WORDTAG O imposed
1 WORDTAG I-PER N.J.
5 WORDTAG O planes
14 WORDTAG O banned
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Croatia
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bristol
84 WORDTAG O metres
144 WORDTAG O than
24 WORDTAG O penalty
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
11 WORDTAG O status
6 WORDTAG O terrorist
4 WORDTAG O Business
7 WORDTAG O signing
9 WORDTAG I-PER Smicer
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Zimbabwe
5 WORDTAG I-PER Boer
1 WORDTAG O Best
15 WORDTAG O joined
13 WORDTAG O wants
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
7 WORDTAG O amount
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kevorkian
17 WORDTAG I-PER Anwar
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamic
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Benfica
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Liberia
6 WORDTAG O express
5 WORDTAG O investments
75 WORDTAG O early
1 WORDTAG I-MISC India
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
7 WORDTAG O installed
7 WORDTAG O 3311812-4
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Leduc
10 WORDTAG O read
19 WORDTAG I-LOC City
16 WORDTAG O things
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
6 WORDTAG I-PER Hope
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
16 WORDTAG O majority
6 WORDTAG O 7.0
23 WORDTAG O carrying
9 WORDTAG O expectations
26 WORDTAG O convention
9 WORDTAG O meetings
6 WORDTAG O limits
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
11 WORDTAG O means
25 WORDTAG O outside
10 WORDTAG I-PER Max
59 WORDTAG O singles
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mauritius
26 WORDTAG O comment
6 WORDTAG O seriously
6 WORDTAG I-PER Cyprien
27 WORDTAG O coming
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
24 WORDTAG I-LOC Jordan
5 WORDTAG O friends
5 WORDTAG O acres
4 WORDTAG I-LOC British
65 WORDTAG O play
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Social
6 WORDTAG O garlic
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgrade
5 WORDTAG O owners
5 WORDTAG O offering
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Banespa
8 WORDTAG O prosecutors
28 WORDTAG O sold
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherlands
6 WORDTAG O suspension
7 WORDTAG O plants
6 WORDTAG O finals
5 WORDTAG I-ORG League
8 WORDTAG I-PER Mika
8 WORDTAG O bring
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
6 WORDTAG O personal
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Kong
7 WORDTAG O ask
11 WORDTAG O clashes
12 WORDTAG O King
7 WORDTAG I-PER Popov
10 WORDTAG O provincial
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Police
50 WORDTAG O court
13 WORDTAG O interview
3390 WORDTAG O in
31 WORDTAG O industry
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Turner
4 WORDTAG O Prince
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Baker
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kansas
9 WORDTAG O 1996/97
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Workers
6 WORDTAG I-ORG America
2 WORDTAG I-PER May
11 WORDTAG O bottom
5 WORDTAG O save
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Republic
5 WORDTAG O reluctant
15 WORDTAG O State
11 WORDTAG I-PER Adrian
5 WORDTAG O tanks
54 WORDTAG O rebels
6 WORDTAG O northeast
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fowler
14 WORDTAG O performance
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Buenos
21 WORDTAG O rain
416 WORDTAG O will
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Burundi
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Community
8 WORDTAG O skull
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Moody
15 WORDTAG O futures
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Democracy
1 WORDTAG I-MISC California
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Agriculture
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Toyota
20 WORDTAG O movement
45 WORDTAG O loss
25 WORDTAG O wheat
8 WORDTAG O maintain
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Authority
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Stock
6 WORDTAG O taxes
5 WORDTAG O fields
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Detroit
7 WORDTAG O pretty
10 WORDTAG O worst
9 WORDTAG O executed
27 WORDTAG O chairman
6 WORDTAG O acquired
12 WORDTAG O moved
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Eritrea
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Daewoo
5 WORDTAG O A-rated
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Rabobank
76 WORDTAG I-LOC South
6 WORDTAG O politician
5 WORDTAG O warning
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperation
5 WORDTAG O pesetas
6 WORDTAG O exile
44 WORDTAG O night
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Interfax
15 WORDTAG O slightly
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Khan
82 WORDTAG O killed
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
42 WORDTAG O morning
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Globo
5 WORDTAG O cool
192 WORDTAG O Monday
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Amsterdam
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Russian
24 WORDTAG O step
6 WORDTAG O irregularities
5 WORDTAG I-PER Blind
94 WORDTAG O 1.
5 WORDTAG O barred
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Securities
8 WORDTAG I-PER Christian
6 WORDTAG O maker
11 WORDTAG O 7-1
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Paris
10 WORDTAG O pts
19 WORDTAG O options
14 WORDTAG O role
16 WORDTAG O common
16 WORDTAG O basis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Reserve
8 WORDTAG O blast
6 WORDTAG O intended
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Colchester
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Miguel
60 WORDTAG O then
757 WORDTAG O from
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 21st
10 WORDTAG I-PER Norman
28 WORDTAG O prison
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Albania
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Community
13 WORDTAG O include
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aoki
9 WORDTAG O Final
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Information
36 WORDTAG O released
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Baltimore
7 WORDTAG O refunds
6 WORDTAG O provinces
15 WORDTAG I-PER Weizman
81 WORDTAG O season
14 WORDTAG O introduced
22 WORDTAG O These
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cash
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Net
11 WORDTAG O Shares
7 WORDTAG O formally
5 WORDTAG O settle
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonan
6 WORDTAG O civilians
7 WORDTAG O railway
27 WORDTAG O within
15 WORDTAG O looking
11 WORDTAG O servants
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Brazil
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gatwick
1 WORDTAG I-LOC No
8 WORDTAG O plus
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Advanced
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fox
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Netherlands
5 WORDTAG O scoreless
48 WORDTAG O women
11 WORDTAG O militants
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
6 WORDTAG O 5-1
4 WORDTAG O Export
1 WORDTAG I-LOC William
6 WORDTAG O invitation
5 WORDTAG O re-election
6 WORDTAG I-PER Yassin
15 WORDTAG I-ORG _DIGIT_
7 WORDTAG O Playing
5 WORDTAG O style
26 WORDTAG O keep
13 WORDTAG O account
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
9 WORDTAG O fellow
20 WORDTAG O union
28 WORDTAG O No
117 WORDTAG O 6-4
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Hamlet
27 WORDTAG O confirmed
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Subaru
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Heathrow
5 WORDTAG I-PER Nilis
5 WORDTAG O bases
8 WORDTAG O emerged
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Queensland
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
5 WORDTAG O pass
7 WORDTAG O regions
5 WORDTAG O follow
6 WORDTAG O operate
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Doetinchem
7 WORDTAG O choice
10 WORDTAG O lifted
6 WORDTAG I-PER An
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sakigake
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp.
6 WORDTAG O stand
14 WORDTAG O rupiah
19 WORDTAG O wanted
6 WORDTAG O arriving
12 WORDTAG O site
23 WORDTAG O single
1 WORDTAG O Social
6 WORDTAG O citizen
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Baltimore
20 WORDTAG O quiet
5 WORDTAG I-PER Veldman
86 WORDTAG O meeting
46 WORDTAG O later
6 WORDTAG O confiscated
6 WORDTAG O makers
24 WORDTAG O leave
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
1 WORDTAG I-MISC My
5 WORDTAG O model
5 WORDTAG O bushel
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Antwerp
6 WORDTAG I-PER Capiot
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamists
5 WORDTAG I-PER Dick
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northern
9 WORDTAG O cross
6 WORDTAG O affairs
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taylor
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
33 WORDTAG O shot
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlantic
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hurricane
49 WORDTAG O demand
14 WORDTAG O veteran
840 WORDTAG O with
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bastia
8 WORDTAG O bed
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Treaty
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
8 WORDTAG O first-round
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Super
18 WORDTAG I-PER Saeed
25 WORDTAG O percentage
22 WORDTAG O 3-6
7 WORDTAG O kick
660 WORDTAG I-MISC _CAP_
10 WORDTAG I-PER Colin
10 WORDTAG O finish
8 WORDTAG O candidates
1 WORDTAG I-PER Virginia
10 WORDTAG O study
17 WORDTAG O visited
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Port
5 WORDTAG O riders
29 WORDTAG O better
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Zurich
5 WORDTAG O effectively
6 WORDTAG O incidents
12 WORDTAG O candidate
23 WORDTAG O line
10 WORDTAG O certain
46 WORDTAG O men
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Paulo
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
21 WORDTAG O ordered
9 WORDTAG O version
23 WORDTAG O lot
6 WORDTAG O renegade
122 WORDTAG O round
17 WORDTAG O church
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ulihrach
67 WORDTAG O our
1 WORDTAG O Winners
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Milan
7 WORDTAG O Its
57 WORDTAG O rate
11 WORDTAG I-PER Simon
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
47 WORDTAG O championship
6 WORDTAG O sound
11 WORDTAG O hostage
6 WORDTAG O forcing
5 WORDTAG O seems
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dennis
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Arab
2994 WORDTAG O a
8 WORDTAG O cotton
5 WORDTAG O 6.5
59 WORDTAG O prices
9 WORDTAG O vehicle
271 WORDTAG O over
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Arsenal
12 WORDTAG O debut
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Northamptonshire
15 WORDTAG O wicket
7 WORDTAG O possibly
31 WORDTAG O rates
8 WORDTAG I-PER Darren
7 WORDTAG O greatest
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Supreme
6 WORDTAG O refined
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Istanbul
5 WORDTAG O elsewhere
6 WORDTAG O cover
1 WORDTAG I-MISC President
6 WORDTAG O 14.
37 WORDTAG O future
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bosnian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Le
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
6 WORDTAG O rider
7 WORDTAG O founded
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Series
21 WORDTAG O plant
12 WORDTAG O soldier
16 WORDTAG O General
12166 WORDTAG O _DIGIT_
6 WORDTAG I-ORG China
7 WORDTAG O restaurant
68 WORDTAG I-LOC Iraq
12 WORDTAG O long-term
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Reds
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Soviet
8 WORDTAG O rare
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Amman
6 WORDTAG O tourist
1 WORDTAG O University
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yankees
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dodgers
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
102 WORDTAG O lost
15 WORDTAG O bat
6 WORDTAG O bombing
131 WORDTAG O '
14 WORDTAG O +44
6 WORDTAG O yield
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Dutch
6 WORDTAG I-PER Miller
2 WORDTAG I-ORG War
79 WORDTAG I-ORG Reuters
25 WORDTAG O poor
12 WORDTAG O software
75 WORDTAG O innings
12 WORDTAG O managed
14 WORDTAG I-PER Greg
8 WORDTAG O animal
38 WORDTAG O region
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Los
10 WORDTAG O growing
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Gas
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Haitai
31 WORDTAG O woman
43 WORDTAG O power
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Cincinnati
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
9 WORDTAG O visiting
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sosa
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Swindon
9 WORDTAG O yuan
26 WORDTAG O services
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Post
8 WORDTAG O tension
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alami
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
7 WORDTAG O foreigners
9 WORDTAG O three-game
20 WORDTAG O included
17 WORDTAG O largest
17 WORDTAG O difficult
4 WORDTAG I-PER Wolf
56 WORDTAG O months
5 WORDTAG O wells
18 WORDTAG O dealer
6 WORDTAG O affect
5 WORDTAG I-PER Lamm
4 WORDTAG O 21st
7 WORDTAG O attending
9 WORDTAG O republic
13 WORDTAG O numbers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG World
5 WORDTAG O riding
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Krakow
10 WORDTAG O Deputy
25 WORDTAG O change
37 WORDTAG O control
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
9 WORDTAG O collided
7 WORDTAG O reveal
5 WORDTAG O stockpile
7 WORDTAG O truth
9 WORDTAG O someone
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Dinamo
11 WORDTAG O streets
10 WORDTAG O jailed
17 WORDTAG O 1-6
5 WORDTAG I-ORG People
5 WORDTAG O pace
112 WORDTAG O five
11 WORDTAG O request
28 WORDTAG O earnings
18 WORDTAG O doing
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Poland
95 WORDTAG O 2.
25 WORDTAG O island
5 WORDTAG O tree
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Japanese
7 WORDTAG O timetable
76 WORDTAG O took
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Giants
17 WORDTAG O landed
15 WORDTAG O heart
6 WORDTAG O itself
6 WORDTAG O controversial
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
14 WORDTAG O activity
6 WORDTAG O becoming
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mitchell
13 WORDTAG O convicted
7 WORDTAG I-PER Koerts
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
7 WORDTAG O class
3 WORDTAG I-LOC University
37 WORDTAG O working
6 WORDTAG I-PER McEwen
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Warsaw
6 WORDTAG O disarmament
17 WORDTAG I-ORG News
37 WORDTAG O cash
7 WORDTAG O cent
23 WORDTAG O whose
30 WORDTAG O old
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Labour
8 WORDTAG O snap
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ruch
5 WORDTAG O require
9 WORDTAG O partner
9 WORDTAG I-PER Enqvist
22 WORDTAG O far
5 WORDTAG O boycott
103 WORDTAG O 1996-08-23
8 WORDTAG O rivals
2 WORDTAG I-PER Spot
37 WORDTAG I-PER Akram
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bielefeld
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Canberra
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Congress
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Law
6 WORDTAG O maximum
6 WORDTAG O sentiment
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Massachusetts
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 4.0
55 WORDTAG O opposition
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
9 WORDTAG I-PER Campbell
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jens
21 WORDTAG O hijackers
42 WORDTAG O oil
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Sudan
5 WORDTAG O preferred
1 WORDTAG I-ORG am
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Indonesian
6 WORDTAG O fails
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
8 WORDTAG O treated
9 WORDTAG O 1996-08-30
11 WORDTAG I-PER Frank
15 WORDTAG O driver
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kevin
349 WORDTAG O two
5 WORDTAG O intends
25 WORDTAG O continue
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Islamic
11 WORDTAG O takes
716 WORDTAG O by
6 WORDTAG O offset
5 WORDTAG O laps
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Battle
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Nikkei
5 WORDTAG O businessman
8 WORDTAG O Her
8 WORDTAG O systems
11 WORDTAG O previously
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blackburn
8 WORDTAG O none
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Essex
29 WORDTAG O captain
45 WORDTAG O came
25 WORDTAG O even
15 WORDTAG O moment
24 WORDTAG I-MISC Turkish
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nijmegen
6 WORDTAG O multiple
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhaka
20 WORDTAG O mission
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventus
16 WORDTAG O building
5 WORDTAG O Queen
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Australia
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kiev
18 WORDTAG O post
1 WORDTAG I-PER of
6 WORDTAG O increasing
5 WORDTAG O autumn
18 WORDTAG O sale
32 WORDTAG O If
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
6 WORDTAG I-LOC S.
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Charlton
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Most
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southern
57 WORDTAG O trade
9 WORDTAG O college
26 WORDTAG O buy
7 WORDTAG O Third
6 WORDTAG O dated
164 WORDTAG O no
10 WORDTAG O customers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Villeneuve
15 WORDTAG O pact
8 WORDTAG O mandate
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vaduz
11 WORDTAG O protection
6 WORDTAG O .538
14 WORDTAG O snapped
33 WORDTAG O bonds
51 WORDTAG O drawn
1 WORDTAG I-ORG motor
32 WORDTAG O free
6 WORDTAG O consensus
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lehman
4 WORDTAG O School
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Aki
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Doncaster
11 WORDTAG O faction
8 WORDTAG O margins
6 WORDTAG O boosted
5 WORDTAG O Premier
37 WORDTAG O died
125 WORDTAG O only
28 WORDTAG O unless
5 WORDTAG O allied
11 WORDTAG O tough
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Suwon
11 WORDTAG O doctors
8 WORDTAG I-PER Maleeva
10 WORDTAG O drive
62 WORDTAG O war
13 WORDTAG O helped
22 WORDTAG O killing
48 WORDTAG O already
6 WORDTAG O ....
14 WORDTAG O almost
42 WORDTAG O countries
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Auckland
5 WORDTAG O walkover
8 WORDTAG I-PER Smith
5 WORDTAG O reigning
36 WORDTAG O conference
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
11 WORDTAG O prevent
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Names
23 WORDTAG O decided
51 WORDTAG O another
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
3 WORDTAG O Ten
20 WORDTAG O couple
11 WORDTAG O Our
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Monaco
19 WORDTAG O analyst
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Southampton
5 WORDTAG O Commander
5 WORDTAG O deny
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Spanish
12 WORDTAG O First
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ivanisevic
8 WORDTAG O repeatedly
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
19 WORDTAG O remained
51 WORDTAG I-PER Paul
12 WORDTAG I-PER Washington
5 WORDTAG O .527
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Switzerland
36 WORDTAG O tour
36 WORDTAG O does
24 WORDTAG I-ORG London
5 WORDTAG O films
6 WORDTAG O signal
5 WORDTAG O quake
23 WORDTAG O armed
28 WORDTAG O rise
155 WORDTAG O But
34 WORDTAG O order
6 WORDTAG O seat
6 WORDTAG O expects
5 WORDTAG O Health
19 WORDTAG O ball
91 WORDTAG O matches
6 WORDTAG O killer
11 WORDTAG I-PER James
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Surrey
120 WORDTAG O match
28 WORDTAG O soon
2 WORDTAG O Stock
25 WORDTAG O prefix
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Arab
36 WORDTAG O March
8 WORDTAG O lift
12 WORDTAG O significant
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Pacific
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
8 WORDTAG O landing
15 WORDTAG O fight
30 WORDTAG O call
16 WORDTAG O walked
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Milan
7 WORDTAG O Earlier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Blacks
5 WORDTAG O association
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Algerian
5 WORDTAG O bottle
14 WORDTAG O guerrilla
14 WORDTAG O suspected
8 WORDTAG O medal
11 WORDTAG O 15-11
13 WORDTAG O west
10 WORDTAG O hurt
34 WORDTAG I-PER Thomas
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Canada
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Hungary
5 WORDTAG O remarkable
9 WORDTAG O People
12 WORDTAG I-PER Rose
43 WORDTAG O agreement
3 WORDTAG B-MISC Super
5 WORDTAG O instructions
21 WORDTAG O copper
15 WORDTAG O rugby
3 WORDTAG O Rugby
15 WORDTAG I-ORG San
19 WORDTAG O risk
5 WORDTAG O Gas
144 WORDTAG O time
36 WORDTAG O ceasefire
5 WORDTAG O promoted
25 WORDTAG I-PER Netanyahu
10 WORDTAG O why
6 WORDTAG O bids
29 WORDTAG O An
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Red
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Centre
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesex
12 WORDTAG O show
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Treasury
13 WORDTAG O issued
5 WORDTAG O crown
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Sox
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Saudi
147 WORDTAG O week
9 WORDTAG O nearby
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
19 WORDTAG O Division
17 WORDTAG I-PER van
9 WORDTAG O holding
104 WORDTAG I-ORG of
143 WORDTAG O could
27 WORDTAG O border
280 WORDTAG O million
5 WORDTAG O 5.5
16 WORDTAG O water
6 WORDTAG O highly
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Wellman
5 WORDTAG O parent
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rights
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Division
6 WORDTAG O briefly
5 WORDTAG O fined
1 WORDTAG I-ORG democracy
98 WORDTAG O back
57 WORDTAG O cents
25 WORDTAG O ground
28 WORDTAG O see
7 WORDTAG I-PER El
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
726 WORDTAG I-MISC _RARE_
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Oklahoma
25 WORDTAG O tie
36 WORDTAG O might
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Leeds
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Central
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hungary
5 WORDTAG O word
13 WORDTAG O accident
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Brisbane
6 WORDTAG O publicly
8 WORDTAG O baht
6 WORDTAG O easy
7 WORDTAG O humanitarian
86 WORDTAG O being
19 WORDTAG O bought
38 WORDTAG O attack
7 WORDTAG O launch
20 WORDTAG O costs
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
1 WORDTAG I-ORG bureau
7 WORDTAG O equaliser
42 WORDTAG O away
95 WORDTAG O president
52 WORDTAG I-MISC _DIGIT_
7 WORDTAG O 11.
5 WORDTAG O fewer
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Antwerp
10 WORDTAG O research
30 WORDTAG O details
22 WORDTAG I-PER Johnson
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sale
48 WORDTAG O many
8 WORDTAG O aged
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
8 WORDTAG O infusion
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nicolas
5 WORDTAG O Sir
5 WORDTAG O Financial
5 WORDTAG O substantial
5 WORDTAG O .466
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Montpellier
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Monde
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Mariners
9 WORDTAG O doubles
22 WORDTAG O protest
6 WORDTAG I-PER Phil
6 WORDTAG O widespread
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Marseille
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Akron
7 WORDTAG O stabbed
9 WORDTAG I-PER Reagan
41 WORDTAG O main
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
6 WORDTAG O dn
14 WORDTAG O announcement
8 WORDTAG O talking
6 WORDTAG O Income
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gingrich
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Minnesota
11 WORDTAG O send
6 WORDTAG O Summaries
8 WORDTAG O observers
9 WORDTAG I-PER Fred
11 WORDTAG I-PER Arantxa
5 WORDTAG O paint
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Atlanta
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Microsoft
4 WORDTAG I-ORG 'S
13 WORDTAG I-PER Marc
15 WORDTAG O property
11 WORDTAG O gained
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Zabrze
34 WORDTAG O members
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Louis
7 WORDTAG O warrants
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Tokyo
13 WORDTAG O injuries
14 WORDTAG O crew
9 WORDTAG O shown
9 WORDTAG O failure
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
7 WORDTAG O balls
8 WORDTAG I-PER Svetlana
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dacom
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
8 WORDTAG I-LOC de
13 WORDTAG I-PER Lauck
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Tour
110 WORDTAG I-LOC Spain
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Games
2036 WORDTAG O on
6 WORDTAG O families
10 WORDTAG O additional
5 WORDTAG O Asked
4 WORDTAG O Price
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
8 WORDTAG O became
22 WORDTAG O drug
10 WORDTAG O Note
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam
5336 WORDTAG I-PER _RARE_
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lincoln
47 WORDTAG O following
14 WORDTAG O Secretary
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
12 WORDTAG O session
6 WORDTAG I-PER Takemura
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Arabs
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tom
7 WORDTAG I-PER Baker
23 WORDTAG O similar
6 WORDTAG O legislature
1 WORDTAG I-MISC First
9 WORDTAG O Their
1 WORDTAG O Radio
2178 WORDTAG O "
18 WORDTAG O probably
25 WORDTAG O rebel
5 WORDTAG O blown
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lincoln
14 WORDTAG O body
5 WORDTAG O laws
5 WORDTAG O aims
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
11 WORDTAG O retired
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Third
5 WORDTAG O tell
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamas
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mozambique
5 WORDTAG O sexual
10 WORDTAG I-PER Tendulkar
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
6 WORDTAG O yards
28 WORDTAG O how
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Preston
10 WORDTAG O clash
5 WORDTAG O aboard
13 WORDTAG O fired
5 WORDTAG O sexually
25 WORDTAG O problem
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
303 WORDTAG O percent
8 WORDTAG I-PER Perry
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Aires
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tranmere
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hingis
59 WORDTAG O both
9 WORDTAG O stable
12 WORDTAG O leadership
6 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
29 WORDTAG O got
7 WORDTAG O assessment
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Colombian
25 WORDTAG O here
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kaluwitharana
11 WORDTAG I-PER Wilson
5 WORDTAG O otherwise
23 WORDTAG O land
7 WORDTAG I-PER Judith
2 WORDTAG O Civil
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Charity
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Company
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Miss
10 WORDTAG O barrels
9 WORDTAG I-ORG White
5 WORDTAG O window
14 WORDTAG O homes
6 WORDTAG O limit
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Toronto
5 WORDTAG O excellent
1 WORDTAG I-MISC telling
5 WORDTAG O representing
3 WORDTAG O Tennis
35 WORDTAG O us
100 WORDTAG O 6-2
21 WORDTAG O cricket
1039 WORDTAG I-LOC _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O suits
7 WORDTAG I-PER Yoshikawa
6 WORDTAG O District
18 WORDTAG O commission
5 WORDTAG O decisive
4 WORDTAG I-LOC .
5 WORDTAG O venue
6 WORDTAG O beyond
6 WORDTAG O units
8 WORDTAG O Sale
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eddie
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Frankfurt
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Election
9 WORDTAG I-PER Roger
9 WORDTAG O midnight
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Romanian
8 WORDTAG O route
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
84 WORDTAG O peace
5 WORDTAG I-PER V.
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linhart
6 WORDTAG O respect
12 WORDTAG O gun
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johansson
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Colorado
5 WORDTAG O unseeded
8 WORDTAG O apparently
10 WORDTAG O suffering
7 WORDTAG O flown
12 WORDTAG O dismissed
7 WORDTAG O 8.0
4 WORDTAG O Ministry
8 WORDTAG O difficulties
5 WORDTAG O fairly
20 WORDTAG O name
16 WORDTAG O forward
8 WORDTAG O Over
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kandahar
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
5 WORDTAG O negotiator
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
29 WORDTAG O named
9 WORDTAG O replace
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jimmy
9 WORDTAG O earned
7 WORDTAG O hog
6 WORDTAG O hat-trick
18 WORDTAG O believe
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Durham
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Norwegian
5 WORDTAG O cannabis
155 WORDTAG O Sunday
4 WORDTAG O Hurricane
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc.
18 WORDTAG B-ORG _CAP_
5 WORDTAG O referendum
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Women
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
5 WORDTAG O taxi
12 WORDTAG O quickly
16 WORDTAG O a.m.
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Park
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
6 WORDTAG O athletes
6 WORDTAG I-PER Basuki
5 WORDTAG O demands
6 WORDTAG O wages
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Iran
16 WORDTAG O seventh
26 WORDTAG O Total
5 WORDTAG O missionary
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Werder
6 WORDTAG I-PER Marcus
56 WORDTAG O gave
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hatoyama
13 WORDTAG O purchase
1 WORDTAG I-MISC law
36 WORDTAG O 're
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Stirling
7 WORDTAG O successive
8 WORDTAG O concerned
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
14 WORDTAG O data
8 WORDTAG I-PER Charles
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wroclaw
5 WORDTAG O highlights
8 WORDTAG O threat
10 WORDTAG O peso
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Port
5 WORDTAG O violation
9 WORDTAG O stepped
8 WORDTAG O definitely
3 WORDTAG O Workers
7 WORDTAG O check
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Sarajevo
11 WORDTAG O however
8 WORDTAG O ceremony
46 WORDTAG I-LOC West
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
78 WORDTAG O around
11 WORDTAG O mother
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
25 WORDTAG I-PER Bill
10 WORDTAG O billions
11 WORDTAG O using
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Arab
10 WORDTAG O three-run
20 WORDTAG O His
21 WORDTAG I-PER Richard
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rovers
6 WORDTAG O Chg
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ipswich
8 WORDTAG O gets
15 WORDTAG O provide
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sierra
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
388 WORDTAG O first
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Desk
22 WORDTAG O bomb
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
6 WORDTAG O unfortunate
3 WORDTAG O interior
15 WORDTAG I-ORG State
6 WORDTAG O impossible
12 WORDTAG O involving
11 WORDTAG O feet
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
10 WORDTAG O relief
5 WORDTAG O importance
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Rome
7 WORDTAG O yesterday
30 WORDTAG O law
25 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchange
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mohammad
5 WORDTAG O blocked
40 WORDTAG O business
5 WORDTAG O meets
306 WORDTAG O they
6 WORDTAG O livestock
17 WORDTAG O pair
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
109 WORDTAG O President
1 WORDTAG I-LOC hospital
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Johannesburg
19 WORDTAG O orders
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Journal
16 WORDTAG O family
7 WORDTAG O mean
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bernd
14 WORDTAG O auction
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sharif
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Virginia
7 WORDTAG O river
15 WORDTAG I-PER Diana
8 WORDTAG O shows
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Saskatchewan
37 WORDTAG O led
7 WORDTAG O sterling
5 WORDTAG O quick
3157 WORDTAG O _CAP_
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Alaska
1 WORDTAG I-MISC is
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Russian
2 WORDTAG I-PER Charlton
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Hamburg
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Conference
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mikael
5 WORDTAG O northwest
5 WORDTAG I-PER Adams
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Canberra
26 WORDTAG O struck
12 WORDTAG O recovery
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Field
2 WORDTAG O Press
15 WORDTAG O delayed
12 WORDTAG O scoring
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Carlos
17 WORDTAG I-PER J.
6 WORDTAG O minimum
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sun
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Ducati
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pinas
8 WORDTAG O veterinary
36 WORDTAG O case
111 WORDTAG O him
40 WORDTAG O c
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Argentine
10 WORDTAG O beef
9 WORDTAG O preparing
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northern
5 WORDTAG O membership
20 WORDTAG O products
37 WORDTAG O best
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Data
7 WORDTAG O versus
11 WORDTAG O fast
7 WORDTAG O partners
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
30 WORDTAG O squad
14 WORDTAG O shortly
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Union
12 WORDTAG O welfare
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bedie
5 WORDTAG I-PER Flower
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Kingdom
11 WORDTAG O lei
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Industry
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ireland
48 WORDTAG O including
15 WORDTAG O either
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bureau
39 WORDTAG O area
32 WORDTAG O standings
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Armed
10 WORDTAG I-PER Johan
5 WORDTAG O winds
75 WORDTAG O number
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Benetton
6 WORDTAG O heads
1 WORDTAG I-ORG bank
1 WORDTAG O Black
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Austria
7 WORDTAG O ca
5 WORDTAG I-PER Aki
25 WORDTAG O conditions
45 WORDTAG O work
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wolverhampton
20 WORDTAG O find
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Ohio
2 WORDTAG O Open
3 WORDTAG O Centre
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Reef
13 WORDTAG O bourse
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tyrrell
13 WORDTAG O buying
7 WORDTAG O copies
19 WORDTAG O release
9 WORDTAG O politicians
8 WORDTAG O fever
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Dm
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Guerrero
37 WORDTAG O without
6 WORDTAG I-ORG India
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Ssangbangwool
27 WORDTAG I-LOC East
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazprom
8 WORDTAG O treatment
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Leeds
25 WORDTAG O wife
5 WORDTAG O Seven
6 WORDTAG O Dec
6 WORDTAG O 212-859-1650
5 WORDTAG O crossing
6 WORDTAG O 15-9
120 WORDTAG O off
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Wimbledon
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
83 WORDTAG O talks
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Mideast
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Research
13 WORDTAG O And
15 WORDTAG O kidnapped
72 WORDTAG O foreign
7 WORDTAG O hot
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erbakan
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rally
10 WORDTAG O danger
6 WORDTAG O estimate
7 WORDTAG O organisations
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lance
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Honda
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Financial
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Federation
7 WORDTAG I-PER Sergi
16 WORDTAG O cooperation
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
35 WORDTAG O average
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Belgian
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Philadelphia
9 WORDTAG O knew
9 WORDTAG O jump
5 WORDTAG O pulp
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Khartoum
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
14 WORDTAG O tight
11 WORDTAG O attend
15 WORDTAG I-PER S.
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Bombay
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Zurich
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
15 WORDTAG O administration
59 WORDTAG O town
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Philip
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
5 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Soviet
6 WORDTAG O secure
6 WORDTAG O 3-2
8 WORDTAG I-PER Julie
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Year
7 WORDTAG O failing
6 WORDTAG O slaughter
8 WORDTAG O construction
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Haj
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslems
5 WORDTAG O five-run
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Commodities
10 WORDTAG O sprint
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Patriotic
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Nottingham
13 WORDTAG O stages
13 WORDTAG O gross
32 WORDTAG I-LOC Bank
19 WORDTAG O charge
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kenny
15 WORDTAG O protests
57 WORDTAG O make
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Russians
22 WORDTAG O premier
19 WORDTAG O governor
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Germany
5 WORDTAG O escaped
6 WORDTAG O safety
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Bangladesh
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Assembly
29 WORDTAG O process
10 WORDTAG O proposal
15 WORDTAG O light
8 WORDTAG O Gov
1 WORDTAG O East
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Bundesliga
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Queens
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mother
22 WORDTAG I-PER Alex
5 WORDTAG O titles
11 WORDTAG O determine
26 WORDTAG O tried
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
7 WORDTAG O abuses
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Belarus
15 WORDTAG O consumer
5 WORDTAG I-PER Oliver
19 WORDTAG O competition
6 WORDTAG O believes
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Bucharest
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Southampton
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Trent
3 WORDTAG O Club
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Gulf
10 WORDTAG O scattered
14 WORDTAG O factions
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Americans
9 WORDTAG O custody
16 WORDTAG O passenger
5 WORDTAG I-PER Larry
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
5 WORDTAG O walking
14 WORDTAG O seeking
18 WORDTAG O bln
14 WORDTAG O join
25 WORDTAG O parties
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Czech
61 WORDTAG O close
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlanta
5 WORDTAG O producers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Guzman
19 WORDTAG O sign
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Petroleum
3382 WORDTAG O to
7 WORDTAG O continuing
5 WORDTAG O larger
6 WORDTAG O dissidents
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wells
5 WORDTAG O pending
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Zealand
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Texas
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Zaire
53 WORDTAG O agreed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kingdom
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wolf
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Oklahoma
7 WORDTAG O fallen
9 WORDTAG O capped
356 WORDTAG O --
9 WORDTAG O permission
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jorge
5 WORDTAG O From
5 WORDTAG O load
2 WORDTAG I-MISC championship
7 WORDTAG O affected
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dean
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rennes
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rangarajan
10 WORDTAG O Officials
16 WORDTAG O voters
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mary
7 WORDTAG O Jan
3 WORDTAG I-PER McCarthy
13 WORDTAG O begin
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
13 WORDTAG O weaker
26 WORDTAG O gold
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kan
11 WORDTAG O Revenue
39 WORDTAG O Standings
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sun
10 WORDTAG O guilty
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Belgrade
27 WORDTAG O road
5 WORDTAG O 11.00
6 WORDTAG O scientist
16 WORDTAG O job
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Arthur
12 WORDTAG O offices
8 WORDTAG O hijacking
6 WORDTAG O operator
7 WORDTAG O hearing
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
7 WORDTAG O customer
5 WORDTAG I-PER Prince
10 WORDTAG O witnesses
24 WORDTAG O treaty
1 WORDTAG O Championship
35 WORDTAG O overs
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Larnaca
9 WORDTAG O captured
74 WORDTAG O days
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
6 WORDTAG O placings
9 WORDTAG O together
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Cyprus
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Catholic
86 WORDTAG O They
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Boston
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ,
14 WORDTAG O walk
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bonds
7 WORDTAG O stance
5 WORDTAG O trafficking
43 WORDTAG O This
11 WORDTAG O premium
5 WORDTAG O div
33 WORDTAG O rose
7 WORDTAG O troubled
21 WORDTAG O stocks
58 WORDTAG O put
35 WORDTAG O prime
10 WORDTAG O row
5 WORDTAG O Only
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wednesday
1 WORDTAG O Air
22 WORDTAG O important
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
11 WORDTAG O surplus
12 WORDTAG O income
5 WORDTAG O penalties
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Wall
16 WORDTAG O losses
6 WORDTAG O reply
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hansa
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mapei
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pires
12 WORDTAG O resume
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Europe
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Washington
10 WORDTAG O serve
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Roman
10 WORDTAG O sentenced
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Basque
5 WORDTAG O farms
23 WORDTAG O offer
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
13 WORDTAG O hands
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Ford
7 WORDTAG O exact
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Day
8 WORDTAG O remove
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jeff
5 WORDTAG O 12th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG is
5 WORDTAG O weakening
9 WORDTAG O allegedly
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Fiorentina
80 WORDTAG O take
36 WORDTAG O little
5 WORDTAG O shift
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royal
5 WORDTAG O Five
6 WORDTAG I-PER Karina
10 WORDTAG O committed
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Linz
13 WORDTAG O claimed
9 WORDTAG O lose
127 WORDTAG O company
15 WORDTAG O currently
13 WORDTAG O accept
8 WORDTAG O rallied
8 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neal
2 WORDTAG O Investors
7 WORDTAG O privatization
34 WORDTAG O service
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Group
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Saskatchewan
12 WORDTAG O barter
6 WORDTAG O dealing
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vatican
557 WORDTAG O has
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mia
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Home
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Four
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Security
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Sri
5 WORDTAG O investigations
12 WORDTAG I-PER Maria
5 WORDTAG O YEAR-AGO
27 WORDTAG O straight
14 WORDTAG O rally
5 WORDTAG O acquire
15 WORDTAG I-PER Peres
507 WORDTAG O an
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Prague
37 WORDTAG O club
7 WORDTAG O holders
7 WORDTAG I-PER McGrath
12 WORDTAG O boost
23 WORDTAG O trial
17 WORDTAG O concern
5 WORDTAG O eye
17 WORDTAG O although
12 WORDTAG O front
6 WORDTAG O Despite
10 WORDTAG O announce
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
13 WORDTAG O entering
306 WORDTAG O its
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Munich
6 WORDTAG O relay
21 WORDTAG O black
8 WORDTAG O handling
20 WORDTAG I-PER N.
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Four
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Peace
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Service
9 WORDTAG O present
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
21 WORDTAG O sector
19 WORDTAG I-ORG Democratic
40 WORDTAG O army
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Montreal
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Puchon
13 WORDTAG O address
10 WORDTAG O create
10 WORDTAG O apartheid
5 WORDTAG O skilled
5 WORDTAG O restored
34 WORDTAG O across
26 WORDTAG O nuclear
30 WORDTAG O yen
6 WORDTAG O editorial
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Christian
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
9 WORDTAG O largely
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
20 WORDTAG O steady
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Palace
9 WORDTAG O researchers
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Stuttgart
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Tibet
9 WORDTAG I-ORG County
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Gaza
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
11 WORDTAG I-ORG )
8 WORDTAG O ousted
122 WORDTAG O there
8 WORDTAG O keeping
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Guingamp
9 WORDTAG O values
5 WORDTAG O MPs
9 WORDTAG O addition
15 WORDTAG O presence
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Sao
43 WORDTAG O share
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahamas
37 WORDTAG O available
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostock
63 WORDTAG O 7-5
26 WORDTAG I-PER Mullally
17 WORDTAG I-PER Van
10 WORDTAG I-PER Bailey
13 WORDTAG I-PER Gary
6 WORDTAG O drought
98 WORDTAG O shares
5 WORDTAG O defenders
1 WORDTAG O Research
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Phillies
5 WORDTAG I-PER Foe
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 12th
34 WORDTAG O October
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Hungarian
12 WORDTAG O afternoon
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
18 WORDTAG O life
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardiff
5 WORDTAG O 59th
7 WORDTAG O embargo
12 WORDTAG O millions
602 WORDTAG O as
5 WORDTAG B-MISC _CAP_
6 WORDTAG O alone
6 WORDTAG I-MISC serie
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bulgaria
7 WORDTAG O camp
17 WORDTAG O investment
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Alaska
24 WORDTAG O denotes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Milan
4 WORDTAG I-PER Games
9 WORDTAG O success
7 WORDTAG O grenades
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Internet
13 WORDTAG O 11th
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kucera
16973 WORDTAG O _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O badly
9 WORDTAG O H1
88 WORDTAG I-LOC Russia
16 WORDTAG O accuracy
44 WORDTAG I-PER Dole
6 WORDTAG I-PER Michelle
9 WORDTAG I-LOC of
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Nepali
5 WORDTAG O iron
28 WORDTAG O believed
5 WORDTAG O 60th
14 WORDTAG O 6-7
7 WORDTAG O true
5 WORDTAG O riyal
53 WORDTAG O until
6 WORDTAG O amid
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Unita
31 WORDTAG O 2-0
7 WORDTAG O hear
5 WORDTAG O unclear
23 WORDTAG O investors
4 WORDTAG I-PER Allenby
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Massachusetts
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbian
1 WORDTAG O Reserve
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Warsaw
39 WORDTAG O growth
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Moenchengladbach
7 WORDTAG I-PER Date
2 WORDTAG O Industry
4 WORDTAG O Armed
13 WORDTAG O responsible
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Preston
59 WORDTAG O lower
6 WORDTAG O pushed
5 WORDTAG O set-top
12 WORDTAG O rather
8 WORDTAG O century
6 WORDTAG O pitched
5 WORDTAG O dozens
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
13 WORDTAG O investigators
18 WORDTAG O range
7 WORDTAG O kidnapping
45 WORDTAG O way
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aslan
36 WORDTAG I-LOC Ireland
5 WORDTAG O wing
8 WORDTAG O organised
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Karlsruhe
11 WORDTAG O material
126 WORDTAG O Saturday
6 WORDTAG O attempted
7 WORDTAG O venture
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Singapore
17 WORDTAG O arrest
11 WORDTAG O advantage
1 WORDTAG I-ORG central
3 WORDTAG I-PER Louis
561 WORDTAG O had
6 WORDTAG O highest
36 WORDTAG O sent
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Royal
6 WORDTAG O dragged
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Queen
6 WORDTAG O ratio
16 WORDTAG O Extras
1 WORDTAG I-PER Colombo
11 WORDTAG I-PER Tony
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
5 WORDTAG O Socialist
17 WORDTAG O resignation
5 WORDTAG O metal
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
1 WORDTAG O War
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
22 WORDTAG O tabulated
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gold
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grobbelaar
7 WORDTAG O deposit
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Libya
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Street
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ruch
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Middle
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wells
7 WORDTAG I-PER Kabariti
19 WORDTAG O farmers
5 WORDTAG O partly
362 WORDTAG O $
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Men
16 WORDTAG O scores
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Portsmouth
29 WORDTAG O daily
10 WORDTAG O leads
14 WORDTAG O product
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
59 WORDTAG O eight
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Wheat
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Miami
16 WORDTAG O positions
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
9 WORDTAG O comes
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Kawasaki
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
17 WORDTAG O among
23 WORDTAG O Scorers
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
9 WORDTAG O enter
5 WORDTAG O soybeans
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Reform
181 WORDTAG O Friday
15 WORDTAG O owned
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
5 WORDTAG O shr
80 WORDTAG O held
6 WORDTAG O faster
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Jewish
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Championship
7 WORDTAG O sentence
8 WORDTAG I-ORG in
6 WORDTAG O developed
11 WORDTAG O estimates
31 WORDTAG O fifth
16 WORDTAG I-PER Martinez
40 WORDTAG O scored
92 WORDTAG O while
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
8 WORDTAG O station
1 WORDTAG O Wheat
43 WORDTAG O test
5 WORDTAG O usual
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greece
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
12 WORDTAG O strategic
2 WORDTAG I-LOC free
12 WORDTAG O allegations
3 WORDTAG I-ORG England
7 WORDTAG O tied
30 WORDTAG O That
8 WORDTAG O shut
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brush
7 WORDTAG I-PER Liam
12 WORDTAG O direct
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Human
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Itar-Tass
46 WORDTAG O authorities
14 WORDTAG O grand
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Angeles
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Liu
5 WORDTAG O engine
5 WORDTAG O +7095
5 WORDTAG O youth
20 WORDTAG O votes
15 WORDTAG O houses
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Calcutta
19 WORDTAG O 4-6
20 WORDTAG O dropped
52 WORDTAG I-MISC Australian
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Rwandan
34 WORDTAG O airport
4 WORDTAG I-ORG District
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Old
7 WORDTAG O certainly
16 WORDTAG O recently
2 WORDTAG O Council
5 WORDTAG O Gluten
36 WORDTAG O ban
27 WORDTAG O levels
15 WORDTAG O avoid
5 WORDTAG I-PER Arnold
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tankan
5 WORDTAG O cast
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
58 WORDTAG O deal
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Lankan
1 WORDTAG O Mother
40 WORDTAG O rights
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Council
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gold
8 WORDTAG O 12.0
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
2 WORDTAG I-ORG States
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Togo
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Celsius
23 WORDTAG O need
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damm
5 WORDTAG O Pro
17 WORDTAG O output
133 WORDTAG O since
285 WORDTAG O Thursday
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
2 WORDTAG O Information
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Brussels
8 WORDTAG O elected
5 WORDTAG O diverted
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrix
330 WORDTAG O would
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jack
21 WORDTAG O federal
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Index
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
5 WORDTAG O particularly
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Petra
6 WORDTAG O rice
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Notts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Arch
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ken
5 WORDTAG O setting
5 WORDTAG O Opposition
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazeta
28 WORDTAG O halftime
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joyce
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costantino
56 WORDTAG O pct
6 WORDTAG O 26th
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arminia
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rwanda
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
9 WORDTAG I-PER Brunswijk
23 WORDTAG O complete
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weaver
71 WORDTAG O political
5 WORDTAG O painful
33 WORDTAG O Two
291 WORDTAG O out
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
19 WORDTAG I-MISC A$
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Toyota
5 WORDTAG O telling
1 WORDTAG I-LOC La
5 WORDTAG O merely
11 WORDTAG O ever
17 WORDTAG O polls
7 WORDTAG O 12.
78 WORDTAG O should
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Helens
5 WORDTAG O glass
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Valletta
74 WORDTAG O b
107 WORDTAG O third
5 WORDTAG O pursue
14 WORDTAG O secret
9 WORDTAG O rail
17 WORDTAG O rules
10 WORDTAG O threw
41 WORDTAG O north
1 WORDTAG O Central
45 WORDTAG O troops
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kelly
6 WORDTAG O acting
117 WORDTAG O down
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Swiss
163 WORDTAG O we
7 WORDTAG O festival
36 WORDTAG O right
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Total
21 WORDTAG O eastern
6 WORDTAG O medallist
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Portuguese
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Medicare
582 WORDTAG O he
16 WORDTAG O running
9 WORDTAG O rating
11 WORDTAG I-PER Boardman
1 WORDTAG I-MISC San
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Vienna
2 WORDTAG I-ORG radio
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Mitsubishi
6 WORDTAG O 32.0
50 WORDTAG O my
10 WORDTAG I-PER Andrew
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Scottish
50 WORDTAG O place
8 WORDTAG O merger
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Barrick
5 WORDTAG O ordering
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Khmer
7 WORDTAG O attempts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Amoco
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greens
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Labour
66 WORDTAG O left
8 WORDTAG O striking
8 WORDTAG I-PER Miguel
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Glamorgan
30 WORDTAG O train
5 WORDTAG O football
71 WORDTAG O per
134 WORDTAG O years
22 WORDTAG I-ORG &
24 WORDTAG O himself
34 WORDTAG O planned
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rabbani
8 WORDTAG O room
9 WORDTAG O closing
8 WORDTAG O unknown
7 WORDTAG O hopes
11 WORDTAG O 4-0
12 WORDTAG O passed
6 WORDTAG O monitoring
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferrari
5 WORDTAG O endorse
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warburg
12 WORDTAG O progress
5 WORDTAG O Data
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
7 WORDTAG O facing
13 WORDTAG O crowd
6 WORDTAG I-PER Tommi
5 WORDTAG O freedom
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Reading
29 WORDTAG O result
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Costa
17 WORDTAG O operation
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
6 WORDTAG O toward
18 WORDTAG O officers
41 WORDTAG O index
10 WORDTAG O five-year
5 WORDTAG O bush
5 WORDTAG O Nearly
6 WORDTAG O kms
6 WORDTAG O kuna
6 WORDTAG O love
10 WORDTAG O built
5 WORDTAG O handgun
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
9 WORDTAG O disappointing
5 WORDTAG O boss
6 WORDTAG O compatriot
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ligier
15 WORDTAG O figure
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Star
8 WORDTAG O backing
5 WORDTAG O realised
18 WORDTAG O diplomat
5 WORDTAG O sport
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Queensland
2 WORDTAG I-PER Angeles
60 WORDTAG O man
8 WORDTAG O schedule
1 WORDTAG O Grand
38 WORDTAG O accused
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
531 WORDTAG O were
12 WORDTAG I-MISC '
5 WORDTAG O intensive
21 WORDTAG O air
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
6 WORDTAG O contribute
34 WORDTAG O stories
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nasdaq
53 WORDTAG O dollar
5 WORDTAG O contents
16 WORDTAG O programme
1 WORDTAG O League
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
9 WORDTAG O nomination
32 WORDTAG O interest
38 WORDTAG O strike
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sion
9 WORDTAG O supplies
61 WORDTAG I-LOC London
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
11 WORDTAG O continues
368 WORDTAG O been
6 WORDTAG O Finance
19 WORDTAG O December
40 WORDTAG O major
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Medical
8 WORDTAG O arrives
14 WORDTAG O emergency
7 WORDTAG O thin
5 WORDTAG I-PER Shane
7 WORDTAG O cup
5 WORDTAG O shed
18 WORDTAG O voting
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Lithuania
4 WORDTAG I-MISC International
5 WORDTAG O projects
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Canadian
124 WORDTAG O group
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Salang
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Hong
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Treaty
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Pauli
389 WORDTAG O but
9 WORDTAG O served
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dan
12 WORDTAG O grain
9 WORDTAG O joint
5 WORDTAG O meal
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tehran
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bhutto
5 WORDTAG O returning
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
3 WORDTAG I-PER Goldman
9 WORDTAG O weak
9 WORDTAG O nor
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Red
7 WORDTAG O dark
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
9 WORDTAG O detained
12 WORDTAG I-ORG California
11 WORDTAG O distribution
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nepal
8 WORDTAG O wrist
6 WORDTAG O 70th
37 WORDTAG O ministry
6 WORDTAG O follows
6 WORDTAG O inventories
6 WORDTAG O shared
12 WORDTAG O stronger
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sandra
5 WORDTAG I-PER Healy
5 WORDTAG O garden
10 WORDTAG O carry
5 WORDTAG O searched
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
7 WORDTAG O professional
10 WORDTAG I-PER Oncins
24 WORDTAG O winner
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Zastava
14 WORDTAG O approved
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Irish
15 WORDTAG O 3-0
31 WORDTAG O term
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlanta
9 WORDTAG O consumers
53 WORDTAG O plan
6 WORDTAG O ferry
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Hutu
16 WORDTAG O caused
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
9 WORDTAG I-PER Makinen
4 WORDTAG I-PER Young
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Nelson
19 WORDTAG O 'll
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Republican
7 WORDTAG O internal
6 WORDTAG O loaded
49 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli
32 WORDTAG I-PER A.
10 WORDTAG O alliance
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Mexican
84 WORDTAG O At
8 WORDTAG I-PER Bourlet
7 WORDTAG O factors
1 WORDTAG I-MISC France
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nestor
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Convention
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
8 WORDTAG O plays
25 WORDTAG O arrived
40 WORDTAG O budget
43 WORDTAG O national
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
7 WORDTAG O surprise
2 WORDTAG I-LOC French
121 WORDTAG O 1996-08-27
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Christopher
11 WORDTAG O speech
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
6 WORDTAG O slight
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Indonesia
21 WORDTAG I-MISC C$
8 WORDTAG O required
64 WORDTAG O vs.
18 WORDTAG O drew
7 WORDTAG I-PER Eriksson
8 WORDTAG O materials
7 WORDTAG O missed
5 WORDTAG O 2.6
10 WORDTAG O ties
2 WORDTAG I-ORG magazine
46 WORDTAG I-ORG and
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Moscow
7 WORDTAG O fair
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Freiburg
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Atlanta
14 WORDTAG O supply
5 WORDTAG O Nov
68 WORDTAG O country
5 WORDTAG O recover
14 WORDTAG O launched
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
7 WORDTAG O block
13 WORDTAG O industrial
6 WORDTAG O animals
6 WORDTAG O slam
29 WORDTAG O human
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Res
13 WORDTAG O debate
5 WORDTAG O selected
14 WORDTAG I-PER Alan
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Brazil
7 WORDTAG O anyone
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Duesseldorf
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Villa
21 WORDTAG O defence
7 WORDTAG I-PER Reeve
65 WORDTAG O profit
2 WORDTAG O Army
12 WORDTAG O incident
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linford
5 WORDTAG O photographs
11 WORDTAG O 15-10
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
17 WORDTAG O adding
5 WORDTAG O complex
13 WORDTAG O target
7 WORDTAG O fuel
10 WORDTAG O pitch
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bristol
9 WORDTAG O fine
5 WORDTAG O frost
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
5 WORDTAG O finds
12 WORDTAG O What
25 WORDTAG O full
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Fortuna
21 WORDTAG O drugs
11 WORDTAG O threatening
6 WORDTAG O midday
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
11 WORDTAG O judge
160 WORDTAG O into
15 WORDTAG O heavy
38 WORDTAG O winning
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Court
10 WORDTAG O calls
45 WORDTAG O whether
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Shanghai
6 WORDTAG O reach
6 WORDTAG O starter
12 WORDTAG O 4-1
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sion
7 WORDTAG O controlled
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Spain
29 WORDTAG O action
31 WORDTAG O hospital
56 WORDTAG O There
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Seven
16 WORDTAG O Former
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Robert
9 WORDTAG O let
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Munich
8 WORDTAG O slipped
18 WORDTAG O appeared
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Everton
7 WORDTAG O holes
10 WORDTAG O cancelled
14 WORDTAG O effect
9 WORDTAG O friend
7 WORDTAG I-PER Botham
1 WORDTAG B-MISC _DIGIT_
18 WORDTAG O jail
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
7 WORDTAG I-PER Roe
14 WORDTAG O act
53 WORDTAG O price
9 WORDTAG O trillion
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
5 WORDTAG O Trade
5 WORDTAG O spinal
8 WORDTAG I-PER Andy
19 WORDTAG O Sept
8 WORDTAG O struggle
1 WORDTAG I-PER the
124 WORDTAG I-LOC England
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
6 WORDTAG O beating
28 WORDTAG O seeding
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
5 WORDTAG O giant
11 WORDTAG O reserve
5 WORDTAG O audience
5 WORDTAG O sending
9 WORDTAG O Group
8 WORDTAG O program
1 WORDTAG O van
5 WORDTAG O detective
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tass
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Athens
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Defence
167 WORDTAG O 1996-08-28
10 WORDTAG O existing
6 WORDTAG O located
10 WORDTAG O quite
49 WORDTAG O quoted
17 WORDTAG O farm
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Beirut
26 WORDTAG O illegal
10 WORDTAG O fears
6 WORDTAG O 80th
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Lille
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
60 WORDTAG O say
23 WORDTAG O %
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympics
95 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Houston
6 WORDTAG O n.a
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Jerusalem
70 WORDTAG O most
5 WORDTAG I-PER Heeswijk
5 WORDTAG O racing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rohrabacher
53 WORDTAG O 7.
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hamilton
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pittsburgh
18 WORDTAG O damage
13 WORDTAG O information
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ross
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
12 WORDTAG I-LOC White
24 WORDTAG O goal
7 WORDTAG O fun
6 WORDTAG O Current
6 WORDTAG I-PER Thomson
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Our
34 WORDTAG O Leading
30 WORDTAG O companies
21 WORDTAG O discuss
6 WORDTAG O abduction
10 WORDTAG I-PER Gajdos
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Southern
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
7 WORDTAG O avoided
8 WORDTAG O answer
12 WORDTAG O sheep
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
1 WORDTAG O Capital
14 WORDTAG O kph
7 WORDTAG O motor
10 WORDTAG O Dealers
19 WORDTAG O tender
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Home
5 WORDTAG O withdrew
5 WORDTAG O Close
5 WORDTAG O grew
6 WORDTAG O crop
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Louis
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Pacific
49 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmed
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ivorian
7 WORDTAG O strikers
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Van
15 WORDTAG O published
7 WORDTAG O +301
7 WORDTAG O .02
21 WORDTAG O injury
6 WORDTAG O mm
5 WORDTAG I-PER Patricia
8 WORDTAG O reaching
7 WORDTAG O +1
6 WORDTAG O decline
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
163 WORDTAG O won
9 WORDTAG O storm
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mayfair
10 WORDTAG O New
1 WORDTAG I-ORG High
23 WORDTAG O having
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
15 WORDTAG O towards
1 WORDTAG O Medical
63 WORDTAG O very
26 WORDTAG O senior
1 WORDTAG O Max
5 WORDTAG I-ORG interior
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Committee
2 WORDTAG I-PER Key
5 WORDTAG O baby
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Nations
18 WORDTAG O evening
7 WORDTAG O hunt
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bromwich
6 WORDTAG O motion
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
3 WORDTAG I-ORG El
9 WORDTAG O corporate
14 WORDTAG O aimed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Paris
7 WORDTAG O happen
26 WORDTAG O message
14 WORDTAG O threatened
19 WORDTAG O traffic
7275 WORDTAG O ,
30 WORDTAG O passengers
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
127 WORDTAG O state
7 WORDTAG O 12-15
5 WORDTAG O consulate
9 WORDTAG O commanding
7 WORDTAG O pledged
35 WORDTAG I-MISC Italian
16 WORDTAG O lap
8 WORDTAG I-PER Iliescu
4 WORDTAG I-PER Roosevelt
3 WORDTAG I-PER Petra
6 WORDTAG O hoped
6 WORDTAG O leftist
6 WORDTAG O intent
3 WORDTAG O Defence
1 WORDTAG O Service
97 WORDTAG O August
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lincoln
9 WORDTAG O throughout
7 WORDTAG I-PER Simpson
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Salomon
6 WORDTAG O governments
5 WORDTAG I-PER Necmettin
5 WORDTAG O dictator
21 WORDTAG O municipal
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbertson
19 WORDTAG O sets
6 WORDTAG O corn
51 WORDTAG O refugees
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Arthur
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
9 WORDTAG O response
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Porto
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
5 WORDTAG I-PER Cocu
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gingrich
1 WORDTAG I-LOC &
13 WORDTAG O blood
7 WORDTAG O brokers
5 WORDTAG O [
41 WORDTAG O money
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jon
9 WORDTAG O equal
22 WORDTAG O province
15 WORDTAG O remain
31 WORDTAG O forced
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Philadelphia
8 WORDTAG O capacity
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Yugoslavia
6 WORDTAG I-PER Conchita
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bistrita
9 WORDTAG O son
68 WORDTAG O seven
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Karachi
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
538 WORDTAG O his
8 WORDTAG O falling
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
8 WORDTAG O initially
8 WORDTAG O accord
26 WORDTAG O independence
7 WORDTAG O moving
149 WORDTAG O before
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Lens
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Breda
7 WORDTAG O abuse
4 WORDTAG I-LOC African
2 WORDTAG I-LOC )
6 WORDTAG O phase
15 WORDTAG O Fall
76 WORDTAG O party
8 WORDTAG O resign
92 WORDTAG O any
6 WORDTAG O 58th
137 WORDTAG O We
13 WORDTAG O broken
6 WORDTAG O Operating
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Trade
6 WORDTAG O receive
31 WORDTAG O opening
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Names
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicestershire
13 WORDTAG O east
10 WORDTAG O brief
6 WORDTAG O quit
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nigeria
10 WORDTAG O investigation
5 WORDTAG O defends
137 WORDTAG O points
2 WORDTAG I-LOC (
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hassan
30 WORDTAG O despite
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Indian
7 WORDTAG O activists
16 WORDTAG O admitted
16 WORDTAG I-PER Sampras
37 WORDTAG O Foreign
7 WORDTAG O moisture
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henman
11 WORDTAG I-PER Gough
5 WORDTAG I-PER Albert
37 WORDTAG O ---
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kubo
5 WORDTAG O negotiated
15 WORDTAG O starts
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
8 WORDTAG O Several
6 WORDTAG O resulted
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Doetinchem
16 WORDTAG O fact
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
5 WORDTAG O freight
5 WORDTAG I-PER Carter
89 WORDTAG O team
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
7 WORDTAG O accompanied
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Government
56 WORDTAG O Men
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Liverpool
9 WORDTAG O markka
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tommy
10 WORDTAG I-PER Maskhadov
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bonilla
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Alkmaar
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Cuba
27 WORDTAG O nearly
7 WORDTAG O prayers
11 WORDTAG O first-half
31 WORDTAG O series
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Legia
6 WORDTAG O packed
20 WORDTAG O coalition
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Barbara
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arthur
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
7 WORDTAG O original
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Oxford
12 WORDTAG O You
7 WORDTAG O sharp
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
5 WORDTAG O unbeaten
5 WORDTAG I-PER Reiffel
128 WORDTAG O all
105 WORDTAG O through
8 WORDTAG O inches
18 WORDTAG O officer
1750 WORDTAG I-ORG _CAP_
15 WORDTAG O efforts
1 WORDTAG I-MISC against
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Yugoslav
5 WORDTAG O short-term
7 WORDTAG O wage
5 WORDTAG O sheet
5 WORDTAG O cutting
29 WORDTAG O groups
5 WORDTAG O mines
11 WORDTAG O marks
10 WORDTAG O loan
4 WORDTAG I-PER Taylor
5 WORDTAG O prospect
16 WORDTAG I-ORG City
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
59 WORDTAG O what
8 WORDTAG O accepted
105 WORDTAG O made
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Rotterdam
9 WORDTAG O 7-3
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnia
12 WORDTAG I-PER Waugh
8 WORDTAG O postponed
74 WORDTAG O due
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Classic
154 WORDTAG O more
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Collstrop
31 WORDTAG O received
9 WORDTAG O assembly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dundee
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Plymouth
30 WORDTAG O immediately
31 WORDTAG O come
11 WORDTAG O monitors
8 WORDTAG O Soyoil
34 WORDTAG O Aug
18 WORDTAG O board
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
53 WORDTAG O net
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Akron
21 WORDTAG O profits
6 WORDTAG O Also
9 WORDTAG O population
18 WORDTAG O hope
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Reform
29 WORDTAG O trip
68 WORDTAG O champion
17 WORDTAG O battle
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Francisco
7 WORDTAG O margin
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Turkey
19 WORDTAG O member
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Serbia
7 WORDTAG O ensure
6 WORDTAG O pursuit
12 WORDTAG O spending
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Internet
9 WORDTAG B-LOC _CAP_
22 WORDTAG O turned
5 WORDTAG I-PER Zinzan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Super
6 WORDTAG O turnover
5 WORDTAG I-PER Donovan
5 WORDTAG O surgeon
30 WORDTAG O point
44 WORDTAG O closed
16 WORDTAG O medical
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Federal
5 WORDTAG O destitute
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Le
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
11 WORDTAG O includes
18 WORDTAG O murder
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
28 WORDTAG O analysts
9 WORDTAG O boxes
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem
3 WORDTAG I-ORG '
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Black
50 WORDTAG O sales
10 WORDTAG O fly
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southend
6 WORDTAG O supporting
2 WORDTAG I-MISC winners
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jakarta
136 WORDTAG O between
9 WORDTAG I-PER Woodbridge
71 WORDTAG O international
1095 WORDTAG O was
1 WORDTAG O Daily
8 WORDTAG O goalkeeper
29 WORDTAG O forecast
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Palestinian
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Betaseron
8 WORDTAG O Just
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nelson
7 WORDTAG O normal
24 WORDTAG O Net
5 WORDTAG O piece
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottingham
44 WORDTAG O higher
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
6 WORDTAG O distance
43 WORDTAG I-ORG Bank
7 WORDTAG O policies
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Jordan
38 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Middle
43 WORDTAG O began
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
71 WORDTAG O final
16 WORDTAG O states
11 WORDTAG O above
17 WORDTAG O twice
7362 WORDTAG O .
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kennedy
32 WORDTAG O possible
38 WORDTAG O recent
7 WORDTAG I-PER Brooke
22 WORDTAG O cost
5 WORDTAG O lions
8 WORDTAG O rescued
16 WORDTAG O situation
5 WORDTAG O normally
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Nancy
22 WORDTAG O dead
2 WORDTAG B-MISC County
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
3 WORDTAG O Major
11 WORDTAG O improve
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ekeus
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Kiev
14 WORDTAG O cases
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
16 WORDTAG O felt
10 WORDTAG O film
9 WORDTAG O solution
5 WORDTAG O accusing
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bratislava
8 WORDTAG O comments
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Angeles
39 WORDTAG O Police
1 WORDTAG O Old
6 WORDTAG O .504
11 WORDTAG O university
4 WORDTAG O de
9 WORDTAG O spend
12 WORDTAG I-LOC North
19 WORDTAG I-PER Aamir
8 WORDTAG O outlook
8 WORDTAG O agents
7 WORDTAG I-LOC National
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Colorado
14 WORDTAG O truce
5 WORDTAG O muscle
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican
7 WORDTAG O equipment
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Five
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Los
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Universe
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
7 WORDTAG O helicopter
11 WORDTAG O =
17 WORDTAG O your
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
5 WORDTAG O mutual
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tauziat
5 WORDTAG O holds
106 WORDTAG O did
53 WORDTAG O get
9 WORDTAG O unions
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Charleroi
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Manchester
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Chechens
8 WORDTAG O advanced
10 WORDTAG I-PER Benjamin
5 WORDTAG O dispute
1 WORDTAG B-MISC East
10 WORDTAG O crash
24 WORDTAG I-ORG Association
6 WORDTAG O surrender
106 WORDTAG O day
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bogra
4 WORDTAG O Company
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ballanger
6 WORDTAG O probe
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lebanon
7 WORDTAG O else
19 WORDTAG O teams
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
11 WORDTAG O opposed
7 WORDTAG O fled
20 WORDTAG O always
8 WORDTAG O envoy
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
7 WORDTAG O reforms
9 WORDTAG O delegates
11 WORDTAG O born
8 WORDTAG O formal
17 WORDTAG O aircraft
12 WORDTAG O daughter
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eales
501 WORDTAG O have
17 WORDTAG O gains
9 WORDTAG O mine
11 WORDTAG O improved
15 WORDTAG O serious
100 WORDTAG O where
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Dow
16 WORDTAG O community
11 WORDTAG O bodies
40 WORDTAG O current
31 WORDTAG O face
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Humenne
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Polish
72 WORDTAG O so
9 WORDTAG O suicide
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Nazi
5 WORDTAG O 38th
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesbrough
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
11 WORDTAG O below
10 WORDTAG O huge
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Merrill
10 WORDTAG O victim
330 WORDTAG O which
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Madrid
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Leverkusen
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bill
6 WORDTAG O blame
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Luxembourg
2 WORDTAG I-PER Edouard
23 WORDTAG O striker
55 WORDTAG O good
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Utrecht
5 WORDTAG O contacts
18 WORDTAG O electoral
1 WORDTAG I-MISC ,
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jones
16 WORDTAG O special
19 WORDTAG I-PER Sanchez
7 WORDTAG O threats
46 WORDTAG O fell
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Czech
6 WORDTAG O administrative
9 WORDTAG O cement
97 WORDTAG O n't
106 WORDTAG O just
6 WORDTAG O halt
25 WORDTAG I-MISC Chinese
25 WORDTAG O attacks
11 WORDTAG O warned
42 WORDTAG O quarter
6 WORDTAG O chances
13 WORDTAG O However
2789 WORDTAG O and
199 WORDTAG O told
3 WORDTAG I-LOC coast
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Nigeria
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Greece
5 WORDTAG I-PER Natalya
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Promodes
1 WORDTAG I-ORG division
6 WORDTAG O bringing
15 WORDTAG O hard
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Commonwealth
20 WORDTAG O stay
28 WORDTAG O exports
12 WORDTAG O every
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardinals
121 WORDTAG O Minister
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Estonia
1 WORDTAG I-ORG No
7 WORDTAG O items
11 WORDTAG O mln
5 WORDTAG O Not
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Zabrze
6 WORDTAG O reputation
9 WORDTAG O 1.5
7 WORDTAG O closes
7 WORDTAG O Squad
22 WORDTAG O committee
5 WORDTAG I-PER Irina
9 WORDTAG O ready
5 WORDTAG O bounce
122 WORDTAG I-LOC France
8 WORDTAG I-PER Simitis
8 WORDTAG O calling
11 WORDTAG O training
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Washington
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
13 WORDTAG O religious
31 WORDTAG O She
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Cologne
23 WORDTAG O bid
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
66 WORDTAG O says
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Mexico
7 WORDTAG O quarterly
9 WORDTAG O travelling
5 WORDTAG I-ORG General
7 WORDTAG O politics
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bremen
10 WORDTAG O hotel
7 WORDTAG O controls
12 WORDTAG O 6-5
75 WORDTAG O 6-1
3 WORDTAG B-MISC Grand
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
11 WORDTAG O real
5 WORDTAG O thrown
11 WORDTAG O subject
6 WORDTAG O space
6 WORDTAG I-PER Berger
6 WORDTAG O hostages
13 WORDTAG O foot
2 WORDTAG I-PER Price
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Roda
10 WORDTAG O cause
4 WORDTAG I-PER Edwards
6 WORDTAG O compensation
9 WORDTAG I-PER Agassi
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Finance
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nepali
9 WORDTAG O successful
7 WORDTAG O 1996-08-21
6 WORDTAG O Shr
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Elect
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costa
7 WORDTAG O attended
57 WORDTAG O race
9 WORDTAG I-PER Olsza
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pollock
11 WORDTAG O assets
32 WORDTAG O reports
31 WORDTAG O brought
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Oakland
5 WORDTAG O establish
7 WORDTAG O judicial
6 WORDTAG O m
5 WORDTAG O anniversary
6 WORDTAG O relatively
1 WORDTAG I-PER Houston
23 WORDTAG I-MISC Sudanese
7 WORDTAG O .531
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Community
19 WORDTAG I-PER Meri
6 WORDTAG O option
6 WORDTAG O wo
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Hyundai
34 WORDTAG O tennis
2613 WORDTAG I-ORG _RARE_
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Miami
5 WORDTAG O palace
8 WORDTAG O elect
106 WORDTAG O games
8 WORDTAG O monthly
6 WORDTAG I-PER Shimon
8 WORDTAG O Six
143 WORDTAG O market
207 WORDTAG O It
5 WORDTAG O eventually
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rifkind
8 WORDTAG O 15-8
52 WORDTAG O going
21 WORDTAG O dealers
10 WORDTAG O crude
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
9 WORDTAG O ballot
471 WORDTAG O after
17 WORDTAG O separatist
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
10 WORDTAG O begun
14 WORDTAG O ending
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanwha
14 WORDTAG O export
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Stadler
19 WORDTAG I-PER R.
1243 WORDTAG O -
9 WORDTAG O rises
5 WORDTAG O sweeping
17 WORDTAG O telephone
6 WORDTAG O directed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Air
525 WORDTAG O be
33 WORDTAG I-ORG York
10 WORDTAG O heroin
8 WORDTAG O lives
7 WORDTAG O active
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Air
17 WORDTAG O port
17 WORDTAG O deals
10 WORDTAG O confidence
33 WORDTAG O April
11 WORDTAG O suspect
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Football
14 WORDTAG O surgery
7 WORDTAG O lifting
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alesi
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Orioles
10 WORDTAG O add
8 WORDTAG O edged
8 WORDTAG O removed
7 WORDTAG I-PER Alberto
6 WORDTAG O birds
18 WORDTAG O child
6 WORDTAG O themselves
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Baghdad
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Diego
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tennis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Houston
7 WORDTAG O lbw
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Iran
5 WORDTAG O nurses
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Lakes
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
1 WORDTAG I-MISC convention
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Investors
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb
5 WORDTAG O genocide
1 WORDTAG I-ORG French
50 WORDTAG O economic
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Emnid
14 WORDTAG O pulled
52 WORDTAG O agency
10 WORDTAG O appointed
53 WORDTAG O late
21 WORDTAG I-PER Mother
11 WORDTAG O heard
10 WORDTAG O documents
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Zenith
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ferguson
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Doboj
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistani
9 WORDTAG O mainly
7 WORDTAG O waste
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Athens
13 WORDTAG O 2-2
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
9 WORDTAG O insurance
8 WORDTAG O names
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Sri
70 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsroom
124 WORDTAG O officials
1 WORDTAG I-ORG alliance
13 WORDTAG O trader
5 WORDTAG O profit-taking
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gianluca
5 WORDTAG O directly
24 WORDTAG O source
14 WORDTAG O done
6 WORDTAG O repeat
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johnny
335 WORDTAG O beat
16 WORDTAG I-PER Chang
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Van
6 WORDTAG O .543
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Business
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Scotland
6 WORDTAG O 15.
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
1 WORDTAG I-MISC division
7 WORDTAG O catch
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Senate
8 WORDTAG O establishment
14 WORDTAG I-PER Boris
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Lewis
110 WORDTAG O next
17 WORDTAG O par
1386 WORDTAG I-LOC _CAP_
5 WORDTAG I-LOC St.
14 WORDTAG O starting
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hill
5 WORDTAG O civilian
24 WORDTAG O big
5 WORDTAG O acts
7 WORDTAG O democratic
6 WORDTAG O except
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
8 WORDTAG O happened
10 WORDTAG O waiting
21 WORDTAG O seized
18 WORDTAG I-PER Rubin
9 WORDTAG O missionaries
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Albanian
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Coast
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlantic
14 WORDTAG I-PER Graham
27 WORDTAG O rule
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bucharest
117 WORDTAG O four
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
6 WORDTAG O credit
5 WORDTAG O Fastest
15 WORDTAG O hour
4 WORDTAG I-MISC on
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tirana
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Ethiopia
38 WORDTAG O total
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Wroclaw
8 WORDTAG O volatility
7 WORDTAG O red
6 WORDTAG O 30th
47 WORDTAG O central
9 WORDTAG O council
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Health
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Battle
7 WORDTAG O claims
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
7 WORDTAG O knee
26 WORDTAG O One
12 WORDTAG O Sales
25 WORDTAG O course
23 WORDTAG I-PER Alexander
35 WORDTAG O cut
7 WORDTAG O bullish
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rocca
57 WORDTAG O goals
5 WORDTAG O heavily
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Council
1 WORDTAG I-MISC London
15 WORDTAG I-ORG /
5 WORDTAG O independent
6 WORDTAG O experience
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesian
20 WORDTAG I-LOC The
36 WORDTAG O fourth
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Export
5 WORDTAG O sentences
50 WORDTAG O taking
9 WORDTAG I-PER Costas
11 WORDTAG O county
7 WORDTAG O linking
7 WORDTAG O agenda
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Black
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Linz
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jean
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Court
21 WORDTAG O guilders
13 WORDTAG O ?
45 WORDTAG I-ORG Commission
12 WORDTAG O weekly
6 WORDTAG O trends
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ross
36 WORDTAG O help
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Pakistani
7 WORDTAG O instead
7 WORDTAG O explosives
5 WORDTAG I-PER Vacek
1 WORDTAG I-ORG German
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hong
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Congress
17 WORDTAG O goods
8 WORDTAG O presidency
24 WORDTAG O leg
1 WORDTAG I-PER Roman
10 WORDTAG O cars
9 WORDTAG O representatives
14 WORDTAG O streak
12 WORDTAG O freed
8 WORDTAG O Rating
78 WORDTAG I-MISC British
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayer
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Sheffield
16 WORDTAG O Bowling
43 WORDTAG O decision
5 WORDTAG O seasons
7 WORDTAG O disappointed
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Army
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Golf
1 WORDTAG I-LOC north
7 WORDTAG O stadium
31 WORDTAG I-LOC Kenya
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Motorola
7 WORDTAG O flow
13 WORDTAG O sanctions
45 WORDTAG O weeks
6 WORDTAG I-PER Bruguera
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vermont
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Ferrari
5 WORDTAG O profitable
5 WORDTAG O congress
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqi
9 WORDTAG O registered
16 WORDTAG O whole
7 WORDTAG O everything
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Public
8 WORDTAG O runner-up
9 WORDTAG O registrations
24 WORDTAG O great
6 WORDTAG O Latest
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
15 WORDTAG I-PER Gore
2 WORDTAG O West
6 WORDTAG O colony
74 WORDTAG O 7-6
5 WORDTAG O coup
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Rally
6 WORDTAG O 33rd
132 WORDTAG O other
10 WORDTAG O kg
12 WORDTAG O abandoned
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Abu
16 WORDTAG I-PER Juan
7 WORDTAG O speed
5 WORDTAG O batsman
186 WORDTAG O or
22 WORDTAG O volume
6 WORDTAG O atmosphere
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bernard
10 WORDTAG O kill
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
70 WORDTAG O victory
5 WORDTAG I-PER Montgomerie
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wall
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Strasbourg
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Algeria
7 WORDTAG O store
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Groningen
21 WORDTAG O really
6 WORDTAG O bronze
8 WORDTAG O activities
5 WORDTAG O span
15 WORDTAG O often
6 WORDTAG O factor
7 WORDTAG O World
31 WORDTAG O used
8 WORDTAG O Now
8 WORDTAG O fob
1 WORDTAG I-MISC States
6 WORDTAG I-MISC S.
34 WORDTAG I-ORG 's
284 WORDTAG O this
11 WORDTAG O towns
7 WORDTAG O flying
6 WORDTAG O reliever
19 WORDTAG O arms
7 WORDTAG O Ambassador
2 WORDTAG I-MISC People
29 WORDTAG O 0-0
64 WORDTAG O 5.
7 WORDTAG I-PER Habsudova
11 WORDTAG O spoke
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
19 WORDTAG O caught
7 WORDTAG O actions
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Biogen
10 WORDTAG O ends
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Florida
27 WORDTAG O times
114 WORDTAG O because
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Yellow
20 WORDTAG I-ORG International
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
99 WORDTAG O July
20 WORDTAG O double
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Los
21 WORDTAG O settlement
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ieng
9 WORDTAG O Cash
11 WORDTAG O posted
74 WORDTAG O saying
17 WORDTAG O attempt
7 WORDTAG O sea
6 WORDTAG O supporters
22 WORDTAG O defeat
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Taibe
59 WORDTAG O ago
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
17 WORDTAG O leaving
8 WORDTAG I-MISC New
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stevanin
5 WORDTAG I-PER Elena
35 WORDTAG O manager
105 WORDTAG O win
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Pirates
35 WORDTAG O disease
29 WORDTAG O latest
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Singapore
11 WORDTAG O living
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Catholic
8 WORDTAG O offers
224 WORDTAG O police
19 WORDTAG I-PER Brady
6 WORDTAG O specified
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
5 WORDTAG O .469
5 WORDTAG I-PER Azharuddin
19 WORDTAG O legal
5 WORDTAG O clause
24 WORDTAG O economy
214 WORDTAG O also
22 WORDTAG O tax
24 WORDTAG O Result
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Moldova
41 WORDTAG O leading
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
33 WORDTAG O strong
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Maria
5 WORDTAG O marijuana
9 WORDTAG O opponents
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Java
7 WORDTAG O solo
74 WORDTAG O end
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloria
6 WORDTAG O sharply
38 WORDTAG I-LOC York
75 WORDTAG O capital
689 WORDTAG O is
11 WORDTAG O consecutive
125 WORDTAG O 1996-08-22
3 WORDTAG I-PER Leon
9 WORDTAG I-PER Haga
7 WORDTAG O specific
8 WORDTAG I-PER Masterkova
7 WORDTAG I-ORG S&P
8 WORDTAG I-MISC US$
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Coast
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
19 WORDTAG O girl
46 WORDTAG O 1-0
6 WORDTAG O reopened
5 WORDTAG O outcome
7 WORDTAG O ------------------------
13 WORDTAG I-PER Banharn
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kohl
7 WORDTAG O pull
7 WORDTAG O pain
12 WORDTAG O diplomats
2 WORDTAG I-MISC One
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
7 WORDTAG O secured
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Briton
7 WORDTAG O decisions
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Organisation
3 WORDTAG O Key
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Dublin
5 WORDTAG O tense
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Vale
6 WORDTAG O self-rule
3 WORDTAG O Spring
50 WORDTAG O arrested
2 WORDTAG I-PER Law
4 WORDTAG O Gold
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Monaco
1 WORDTAG O Index
9 WORDTAG O individual
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Sofia
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Helibor
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Uganda
60 WORDTAG O meet
117 WORDTAG O six
9 WORDTAG O junior
11 WORDTAG O riots
23 WORDTAG O 7-4
15 WORDTAG O To
23 WORDTAG O poll
6 WORDTAG O united
53 WORDTAG O northern
5 WORDTAG O lows
54 WORDTAG O May
5 WORDTAG O platform
11 WORDTAG O worked
83 WORDTAG O earlier
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Newcastle
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lotte
12 WORDTAG O computer
1 WORDTAG O Golf
11 WORDTAG I-ORG House
21 WORDTAG I-PER Todd
7 WORDTAG O allocated
15 WORDTAG I-PER Morris
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Young
7 WORDTAG O criminal
14 WORDTAG O Jul
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Europe
36 WORDTAG O failed
6 WORDTAG O extended
9 WORDTAG O kills
7221 WORDTAG O the
6 WORDTAG O satisfied
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
98 WORDTAG O if
5 WORDTAG O developments
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Iranian
5 WORDTAG O 10.5
25 WORDTAG O letter
10 WORDTAG O suit
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dan
19 WORDTAG O francs
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Sydney
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Law
7 WORDTAG O Baseball
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Juan
7 WORDTAG O settled
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nobel
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Affairs
5 WORDTAG O gestures
7 WORDTAG O prosecutor
57 WORDTAG O bank
4 WORDTAG I-ORG In
5 WORDTAG O reimbursement
15 WORDTAG O Last
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Edwards
6 WORDTAG I-PER Batistuta
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshoppers
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Institute
5 WORDTAG O ]
11 WORDTAG O lack
41 WORDTAG O fighting
16 WORDTAG I-PER William
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Barcelona
20 WORDTAG O February
8 WORDTAG O major-league
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottinghamshire
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
71 WORDTAG O you
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bamerindus
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gloria
57 WORDTAG I-LOC States
25 WORDTAG O sell
7 WORDTAG O bread
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Delhi
8 WORDTAG O rand
24 WORDTAG O returned
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
5 WORDTAG O fix
5 WORDTAG I-PER Yihye
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberia
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Miss
10 WORDTAG I-PER Machado
8 WORDTAG O extremely
5 WORDTAG O printed
5 WORDTAG O 3/4
1 WORDTAG I-LOC _DIGIT_
6 WORDTAG O engineering
14 WORDTAG O bill
157 WORDTAG O some
50 WORDTAG I-PER John
