5 WORDTAG O 83rd
6 WORDTAG O mind
4 WORDTAG O reading
1 WORDTAG O topic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Solano
7 WORDTAG O 47th
1 WORDTAG O 230-1
2 WORDTAG O trouble-free
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hina
1 WORDTAG O 45.810
3 WORDTAG O agricultural
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Carnival
1 WORDTAG O haunted
2 WORDTAG I-PER Amy
33 WORDTAG O declared
1 WORDTAG O intangible
2 WORDTAG I-PER O.J.
10 WORDTAG I-PER Armstrong
95 WORDTAG O 3.
1 WORDTAG O +46-8-700
1 WORDTAG O 3.67
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chongqing
1 WORDTAG O one-third
1 WORDTAG O 50.51
1 WORDTAG I-PER Londono
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
1 WORDTAG O participant
2 WORDTAG I-PER Stranksy
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Sumitomo
4 WORDTAG O conflicts
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pessina
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
4 WORDTAG O expansion
16 WORDTAG O event
1 WORDTAG O continually
4 WORDTAG I-MISC County
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toomas
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Monterey
4 WORDTAG O ranks
2 WORDTAG O transactions
1 WORDTAG O bore
3 WORDTAG I-PER Herve
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Spal
1 WORDTAG O unknowingly
1 WORDTAG O proponents
1 WORDTAG O extinguished
7 WORDTAG I-PER Teutenberg
1 WORDTAG O dilemma
2 WORDTAG O 6.96
6 WORDTAG O briefing
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Gurion
2 WORDTAG O .532
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kudapokuna
1 WORDTAG O photographing
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Veliko
2 WORDTAG O four-game
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dopita
1 WORDTAG O 9.85
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
1 WORDTAG O helper
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wataru
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sultan
2 WORDTAG O cords
9 WORDTAG O maybe
1 WORDTAG O porous
30 WORDTAG O estimated
1 WORDTAG O unloaded
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lovell
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
1 WORDTAG O Joining
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fournier
1 WORDTAG O ethical
10 WORDTAG O necessary
5 WORDTAG O compromise
1 WORDTAG O description
6 WORDTAG O 70th
1 WORDTAG I-PER Talen
9 WORDTAG O aid
1 WORDTAG I-MISC for
1 WORDTAG I-PER Riel
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carretero
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gilford
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rights
2 WORDTAG O gunpoint
2 WORDTAG O contrary
1 WORDTAG O granting
4 WORDTAG O favorable
1 WORDTAG I-PER Meluawati
1 WORDTAG O Depending
1 WORDTAG O ward
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Indah
1 WORDTAG O Sixteen
23 WORDTAG O firm
18 WORDTAG O secretary
55 WORDTAG O city
1 WORDTAG O hamburger
6 WORDTAG O mate
2 WORDTAG I-PER Domingo
4 WORDTAG O assemblies
1 WORDTAG I-PER Omloop
2 WORDTAG I-PER Watkinson
1 WORDTAG I-PER Alloush
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nasr
1 WORDTAG O 12.225
1 WORDTAG O 1:00.754
1 WORDTAG O communicate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sali
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Videoton(*
1 WORDTAG O megawatts
1 WORDTAG O four-year-old
1 WORDTAG I-PER Glafcos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ronny
1 WORDTAG I-PER Belinda
1 WORDTAG O blurted
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Lenzing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Steptoe
2 WORDTAG O abilities
4 WORDTAG O married
12 WORDTAG O immediate
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sound
1 WORDTAG O Packaging
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Medellin
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
1 WORDTAG O mutilating
1 WORDTAG O paramilitary
12 WORDTAG O cow
1 WORDTAG O crops
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Halo
5 WORDTAG O selected
1 WORDTAG I-PER Akpoborie
1 WORDTAG I-PER Watkin
1 WORDTAG I-MISC law
3 WORDTAG I-PER Glickman
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siegfried
4 WORDTAG O participants
1 WORDTAG O 7.03
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bakker
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Corporacion
2 WORDTAG I-PER Montolio
4 WORDTAG O abducted
3 WORDTAG O .537
6 WORDTAG O events
1 WORDTAG O symbols
1 WORDTAG O 111.2
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Procurement
1 WORDTAG O 4:24.427
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Five
1 WORDTAG O 138.0-149.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arrigo
1 WORDTAG I-PER West
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lima
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zalevskaya
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lecce
9 WORDTAG O According
1 WORDTAG O nonstop
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dunedin
1 WORDTAG O +3,831
1 WORDTAG O 14-pct
1 WORDTAG I-PER Beser
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barjuan
1 WORDTAG O April-July
1 WORDTAG O Scandal
2 WORDTAG I-PER McGinley
1 WORDTAG O 4:15.006
19 WORDTAG O sides
1 WORDTAG O curtain-raiser
1 WORDTAG O trawlers
7 WORDTAG O prix
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
5 WORDTAG O voter
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Neuchatel
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
9 WORDTAG O reduce
1 WORDTAG O End
1 WORDTAG O encampment
1 WORDTAG O looted
2 WORDTAG O dyed
1 WORDTAG O informant
1 WORDTAG I-PER Raul
6 WORDTAG O develop
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lanus
2 WORDTAG O spleens
1 WORDTAG O putdowns
1 WORDTAG O 125M
2 WORDTAG O withering
9 WORDTAG O reduced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Levitt
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Soviet-era
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Verona
1 WORDTAG O eurokiwi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Khalid
10 WORDTAG O Government
4 WORDTAG O 2.20
1 WORDTAG O definite
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Western
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Venezuela
12 WORDTAG O soldier
1 WORDTAG I-PER DiSarcina
1 WORDTAG O 4-45
1 WORDTAG O timeframe
1 WORDTAG O blackmailed
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Taibe
1 WORDTAG O incomers
1 WORDTAG O warns
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lions
2 WORDTAG O 107.55
1 WORDTAG O economics
1 WORDTAG O spun
3 WORDTAG O aim
4 WORDTAG O producer
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bistrita
2 WORDTAG O 2:28.98
3 WORDTAG O indicating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Veglio
4 WORDTAG O unlikely
1 WORDTAG O 46.21
2 WORDTAG I-PER (
1 WORDTAG O park
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thiry
2 WORDTAG O hectare
1 WORDTAG O integration
3 WORDTAG O Q1
2 WORDTAG O dignity
8 WORDTAG O eating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Caesar
7 WORDTAG O shots
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
84 WORDTAG O half
10 WORDTAG O clocked
1 WORDTAG O 70M
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rusedski
3 WORDTAG O economists
9 WORDTAG O commanding
7 WORDTAG O chief-of-staff
36 WORDTAG O wickets
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rory
1 WORDTAG O 90-minute
2 WORDTAG O 35-year-old
1 WORDTAG O swore
1 WORDTAG O guess
20 WORDTAG O involved
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Mission
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zejjari
1 WORDTAG O photo-finish
1 WORDTAG O 521.15
2 WORDTAG I-PER Osmond
13 WORDTAG O cuts
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
1 WORDTAG O schemers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gianfranco
2 WORDTAG O dictatorial
1 WORDTAG O Jan-July
127 WORDTAG I-PER _CAP_
1 WORDTAG O sail
1 WORDTAG O renounced
1 WORDTAG O complain
1 WORDTAG O d'emploi
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wyludda
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marsh
9 WORDTAG O jet
1 WORDTAG O shameful
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Butch
4 WORDTAG O trades
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Dynasty
1 WORDTAG O 5.602
1 WORDTAG O Soon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Paulinho
1 WORDTAG O Continent
1 WORDTAG O denouncing
1 WORDTAG O bicycle
12 WORDTAG O winners
1 WORDTAG O commited
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Rep
1 WORDTAG O kilo
1 WORDTAG O censors
1 WORDTAG I-PER Koprinovic
2 WORDTAG I-MISC North
6 WORDTAG O maker
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Division
1 WORDTAG O 27.25
3 WORDTAG O strict
3 WORDTAG O watch
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Diyarbakir
35 WORDTAG O started
1 WORDTAG O infant
20 WORDTAG O question
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Gorgona
1 WORDTAG I-PER Orel
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Sofia
3 WORDTAG O cleric
1 WORDTAG O 7-283
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Limerick
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Azul
5 WORDTAG I-PER Preston
1 WORDTAG O hardened
1 WORDTAG O admitting
8 WORDTAG O seedings
1 WORDTAG O gradually
1 WORDTAG O 312-983-7347--
3 WORDTAG O arson
1 WORDTAG O 6.2
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mexican
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jiaxuan
22 WORDTAG O problems
49 WORDTAG O those
1 WORDTAG O Interviewed
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Tirol
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ukyo
13 WORDTAG I-LOC House
1 WORDTAG O undone
1 WORDTAG I-PER Art
4 WORDTAG O lobby
15 WORDTAG O others
4 WORDTAG O warehouses
1 WORDTAG O 3/8
2 WORDTAG I-PER Coers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brunmayr
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Porsche
1 WORDTAG O acquitted
1 WORDTAG O formerly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Charmaine
1 WORDTAG O forbid
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hambrecht
12 WORDTAG O stronger
84 WORDTAG O still
1 WORDTAG O draconian
3 WORDTAG O vicious
1 WORDTAG I-PER Angelo
3 WORDTAG I-PER den
20 WORDTAG O summer
3 WORDTAG O debris
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
2 WORDTAG O 21.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Alert
1 WORDTAG O 97.42
1 WORDTAG O 18.5
2 WORDTAG O 1-10-100
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wilkins
716 WORDTAG O by
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
1 WORDTAG I-PER Grieg
29 WORDTAG O figures
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
3 WORDTAG O stretch
2 WORDTAG O harassed
2 WORDTAG O round-trip
6 WORDTAG O radical
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mir
1 WORDTAG O tone
1 WORDTAG O Ranked
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mather
2 WORDTAG O Thieves
1 WORDTAG O 42.45
1 WORDTAG O upland
1 WORDTAG O Gaseous
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kryvy
2 WORDTAG O patient
2 WORDTAG O deported
1 WORDTAG O react
1 WORDTAG O WHEAT--Rains
1 WORDTAG O 100M
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
2 WORDTAG I-PER Aliuska
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arlen
3 WORDTAG O reportedly
1 WORDTAG O constructing
1 WORDTAG O predicting
2 WORDTAG O spongiform
1 WORDTAG O off-side
1 WORDTAG O 32.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Giga
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferris
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mujahideen
3 WORDTAG O full-year
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eddo
1 WORDTAG O Jobless
1 WORDTAG O quieter
10 WORDTAG O alliance
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
1 WORDTAG O climatologist
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hall
14 WORDTAG O large
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Marines
1 WORDTAG O 5-6
3 WORDTAG I-PER Glenn
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Civil
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Crvena
9 WORDTAG O balance
1 WORDTAG I-MISC MS-NBC
1 WORDTAG I-MISC du
3 WORDTAG O pre-season
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ohrel
3 WORDTAG I-PER Weiss
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Watts
12 WORDTAG O managed
1 WORDTAG O guides
1 WORDTAG O 61.00
1 WORDTAG O consideration
1 WORDTAG O 1:45.24
1 WORDTAG O 2-yr
4 WORDTAG O Series
1 WORDTAG O blockbusters
1 WORDTAG O insistent
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Royals
2 WORDTAG O journalism
1 WORDTAG O beneficial
3 WORDTAG O birdie
8 WORDTAG O decree
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnian-Croat
1 WORDTAG O vied
1 WORDTAG O divine
2 WORDTAG O 98.9
4 WORDTAG I-PER Kan
1 WORDTAG O 8.25
2 WORDTAG I-PER Frost
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hans-Otto
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Valuable
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Lahore
1 WORDTAG I-PER Griffiths
2 WORDTAG O decrees
10 WORDTAG O owns
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
1 WORDTAG O nascent
1 WORDTAG O packet
2 WORDTAG O freight-tonne
2 WORDTAG O Majesty
4 WORDTAG O stick
15 WORDTAG O provide
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aryeh
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ro
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Stoke
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mid-East
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhahran
24 WORDTAG O bond
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Criciuma
2 WORDTAG O replying
1 WORDTAG O highest-ranked
1 WORDTAG O Hopes
1 WORDTAG O coupons
2 WORDTAG O chicken
5 WORDTAG O soybeans
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
3 WORDTAG O submit
1 WORDTAG O 5-240
4 WORDTAG I-PER Giovanni
1 WORDTAG O directorate-grade
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Government
1 WORDTAG O instrument
1 WORDTAG O 7:36.81
1 WORDTAG O 406.6
1 WORDTAG O torture
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greenville
2 WORDTAG O dependent
1 WORDTAG O pursued
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Soccer
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Planning
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Markets
1 WORDTAG O liberated
4 WORDTAG O 33-26
2 WORDTAG I-PER Battersby
1 WORDTAG I-MISC BALANCE-Water
1 WORDTAG O recommend
1 WORDTAG I-PER Srutwa
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperation
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rickey
27 WORDTAG O confirmed
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Illinois
1 WORDTAG O adulthood
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
1 WORDTAG O out-of-court
1 WORDTAG O 125-member
7 WORDTAG O hot
5 WORDTAG O Many
1 WORDTAG I-PER Josef
2 WORDTAG O volunteers
2 WORDTAG O Bodies
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dusan
1 WORDTAG O dlrs
9 WORDTAG O visiting
1 WORDTAG O equally
1 WORDTAG O 837/763
2 WORDTAG I-PER Chaminda
1 WORDTAG O 85.26
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
2 WORDTAG O lasagna
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Colombia
16 WORDTAG O walked
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
1 WORDTAG O newroom
1 WORDTAG O headless
4 WORDTAG O crucial
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gevirtz
1 WORDTAG O portrait
2 WORDTAG O younger
3 WORDTAG O turns
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kneipp
1 WORDTAG O managerless
1 WORDTAG O mantra
3 WORDTAG O tbf
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
2 WORDTAG O rallying
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Becej
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
1 WORDTAG O deflating
1 WORDTAG O reprisal
1 WORDTAG O enlistment
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
7 WORDTAG O regarding
1 WORDTAG O 12.2
3 WORDTAG O compete
31 WORDTAG O death
9 WORDTAG O driving
2 WORDTAG O cleaning
2 WORDTAG O boycotting
2 WORDTAG I-PER Chan
2 WORDTAG O furnace
8 WORDTAG O tension
53 WORDTAG O near
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wath
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Riviera
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
1 WORDTAG O pacts
1 WORDTAG O rectify
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
3 WORDTAG I-PER Dahman
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hicham
4 WORDTAG O 16th
2 WORDTAG O warm-up
2 WORDTAG O yourself
1 WORDTAG I-PER Malgorzata
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
5 WORDTAG O experts
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
2 WORDTAG O obstructing
53 WORDTAG O security
1 WORDTAG O inadequacy
1 WORDTAG O tackle
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Former
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
5 WORDTAG O container
2 WORDTAG O ideal
1 WORDTAG O -----
1 WORDTAG O 12.70
1 WORDTAG I-PER Virna
1 WORDTAG O incorrectly
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gaudenzi
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Munich
27 WORDTAG O violence
2 WORDTAG O combatants
3 WORDTAG O rebellion
3 WORDTAG O Cricket
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Sidor
1 WORDTAG I-PER Margit
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nature
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pork
1 WORDTAG O wrecking
2 WORDTAG O 11.04
1 WORDTAG O south-west
1 WORDTAG O forfeiting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC President
1 WORDTAG O .589
1 WORDTAG O enemy
1 WORDTAG O Central
2 WORDTAG O summit
2 WORDTAG O 30.AUG.96
29 WORDTAG O trip
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Prievidza
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Iscor
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Observatory
1 WORDTAG O .565
1 WORDTAG I-PER Valentine
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG O 23.53
31 WORDTAG O coach
1 WORDTAG O nc=acomparison
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
1 WORDTAG O councils
1 WORDTAG O dodging
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ferdinand
1 WORDTAG O cabaret
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chatichai
1 WORDTAG O 728-9559
1 WORDTAG O repatriate
8 WORDTAG O blow
1 WORDTAG I-PER Johnstone
3 WORDTAG O purchases
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northampton
9 WORDTAG O scientific
3 WORDTAG O voiced
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brumm
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
1 WORDTAG I-MISC FTSE-100
1 WORDTAG I-ORG wall
2 WORDTAG O unexpected
1 WORDTAG O dislodge
2 WORDTAG O 147.159
1 WORDTAG O annually
1 WORDTAG I-PER Islam
1 WORDTAG O 11.45
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sierra
2 WORDTAG O unbeatable
1 WORDTAG O distributes
4 WORDTAG O secrets
12 WORDTAG O Sales
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
12 WORDTAG O history
1 WORDTAG O soothed
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Mapourdit
2 WORDTAG O tiebreaker
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Birmingham
1 WORDTAG I-PER Emese
1 WORDTAG O wiped
1 WORDTAG O t-shirt
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
1 WORDTAG O 146.2
2 WORDTAG O boatman
2 WORDTAG O licensed
3 WORDTAG O releases
1 WORDTAG O mode
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Osaka
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Nebraska
2 WORDTAG I-PER Markus
1 WORDTAG O +7.3;-3.6
6 WORDTAG O speaking
1 WORDTAG O unnerved
2 WORDTAG O relive
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Keirin
4 WORDTAG O testimony
2 WORDTAG I-PER Devon
2 WORDTAG O colon
1 WORDTAG I-MISC program
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Shatoi
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mostostal
3 WORDTAG O 1.09
17 WORDTAG O thought
13 WORDTAG O crime
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ruud
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
1 WORDTAG O dream
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kappes
4 WORDTAG O 42nd
9 WORDTAG O Did
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Whittier
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BellSouth
5 WORDTAG O sending
1 WORDTAG O acknowledge
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bavarian
1 WORDTAG O corrections
1 WORDTAG I-PER P.V.
3 WORDTAG O lawsuits
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Salzburg
1 WORDTAG O firebreathing
1 WORDTAG O passers-by
3 WORDTAG O Delivery
1 WORDTAG O 385-1-4557075
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nobel
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul-Salang
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bunol
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kouame
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Prisoners
2 WORDTAG O outscored
2 WORDTAG O 3,894.00
1 WORDTAG O merge
25 WORDTAG O civil
1 WORDTAG I-PER Moses
18 WORDTAG O rival
1 WORDTAG O rain-curtailed
3 WORDTAG O 5.60
1 WORDTAG O forecasters
6 WORDTAG O majors
1 WORDTAG O handsome
1 WORDTAG O chasing
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
1 WORDTAG O flatly
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
15 WORDTAG O published
2 WORDTAG O 14,390.7
1 WORDTAG O 112.56
1 WORDTAG O oilfield
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Yorkers
3 WORDTAG O hardline
1 WORDTAG I-PER Inger
1 WORDTAG I-PER Stephenson
2 WORDTAG O evasion
1 WORDTAG O 21-11
1 WORDTAG O 311.9
1 WORDTAG O decentralisation
1 WORDTAG O four-month
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rupert
1 WORDTAG O Things
1 WORDTAG O 3.13
4 WORDTAG O waters
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chesterfield
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Glenview
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Carlo
5 WORDTAG O medicine
8 WORDTAG O rescued
1 WORDTAG O Surprise
1 WORDTAG O Looming
1 WORDTAG O 10-5
3 WORDTAG O umpires
1 WORDTAG O unjustified
2 WORDTAG O 12-1-41-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kurdistan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Naish
17 WORDTAG O track
5 WORDTAG I-ORG People
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
1 WORDTAG O daughters
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Channel
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hermawan
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Moller
17 WORDTAG O losing
6 WORDTAG O scientists
1 WORDTAG O third-longest
1 WORDTAG O cart
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kilda
4 WORDTAG I-PER Yevgeny
1 WORDTAG O passers
8 WORDTAG O finance
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
1 WORDTAG O 25.50
2 WORDTAG O bacillus
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Straits
2 WORDTAG O comprehensive
1 WORDTAG O differential
4 WORDTAG O feeling
4 WORDTAG O pool
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Lancer
3 WORDTAG O spotted
1 WORDTAG I-PER Drechsler
1 WORDTAG O idiots
1 WORDTAG O 4950.000
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunfermline
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
1 WORDTAG O manipulation
9 WORDTAG O travelling
1 WORDTAG O golds
2 WORDTAG O commissioner
2 WORDTAG O teak
1 WORDTAG O scouts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wicky
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Charleroi
1 WORDTAG O sacks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tolkacheva
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Reggiana
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Leon
3 WORDTAG O withdraw
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Block
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ibrahimi
1 WORDTAG O rents
1 WORDTAG O rotate
5 WORDTAG O acts
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
18 WORDTAG O defender
4 WORDTAG O singer
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ruano-Pascual
6 WORDTAG O gain
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tan
1 WORDTAG O violently
5 WORDTAG O legs
2 WORDTAG O skills
3 WORDTAG O spy
3 WORDTAG O clothes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Matusevitch
3 WORDTAG O existed
2 WORDTAG O newsprint
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sociological
1 WORDTAG O Piano
32 WORDTAG O further
1 WORDTAG O singing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Traore
1 WORDTAG O risked
15 WORDTAG O sex
6 WORDTAG O controversial
1 WORDTAG O accounts
7 WORDTAG O commercial
21 WORDTAG O food
3 WORDTAG O handover
1 WORDTAG O 40-34
35 WORDTAG O manager
4 WORDTAG O 5.50
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
1 WORDTAG I-MISC SBF-120
1 WORDTAG O savaged
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Code
1 WORDTAG O 28.0
1 WORDTAG O 27.495
2 WORDTAG O 35.0
1 WORDTAG O 13.37
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ilke
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lisabeth
3 WORDTAG O 941-8100
3 WORDTAG I-PER Coughlan
1 WORDTAG O prey
46 WORDTAG O ahead
1 WORDTAG O downside
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Love
1 WORDTAG O narrowed
5 WORDTAG O assistant
4 WORDTAG I-PER Mokhoff
2 WORDTAG O lineup
1 WORDTAG O 817.60
1 WORDTAG O heir-to-the-throne
1 WORDTAG O sticking
3 WORDTAG O metals
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gray
1 WORDTAG O defense
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lattakia
1 WORDTAG O 64ths-inch
1 WORDTAG O Offered
2 WORDTAG I-PER Flavin
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shehu
2 WORDTAG O 3-1/2
1 WORDTAG O rubella
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Abbaye
27 WORDTAG O pound
2 WORDTAG O founder
1 WORDTAG O 1,750-hectare
14 WORDTAG O filed
1 WORDTAG O 19.92
1 WORDTAG O 27,535.5
26 WORDTAG O south
1 WORDTAG O Sep.96
1 WORDTAG O irregularly
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Conference
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Casablanca
1 WORDTAG I-PER Seedorf
7 WORDTAG O owner
3 WORDTAG O karbovanets
1 WORDTAG O Adventurers
5 WORDTAG O businessman
1 WORDTAG O 12.83
30 WORDTAG O private
2 WORDTAG O disarmed
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kinkel
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dead
2 WORDTAG O Supreme
1 WORDTAG O mixers
4 WORDTAG I-PER Chiate
4 WORDTAG O unlisted
1 WORDTAG O 2,500-seat
1 WORDTAG O ground-floor
1 WORDTAG O IAE-3
5 WORDTAG O supported
1 WORDTAG O depot
1 WORDTAG O Collated
1 WORDTAG O www.internetstartup.com
1 WORDTAG O all-share
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hwa
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ingwe
1 WORDTAG O includind
2 WORDTAG O Silver
1 WORDTAG O declining
1 WORDTAG O hunted
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Representatives
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Victoria
1 WORDTAG O 02/09
45 WORDTAG O hours
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lausgberg
4 WORDTAG O trio
2 WORDTAG O filming
1 WORDTAG O 2320.00
1 WORDTAG O mocked
1 WORDTAG O 22.94
1 WORDTAG O Consulate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kojima
2 WORDTAG I-MISC System
2 WORDTAG O protected
1 WORDTAG O thief
4 WORDTAG O unpaid
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Springfield
3 WORDTAG O requested
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Newark
2 WORDTAG O importing
1 WORDTAG O +3,428
1 WORDTAG O Playoff
5 WORDTAG O crowds
1 WORDTAG O Building
1 WORDTAG I-PER Keter
5 WORDTAG O Fax
1 WORDTAG O cemented
1 WORDTAG I-PER Grimwade
11 WORDTAG O promised
1 WORDTAG I-PER Romina
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Swiss
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wash
3 WORDTAG O works
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
1 WORDTAG I-PER Peeters
1 WORDTAG I-MISC INTERVIEW-T&N
1 WORDTAG O infamous
2 WORDTAG O jointly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Klimis
3 WORDTAG I-PER Love
1 WORDTAG O blood-red
1 WORDTAG O immunizes
8 WORDTAG O network
1 WORDTAG O paralyzed
40 WORDTAG O such
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zemin
2 WORDTAG O naked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Etienne
40 WORDTAG O past
1 WORDTAG O exercised
1 WORDTAG O fatigues
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosia-Hercegovina
19 WORDTAG O For
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wojtek
1 WORDTAG I-ORG M'bishi
1 WORDTAG O bare-chested
1 WORDTAG O blockbuster
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BioVest
1 WORDTAG O multple
8 WORDTAG O wait
1 WORDTAG O 300th
1 WORDTAG O Statement
1 WORDTAG O 10.02
5 WORDTAG O fours
3 WORDTAG O surface
3 WORDTAG O priority
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Mo
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Burundi-Central
1 WORDTAG I-PER Damien
1 WORDTAG O Hostilities
7 WORDTAG O trouble
1 WORDTAG O reassure
1 WORDTAG O clutched
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vitoux
1 WORDTAG O tirades
1 WORDTAG O loyal
1 WORDTAG O 9.93
1 WORDTAG O 199.71
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Wars
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mariusz
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Telfer
1 WORDTAG O horns
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Alexandroupolis
1 WORDTAG O .22
2 WORDTAG I-PER Keith
1 WORDTAG I-PER Olly
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bahrain
1 WORDTAG O 83.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lubarskij
1 WORDTAG O uneasiness
1 WORDTAG O 44.92
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Avianca
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ploiesti
11 WORDTAG O residents
3 WORDTAG O pictures
1 WORDTAG O establishes
27 WORDTAG O today
35 WORDTAG O period
1 WORDTAG O 02.777
1 WORDTAG O 1:06.289
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Louis
3 WORDTAG O hailed
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Cup
1 WORDTAG I-PER Volker
1 WORDTAG O 23/96
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
1 WORDTAG O rescuers
1 WORDTAG O 20-6-70-2
1 WORDTAG O individually
2 WORDTAG I-PER Herman
17 WORDTAG O looked
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gilardi
2 WORDTAG O promoting
3 WORDTAG I-PER Engquist
1 WORDTAG O 11.20:33
1 WORDTAG I-PER Park
1 WORDTAG O .626
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jansher
1 WORDTAG O Receipts
1 WORDTAG O influenced
1 WORDTAG O similarly
51 WORDTAG O miles
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mayock
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sacchi
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Montenegrin
2 WORDTAG O contingency
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
1 WORDTAG O Conc
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
9 WORDTAG O demanded
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kosice
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pakistan
1 WORDTAG O baseball
2 WORDTAG O Working
3 WORDTAG O blaze
9 WORDTAG O reasons
1 WORDTAG O inserted
1 WORDTAG O avoiding
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Congress
1 WORDTAG O 195-km
1 WORDTAG O implying
12 WORDTAG O assault
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
1 WORDTAG O 13.65
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pena
1 WORDTAG O Conversions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tadeusz
1 WORDTAG O rickety
5 WORDTAG O nominated
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ramprakash
1 WORDTAG O 8/30
1 WORDTAG O 8.26
18 WORDTAG O management
1 WORDTAG O 422.1
2 WORDTAG O doubted
4 WORDTAG O engaged
1 WORDTAG O fire-related
3 WORDTAG O departure
2 WORDTAG I-PER Predrosa
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mariaan
3 WORDTAG I-PER Derrick
3 WORDTAG O cm
10 WORDTAG O longer
12 WORDTAG O cattle
1 WORDTAG O 242.94
3 WORDTAG O alight
2 WORDTAG I-PER Valkov
4 WORDTAG O go-ahead
2 WORDTAG O immune
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Tadamun
8 WORDTAG O lived
1 WORDTAG O maiden
2 WORDTAG O author
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Player
220 WORDTAG O when
2 WORDTAG O 2/3
1 WORDTAG O Bank
1 WORDTAG O 38.1
6 WORDTAG O franc
3 WORDTAG O pursuing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lareau
1 WORDTAG O confined
1 WORDTAG O 55,929.89
4 WORDTAG O formula
1 WORDTAG I-PER Corcoran
1 WORDTAG I-PER Harwood
1 WORDTAG O 17th-ranked
3 WORDTAG O combines
5 WORDTAG O bureau
1 WORDTAG O 2,342.75
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Heart
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
1 WORDTAG O outscoring
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Holding
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Portsmouth
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
12 WORDTAG O recovery
2 WORDTAG O milk
2 WORDTAG O .539
85 WORDTAG O news
1 WORDTAG O heterosexual
40 WORDTAG O signed
1 WORDTAG I-ORG S.A.
42 WORDTAG O head
4 WORDTAG O sugar
3 WORDTAG O tasks
5 WORDTAG I-PER Brandes
3 WORDTAG I-PER Robbie
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shriver
8 WORDTAG O proposals
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Province
1 WORDTAG I-PER Warren
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Phnom
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jodie
1 WORDTAG O 5.2893
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hana
1 WORDTAG I-PER al-
1 WORDTAG O guitarist
1 WORDTAG I-PER Whittingham
35 WORDTAG O champions
2 WORDTAG I-PER Langer
10 WORDTAG O All
2 WORDTAG O ongoing
23 WORDTAG O compared
1 WORDTAG O internationally
1 WORDTAG O 109.36
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Tribunal
2 WORDTAG O bang
1 WORDTAG O processing
2 WORDTAG O upward
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spence
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Montana
1 WORDTAG O 4:21.715
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Eastern
2 WORDTAG O 290.00
13 WORDTAG O unable
1 WORDTAG O dreaded
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Yates
1 WORDTAG O Reg
1 WORDTAG O 1:46.09
2 WORDTAG O Here
1 WORDTAG O advocate
9 WORDTAG O homered
4 WORDTAG O monetary
1 WORDTAG O 25.75
2 WORDTAG O merchants
4 WORDTAG O barges
1 WORDTAG O 45.3
1 WORDTAG O One-month
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Minardi
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
1 WORDTAG O 2-mth
1 WORDTAG O cancell
1 WORDTAG O bookable
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dirkx
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
1 WORDTAG O 13-0
2 WORDTAG O 0.75
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
1 WORDTAG O 91.36
3 WORDTAG O 9.5
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gradin
1 WORDTAG O --------------------------------
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Teixeira
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leong
2 WORDTAG O Revs
1 WORDTAG O rattled
1 WORDTAG O K-SHEETS
1 WORDTAG O 51.80
67 WORDTAG O minute
2 WORDTAG O centrist
56 WORDTAG O behind
1 WORDTAG O 71.70
3 WORDTAG O infection
1 WORDTAG I-PER Teravainen
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Rockies
1 WORDTAG O 38:43.253
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Testament
1 WORDTAG O fo
5 WORDTAG O settlements
1 WORDTAG O mesures
3 WORDTAG O 7.2
1 WORDTAG O one-kg
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jonas
5 WORDTAG O Q2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Astrue
1 WORDTAG O Union
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
1 WORDTAG O Jul-18.Jul
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
3 WORDTAG O second-round
24 WORDTAG O step
1 WORDTAG O emerge
3 WORDTAG O benefits
1 WORDTAG O 4:20.341
3 WORDTAG I-PER Smirnov
6 WORDTAG O critics
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Towers
1 WORDTAG O stationary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Griqualand
1 WORDTAG O ppm
3 WORDTAG O extortion
1 WORDTAG O vehement
1 WORDTAG I-PER Manson
18 WORDTAG O sources
1 WORDTAG I-PER Loewen
2 WORDTAG O 869.3
4 WORDTAG I-PER Knup
4 WORDTAG O implementation
1 WORDTAG O shrink
1 WORDTAG O Diluted
48 WORDTAG O several
19 WORDTAG O issues
1 WORDTAG O bosses
2 WORDTAG O circles
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Amsterdam-Rotterdam
1 WORDTAG O lie
2 WORDTAG O 17.4
1 WORDTAG I-PER Abel
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nizhny
12 WORDTAG I-PER Tsang
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bencevic
3 WORDTAG O actor
3 WORDTAG O brain-wasting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss-based
2 WORDTAG O machinery
1 WORDTAG O visualise
1 WORDTAG O hard-pressed
4 WORDTAG O 75th
1 WORDTAG O 1.91
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vital
1 WORDTAG O 81-7
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maggie
1 WORDTAG O 2:39.00
2 WORDTAG I-PER Patrice
1 WORDTAG O distinctively
7 WORDTAG O transition
1 WORDTAG O passports
1 WORDTAG O much-larger
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Astros
1 WORDTAG I-PER Donizetti
1 WORDTAG I-MISC convention
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Lloyds
3 WORDTAG O announcing
1 WORDTAG O institute
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
1 WORDTAG O deferring
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tunbridge
1 WORDTAG O mid-to-large
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pangalos
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Trax
1 WORDTAG O 0.35
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bombay
1 WORDTAG I-PER Birenda
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jyrki
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Saskatchewan
3 WORDTAG O competing
1 WORDTAG O defend
1 WORDTAG O transfers
2 WORDTAG O three-year-old
1 WORDTAG O starker
3 WORDTAG O serves
3 WORDTAG O hair
1 WORDTAG O predicated
4 WORDTAG O complaint
1 WORDTAG O editor-in-chief
4 WORDTAG O divorced
1 WORDTAG O fries
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisc
1 WORDTAG O Succeeding
1 WORDTAG O pastor
1 WORDTAG O nine-day
1 WORDTAG O 14:59.70
4 WORDTAG O fake
4 WORDTAG O surged
2 WORDTAG O Aa3
1 WORDTAG O high-performance
1 WORDTAG O 0.68
3 WORDTAG O dealt
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vince
1 WORDTAG O instability
5 WORDTAG O surrounded
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kaspars
1 WORDTAG I-PER Clontz
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Luxembourg
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Coal
2 WORDTAG O concessions
1 WORDTAG O viewing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lazarek
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Farewell
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wheaton
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
3 WORDTAG O approximately
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ignacio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tristan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wellman
3 WORDTAG O Scorer
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Homewood
4 WORDTAG I-PER Voinea
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arequipa
6 WORDTAG O deposed
1 WORDTAG O 9.0-12.0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Udovenko
17 WORDTAG O form
2 WORDTAG I-PER Debbie
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Tanzanian
1 WORDTAG O Inaction
86 WORDTAG O June
1 WORDTAG O half-game
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Politehnica
3 WORDTAG I-PER Indra
1 WORDTAG O 6.30
1 WORDTAG O hygiene
2 WORDTAG O plate
1 WORDTAG O touching
2 WORDTAG O separation
1 WORDTAG O ailment
54 WORDTAG O report
9 WORDTAG O stable
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ferro
1 WORDTAG O overbought
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Office
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Near
6 WORDTAG O pleased
1 WORDTAG O Thirty
1 WORDTAG O 0.8584
1 WORDTAG O thwarting
1 WORDTAG I-MISC d'Outre
37 WORDTAG O 9.
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Truth
1 WORDTAG O 25-6-95-4
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jerome
1 WORDTAG I-PER Glenallen
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greece
1 WORDTAG O Sister
1 WORDTAG O 23-year-old
65 WORDTAG O league
2 WORDTAG I-PER Margaret
8 WORDTAG O threat
11 WORDTAG O mixed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bouterse
2 WORDTAG O housing
4 WORDTAG O 0.50
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Darlington
1 WORDTAG O thanking
1 WORDTAG O invade
2 WORDTAG O well-known
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Western-organised
1 WORDTAG O unleashing
1 WORDTAG O disqualified
1 WORDTAG I-PER Seeliger
1 WORDTAG O Goals
2 WORDTAG O 6.00
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sturrup
1 WORDTAG I-PER Huddart
1 WORDTAG O Ride
1 WORDTAG O 59.50
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sciandri
1 WORDTAG I-PER Romero
6 WORDTAG O kilometre
14 WORDTAG O shortly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thul
13 WORDTAG O picked
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Flamurtari
1 WORDTAG O publicized
1 WORDTAG O +
1 WORDTAG I-PER Webster
2 WORDTAG O fielding
1 WORDTAG O 1:56.830
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Auxerre
4 WORDTAG O Goalkeepers
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bremen
1 WORDTAG O 965M
5 WORDTAG O Seven
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nisbet
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royce
3 WORDTAG O farce
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Australia
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boston
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperative
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indian
1 WORDTAG O lasted
1 WORDTAG O calmed
5 WORDTAG O shelling
5 WORDTAG O provided
1 WORDTAG O Wednedsay
1 WORDTAG O evaporate
3 WORDTAG O Members
1 WORDTAG O Analyst
2 WORDTAG O stealing
31 WORDTAG O clear
1 WORDTAG O 17-0-91-0
16 WORDTAG O measures
4 WORDTAG O observed
3 WORDTAG I-PER Roca
24 WORDTAG O director
2 WORDTAG I-PER Fabien
4 WORDTAG O blew
7 WORDTAG O selling
3 WORDTAG O aluminum
1 WORDTAG O 110.50
2 WORDTAG O oblige
1 WORDTAG O cracked
1 WORDTAG O disposed
2 WORDTAG O 13.18
18 WORDTAG O debt
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Individual
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ileana
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Aussies
1 WORDTAG O succeed
10 WORDTAG O drive
1 WORDTAG O Preliminary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Eleusis
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Brooks
1 WORDTAG O vacant
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gascoigne
36 WORDTAG O little
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Development
1 WORDTAG O 1980-88
2 WORDTAG I-PER Volkov
2 WORDTAG O novelist
6 WORDTAG I-PER McEwen
1 WORDTAG O charlatan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lazar
1 WORDTAG O unsatisfied
1 WORDTAG O 387.50
1 WORDTAG O albeit
1 WORDTAG O escalating
1 WORDTAG O pipe
1 WORDTAG O polishing
5 WORDTAG O ONE-DAY
2 WORDTAG O reflects
1 WORDTAG O striving
2 WORDTAG O Corporate
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Singer
18 WORDTAG O life
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
1 WORDTAG O presented
2 WORDTAG O 5.2
13 WORDTAG O wins
6 WORDTAG O education
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fernandez
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Imphold
1 WORDTAG O psychologist
1 WORDTAG O Nothing
1 WORDTAG O 95.7
2 WORDTAG I-PER Swardt
1 WORDTAG I-PER N.J.
5 WORDTAG O planes
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Eindhoven
1 WORDTAG O 5-0
84 WORDTAG O metres
1 WORDTAG O 10752.092
24 WORDTAG O penalty
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
1 WORDTAG O financers
11 WORDTAG O status
1 WORDTAG O knives
2 WORDTAG O denial
4 WORDTAG O Business
3 WORDTAG O deaths
4 WORDTAG O band
2 WORDTAG O 4-205
1 WORDTAG O demurred
2 WORDTAG O valley
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Investigation
2 WORDTAG O contributions
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Vietnamese
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Rajavi
7 WORDTAG O amount
1 WORDTAG O U.N
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aishwarya
4 WORDTAG O raids
1 WORDTAG I-PER Thily
2 WORDTAG I-PER Oremans
2 WORDTAG O deadlocked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Danielyan
1 WORDTAG O 45.05
75 WORDTAG O early
2 WORDTAG I-PER Owen-Jones
1 WORDTAG O +225
2 WORDTAG O attackers
2 WORDTAG O viruses
1 WORDTAG O blanks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kapeta
4 WORDTAG O motorist
2 WORDTAG O favourites
16 WORDTAG O things
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mocude
1 WORDTAG O bails
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
1 WORDTAG I-PER Geoffrey
2 WORDTAG O restitution
7 WORDTAG O attempts
1 WORDTAG O considerably
4 WORDTAG O offenders
30 WORDTAG O train
1 WORDTAG O 2,558.84
1 WORDTAG O frees
1 WORDTAG O upright
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
4 WORDTAG I-PER Samper
1 WORDTAG O cry
1 WORDTAG O 150.3
1 WORDTAG O Soldiers
4 WORDTAG O coached
1 WORDTAG O gmt
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
3 WORDTAG O transmission
11 WORDTAG O means
127 WORDTAG O state
1 WORDTAG O OctNov
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sask
1 WORDTAG O +41
1 WORDTAG O indignant
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
3 WORDTAG O worsened
1 WORDTAG O adversories
1 WORDTAG I-PER Carraz
1 WORDTAG O non-prescription
1 WORDTAG I-PER Corina
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Macedonian
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
1 WORDTAG O 8-284
1 WORDTAG O three-
2 WORDTAG O disabled
2 WORDTAG O left-field
2 WORDTAG O 4-80
3 WORDTAG O baseman
1 WORDTAG O Indeed
1 WORDTAG O 31.80
1 WORDTAG O cups
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
1 WORDTAG O pumping
1 WORDTAG O immunity
1 WORDTAG O 7-502
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rabinovich
1 WORDTAG O 368-7
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nagy
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bohinen
4 WORDTAG O teenagers
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Jamaican
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Loretto
1 WORDTAG I-PER Austin
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rec
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kwai
1 WORDTAG O Arguing
4 WORDTAG O access
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shinichi
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Baxter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lori
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Gisenyi
3 WORDTAG O registry
3 WORDTAG O somewhere
1 WORDTAG O qrtly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reichel
2 WORDTAG O 14-7
1 WORDTAG O 1-48
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Reina
1 WORDTAG O sadness
10 WORDTAG O provincial
2 WORDTAG O Sheet
8 WORDTAG O answer
3390 WORDTAG O in
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sells
1 WORDTAG O snack
1 WORDTAG O trailing
1 WORDTAG O height
1 WORDTAG O 1:56.417
1 WORDTAG O 151-to-1
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Medicine
2 WORDTAG O elaborating
1 WORDTAG O 42.
1 WORDTAG O 80.70
1 WORDTAG O surprises
1 WORDTAG O vetoing
2 WORDTAG O 384-6364
15 WORDTAG O State
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitrios
3 WORDTAG O draws
1 WORDTAG O 31.44
1 WORDTAG O invested
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Games
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Aviv
1 WORDTAG O 10-3-31-1
1 WORDTAG I-PER Craybas
5 WORDTAG O larger
21 WORDTAG O rain
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Platinum
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Seven
1 WORDTAG O tending
1 WORDTAG O implementing
1 WORDTAG O risky
8 WORDTAG O skull
1 WORDTAG O festivities
3 WORDTAG O bourses
1 WORDTAG I-PER Akira
1 WORDTAG O capita
2 WORDTAG O joy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Karl
1 WORDTAG O 2:43.82
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bryan
25 WORDTAG O wheat
4 WORDTAG O 18th
1 WORDTAG O Draws
2 WORDTAG O perfected
1 WORDTAG O 1.4765
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Companion
1 WORDTAG O pioneers
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jaime
1 WORDTAG O mandates
1 WORDTAG O 273.6
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Detroit
1 WORDTAG O disgust
1 WORDTAG O snooze
2 WORDTAG O financed
4 WORDTAG O fence
2 WORDTAG I-PER Grande
1 WORDTAG O racked
2 WORDTAG O Dollar
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Pierre
1 WORDTAG O lingered
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Real
11 WORDTAG O improve
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gaidano
1 WORDTAG O appeals
1 WORDTAG O 9-120
5 WORDTAG O warning
1 WORDTAG O filings
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lupu
2 WORDTAG O 41.5
3 WORDTAG O lamb
1 WORDTAG O shuttled
1 WORDTAG O keyed
1 WORDTAG O Outlook
2 WORDTAG O 3.7
1 WORDTAG O bullion
1 WORDTAG O disillusioned
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
1 WORDTAG O tea
1 WORDTAG O 39-32
3 WORDTAG O heavier
7 WORDTAG I-PER Simpson
4 WORDTAG O lunches
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Broncos
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Constructorol
1 WORDTAG O burial
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Unit
5 WORDTAG I-PER Necmettin
1 WORDTAG O Proceeds
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Hitleresque
13 WORDTAG O religious
2 WORDTAG O villages
1 WORDTAG O downtown
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Studies
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Perm
3 WORDTAG O liabilities
1 WORDTAG O derision
3 WORDTAG O fly-half
3 WORDTAG I-PER McGriff
16 WORDTAG O common
2 WORDTAG O .359
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hansen
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Valley
1 WORDTAG O limb
1 WORDTAG I-PER Martinelli
4 WORDTAG O feared
5 WORDTAG O eventually
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
1 WORDTAG O 1.126
3 WORDTAG O defensive
1 WORDTAG O reinsure
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dubai
1 WORDTAG O +2.6
2 WORDTAG O felons
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Diego
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jemison
1 WORDTAG O 20.21
1 WORDTAG O unidentifed
1 WORDTAG O inflamation
4 WORDTAG O looks
1 WORDTAG O drains
1 WORDTAG O 44.4
81 WORDTAG O season
2 WORDTAG O drift
1 WORDTAG O Destinations
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Penrith
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jadida
1 WORDTAG I-PER Batigol
2 WORDTAG O ups
3 WORDTAG I-PER Benazir
1 WORDTAG O vigorously
1 WORDTAG O compulsory
6 WORDTAG O civilians
1 WORDTAG O reassert
1 WORDTAG O 5-7/8
1 WORDTAG O marine
6 WORDTAG O experience
1 WORDTAG O square-jawed
2 WORDTAG O coal
3 WORDTAG O importers
1 WORDTAG O problematic
3 WORDTAG O lone
4 WORDTAG O denounced
2 WORDTAG O launches
2 WORDTAG O gearbox
1 WORDTAG O thunderstorm
1 WORDTAG O officiated
1 WORDTAG O improperly
1 WORDTAG O cathedral
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
1 WORDTAG O 4.6200
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ulysses
5 WORDTAG O re-election
3 WORDTAG O islands
2 WORDTAG O steep
2 WORDTAG O placing
2 WORDTAG O throw
2 WORDTAG O 339-4
26 WORDTAG O keep
1 WORDTAG O 2467.872
1 WORDTAG O reopen
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
1 WORDTAG I-PER Younnes
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Twyford
1 WORDTAG O Exiled
2 WORDTAG I-PER Bongo
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
1 WORDTAG O rode
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Stanley
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fokker
1 WORDTAG O 128-1
1 WORDTAG O 0-50
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kareda
1 WORDTAG I-MISC IMKB-100
2 WORDTAG O affecting
2 WORDTAG O attracts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Assad
1 WORDTAG O lax
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Mozambican
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Doetinchem
1 WORDTAG O defended
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Centre
1 WORDTAG O mountainside
1 WORDTAG I-PER Stubbs
1 WORDTAG O efficiency
2 WORDTAG O obsessed
2 WORDTAG O solidify
1 WORDTAG O sit
1 WORDTAG O commotion
1 WORDTAG O 23-3-112-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dmitrieva
1 WORDTAG O workplaces
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Libanais
23 WORDTAG O single
1 WORDTAG O core
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pate
1 WORDTAG O *INDICES
1 WORDTAG O herald
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nikki
3 WORDTAG I-PER Neagle
1 WORDTAG O 10-game
3 WORDTAG I-PER Deby
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
1 WORDTAG O drive-through
1 WORDTAG O turnaround
1 WORDTAG O 61-year-old
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Petrobulk
1 WORDTAG I-PER Umberto
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanson
4 WORDTAG O patrols
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Climatological
31 WORDTAG O forced
1 WORDTAG O undressing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Siow
2 WORDTAG I-PER Quarracino
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
1 WORDTAG O 22.73
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Franklin
1 WORDTAG O dynamics
14 WORDTAG O veteran
2 WORDTAG O downstairs
2 WORDTAG O labourers
1 WORDTAG O theoretical
2 WORDTAG O resumption
1 WORDTAG O 24.40
1 WORDTAG I-PER Peters
3 WORDTAG O year-end
5 WORDTAG O nominee
2 WORDTAG O 120.5
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
4 WORDTAG I-LOC H.K.
1 WORDTAG O 1:45.62
660 WORDTAG I-MISC _CAP_
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ortelli
10 WORDTAG O finish
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Seaford
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pizzi
1 WORDTAG O .451
1 WORDTAG O spurt
7 WORDTAG O newsdesk
1 WORDTAG O correspondents
1 WORDTAG O .533
4 WORDTAG O survivors
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chateaubriand
7 WORDTAG I-PER Black
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Ill
1 WORDTAG O destroying
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leonid
3 WORDTAG I-PER Westwood
1 WORDTAG O dossier
1 WORDTAG O 23.5
1 WORDTAG O islanders
1 WORDTAG I-PER Perfetti
1 WORDTAG I-PER Damion
42 WORDTAG O like
4 WORDTAG I-PER Jane
17 WORDTAG O church
1 WORDTAG O cordoned-off
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Milan
1 WORDTAG O briskly
1 WORDTAG O repo
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
1 WORDTAG I-PER Walsh
2 WORDTAG O thefts
1 WORDTAG O post-holiday
2 WORDTAG I-PER Louise
2 WORDTAG O pellets
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Constanza
3 WORDTAG O trln
4 WORDTAG O issuing
1 WORDTAG O cemetary
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ong
2994 WORDTAG O a
2 WORDTAG O captivity
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Cameroon
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
1 WORDTAG O capacities
3 WORDTAG O shall
2 WORDTAG I-LOC State
1 WORDTAG O 10.982
6 WORDTAG O ferry
5 WORDTAG O sports
1 WORDTAG O half-yearly
1 WORDTAG O so-far
1 WORDTAG O towels
1 WORDTAG O symphonies
2 WORDTAG O 97.82
6 WORDTAG O refined
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sheriff
3 WORDTAG I-PER Esnaider
3 WORDTAG O origin
1 WORDTAG O punish
37 WORDTAG O future
1 WORDTAG O 49.72
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Zirka-Nibas
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bosnian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
1 WORDTAG O 1,236.5
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Macedonia
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stankov
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boonen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reed
1 WORDTAG O co-world
1 WORDTAG O favorite
4 WORDTAG O Yr
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurd
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Karen
3 WORDTAG I-PER Klerk
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Soviet
8 WORDTAG O rare
1 WORDTAG O listless
1 WORDTAG O 49.48
1 WORDTAG O swollen
1 WORDTAG O ropes
4 WORDTAG O entry
4 WORDTAG O nationals
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Tetouan
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
80 WORDTAG O during
2 WORDTAG O teenaged
1 WORDTAG O scrum-half
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Droits
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boudova
1 WORDTAG O Rev
3 WORDTAG O stunning
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Velez
2 WORDTAG O 1994/95
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Ingaz
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Catalan
1 WORDTAG O 105-4
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shumer
1 WORDTAG O thorough
1 WORDTAG I-PER Guerrouj
1 WORDTAG O 8:12.04
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kukic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Savimbi
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hendrika
1 WORDTAG O preys
1 WORDTAG O consultation
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chenab
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Gateway
1 WORDTAG O knack
1 WORDTAG O .606
2 WORDTAG O prediction
1 WORDTAG O longer-dated
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Post
2 WORDTAG O marathon
15 WORDTAG O Fall
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
7 WORDTAG O foreigners
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Admira
20 WORDTAG O included
5 WORDTAG O pesetas
1 WORDTAG I-PER Delbruck
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Cowdenbeath
2 WORDTAG O citizens
6 WORDTAG O 64th
2 WORDTAG O 10-8
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ceahlaul
2 WORDTAG I-PER Guivarch
1 WORDTAG O grains
13 WORDTAG O numbers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG World
1 WORDTAG O overseers
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kengo
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Huddersfield
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventude
2 WORDTAG I-PER Adel
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ove
3 WORDTAG O assessed
2 WORDTAG I-PER Carl-Uwe
1 WORDTAG O blazing
1 WORDTAG O oct
4 WORDTAG O Witnesses
102 WORDTAG O them
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Naberezhnye
11 WORDTAG O request
1 WORDTAG O 4.40
18 WORDTAG O doing
4 WORDTAG O lira
3 WORDTAG O dissolution
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Office
1 WORDTAG O stirring
76 WORDTAG O took
1 WORDTAG O credits
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Javedan
3 WORDTAG O claim
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Impreza
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Federation
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
14 WORDTAG O activity
1 WORDTAG O hyper-inflationary
13 WORDTAG O convicted
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Abidjan
4 WORDTAG O unidentified
1 WORDTAG O chequered
2 WORDTAG I-PER F.W.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Whiteman
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
3 WORDTAG O foil
4 WORDTAG O underwent
2 WORDTAG O regional
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Banik
1 WORDTAG O penetrated
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Amtrak
1 WORDTAG O secs
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marial
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Widad
1 WORDTAG O Anyone
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rydz
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Labour
1 WORDTAG O 2-19
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
1 WORDTAG O well-flighted
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Zeleznik
1 WORDTAG O 63.87
1 WORDTAG O 14-day
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunnes
7 WORDTAG O Most
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Guimaraes
1 WORDTAG O 556.19
1 WORDTAG O rejects
1 WORDTAG I-PER Keane
4 WORDTAG I-PER Franz
2 WORDTAG O slept
3 WORDTAG O dry
1 WORDTAG O self-imposed
1 WORDTAG O @
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kundic
2 WORDTAG O Others
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jens
1 WORDTAG O stuck
1 WORDTAG O 7-11
1 WORDTAG I-ORG am
1 WORDTAG O .427
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nacar
1 WORDTAG O comi
9 WORDTAG I-PER Davies
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
1 WORDTAG O solely
1 WORDTAG O phrase
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pendleton
2 WORDTAG I-PER Georges
30 WORDTAG O *
1 WORDTAG O five-metre
1 WORDTAG O round-the-clock
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Siam
5 WORDTAG O intends
1 WORDTAG O steers
3 WORDTAG I-PER Radulescu
1 WORDTAG I-PER Belcher
1 WORDTAG O 8-4
2 WORDTAG O insisting
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aron
4 WORDTAG I-PER Gabriel
1 WORDTAG O credulity
1 WORDTAG O retailers
1 WORDTAG O much-postponed
8 WORDTAG O Her
1 WORDTAG I-PER Auchard
11 WORDTAG O previously
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lincoln
4 WORDTAG O justified
1 WORDTAG O nominate
4 WORDTAG I-PER Amr
4 WORDTAG I-PER Fulton
2 WORDTAG O 3.34
1 WORDTAG O instances
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ballace
2 WORDTAG O reformed
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hurte
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lion
2 WORDTAG O 5,778.00
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hinchcliffe
4 WORDTAG O knows
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nocerina
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventus
2 WORDTAG O searches
1 WORDTAG O seven-year-old
3 WORDTAG O write
2 WORDTAG O 3-116
2 WORDTAG O Stock
1 WORDTAG O seven-inning
1 WORDTAG O old-timers
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cruz
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Mahala
1 WORDTAG O hungry
1 WORDTAG O clown
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
1 WORDTAG O 8-
3 WORDTAG O modest
1 WORDTAG O 3:33.94
1 WORDTAG O 290.3
3 WORDTAG O recommendation
1 WORDTAG O tricks
1 WORDTAG O protecting
1 WORDTAG O 10-2-51-0
1 WORDTAG I-PER Facchinetti
1 WORDTAG O 21-day
1 WORDTAG O relate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maru
9 WORDTAG O college
1 WORDTAG O revise
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Sturm
1 WORDTAG O thrilled
4 WORDTAG O floor
1 WORDTAG O 0.03
1 WORDTAG I-PER Neal
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Las
3 WORDTAG O feature
1 WORDTAG O 1:58.579
1 WORDTAG O season-high
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Trophy
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Country
3 WORDTAG I-PER Zicot
1 WORDTAG O swim
1 WORDTAG O pasta
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sebastien
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Dalian
51 WORDTAG O drawn
1 WORDTAG O freeing
2 WORDTAG O 9-5
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Mountain
2 WORDTAG O coaches
1 WORDTAG O honoured
1 WORDTAG O Repatriation
1 WORDTAG O 100=1992
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Prairie
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Slough
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Miguel
1 WORDTAG O disguise
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Petah
3 WORDTAG O 11.25
1 WORDTAG O 16.875
1 WORDTAG I-PER Neiland
1 WORDTAG O hindering
2 WORDTAG O Showers
1 WORDTAG O Secondhand
1 WORDTAG O cake
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Karin
1 WORDTAG O infiltrating
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rostislav
1 WORDTAG O 5.35
2 WORDTAG O halls
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tanaki
1 WORDTAG O samurai
6 WORDTAG O bids
2 WORDTAG O ventilation
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Motorola
1 WORDTAG O minors
8 WORDTAG I-PER Smith
2 WORDTAG I-PER Gonzalez
1 WORDTAG O prodcuts
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Fulham
1 WORDTAG O 22,666.80
3 WORDTAG I-PER Levenson
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Haiti
1 WORDTAG O possessors
20 WORDTAG O couple
27 WORDTAG O making
1 WORDTAG O 4.252
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
1 WORDTAG O overstayer
1 WORDTAG O leasing
2 WORDTAG O expulsion
5 WORDTAG O deny
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nainkin
1 WORDTAG O fanfare
1 WORDTAG O 28th-ranked
1 WORDTAG O 115.62
19 WORDTAG O remained
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Honduras
2 WORDTAG O Stocks
1 WORDTAG O nicely
1 WORDTAG O Bankruptcy
2 WORDTAG O s
1 WORDTAG O galeforce
1 WORDTAG O earth
1 WORDTAG O 18:00
2 WORDTAG O 6-1-17-0
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Justice
23 WORDTAG O armed
28 WORDTAG O rise
1 WORDTAG O Six-month
34 WORDTAG O order
5 WORDTAG O freight
1 WORDTAG O dishonourable
7 WORDTAG O kidnapping
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Clean
3 WORDTAG O era
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
1 WORDTAG O 28:18.44
3 WORDTAG O signalled
3 WORDTAG O proportion
1 WORDTAG O 732.50
2 WORDTAG O High
20 WORDTAG O mission
3 WORDTAG O appoint
1 WORDTAG O Eyewitnesses
1 WORDTAG O swells
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
1 WORDTAG O 15-18
1 WORDTAG O Church
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
2 WORDTAG O spate
1 WORDTAG O separated
15 WORDTAG O fight
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Los
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aslan
3 WORDTAG O shouted
1 WORDTAG O regiment
2 WORDTAG O Proj
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rabat
1 WORDTAG O sucked
3 WORDTAG O regulatory
1 WORDTAG O tax-exempt
1 WORDTAG I-PER Inspector
1 WORDTAG O brigade
2 WORDTAG O prostitution
1 WORDTAG O casting
1 WORDTAG O .426
5 WORDTAG O bottle
4 WORDTAG O +0.05
1 WORDTAG O Chronic
1 WORDTAG I-PER Artyom
8 WORDTAG O medal
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Gippsland
1 WORDTAG O 4:23.029
1 WORDTAG O charging
3 WORDTAG O discrimination
1 WORDTAG O Belgians
2 WORDTAG O components
1 WORDTAG O 0:09
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Paralympics
2 WORDTAG O mills
2 WORDTAG O increasingly
7 WORDTAG O launch
2 WORDTAG I-PER Helder
1 WORDTAG O B-
2 WORDTAG O 38:32.719
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bunge
2 WORDTAG O gendarmerie
43 WORDTAG O agreement
1 WORDTAG O 2.79
2 WORDTAG I-PER Superman
2 WORDTAG I-PER Guldimann
2 WORDTAG O Huge
15 WORDTAG O rugby
1 WORDTAG O reasserting
2 WORDTAG O telecoms
1 WORDTAG O rescue
1 WORDTAG O encamped
1 WORDTAG O teeth
14 WORDTAG O guerrilla
1 WORDTAG O weigh
3 WORDTAG O inspection
3 WORDTAG O shore
3 WORDTAG I-PER Alexei
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kate
29 WORDTAG O An
1 WORDTAG O 5.40
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Beja
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
2 WORDTAG O one-week
2 WORDTAG O reformer
1 WORDTAG O beats
2 WORDTAG O 4:17.696
1 WORDTAG O privatisatio
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Horst
1 WORDTAG O libero
7 WORDTAG O sterling
3 WORDTAG O Coupon
1 WORDTAG O appealing
1 WORDTAG O recreated
1 WORDTAG O Sixty
4 WORDTAG O 8.30
143 WORDTAG O could
2 WORDTAG O forehand
8 WORDTAG O apparently
1 WORDTAG O cutback
1 WORDTAG O 41no
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Tacis
4 WORDTAG I-PER Talbott
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Tikhomirov-Maskhadov
2 WORDTAG O rumours
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Fife
2 WORDTAG O cocked
1 WORDTAG O grab
1 WORDTAG O assaulting
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bombarda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eiden
98 WORDTAG O back
3 WORDTAG O proprietary
1 WORDTAG O 0.41
1 WORDTAG O 2.9
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Opera
4 WORDTAG I-PER Pat
2 WORDTAG O 12-8
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Koeln
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gorre
3 WORDTAG O uncertainty
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sutton
2 WORDTAG O reviews
3 WORDTAG O cross-border
1 WORDTAG I-PER Deere
1 WORDTAG O radicals
1 WORDTAG O 4-230
2 WORDTAG O fearing
1 WORDTAG O Sergeant
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bhavan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kostantin
4 WORDTAG O respectively
4 WORDTAG O dystrophy
1 WORDTAG O 10.28
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Stentex
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Col
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Piatra
37 WORDTAG O without
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Leeds
2 WORDTAG O Prices
1 WORDTAG O ramshackle
42 WORDTAG O away
1 WORDTAG O Similar
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dillard
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Financial
3 WORDTAG O easier
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bois
1 WORDTAG O delegations
3 WORDTAG O SBPUs
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroecuador
1 WORDTAG I-PER Doohan
1 WORDTAG O redeemed
1 WORDTAG O bowlers
8 WORDTAG O Gov
1 WORDTAG O latitude
1 WORDTAG O toast
2 WORDTAG I-PER della
1 WORDTAG O climate
4 WORDTAG O locked
1 WORDTAG O 5-67
1 WORDTAG O aspect
1 WORDTAG O Miners
4 WORDTAG O schoolgirl
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Ekeren
2 WORDTAG O x
2 WORDTAG O contracted
1 WORDTAG O 115.259
1 WORDTAG O checkpoint
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
1 WORDTAG O specifically
2 WORDTAG I-MISC DTB-Bund-Future
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Islamic
2 WORDTAG I-PER Suleyman
2 WORDTAG O Colonel
1 WORDTAG I-PER Latif
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
1 WORDTAG O 22.68
1 WORDTAG O Fiscal
14 WORDTAG O announcement
1 WORDTAG O sickened
1 WORDTAG O superstar
10 WORDTAG O committed
4 WORDTAG O originally
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
4 WORDTAG O economist
1 WORDTAG O 9074.850
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Avalon
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Atlanta
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dal
40 WORDTAG O army
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chalmers
2 WORDTAG O detailing
2 WORDTAG O calf
10 WORDTAG O fear
2 WORDTAG O adopt
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pesalai
1 WORDTAG O mational
4 WORDTAG O Defenders
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Fontaine
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
2 WORDTAG I-PER Roshan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Cargo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Li
4 WORDTAG O wild-card
2 WORDTAG O payable
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
7 WORDTAG O balls
2 WORDTAG O 2-5
1 WORDTAG O analogue
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pelletreau
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Peterborough
1750 WORDTAG I-ORG _CAP_
1 WORDTAG O Sentiment
1 WORDTAG O scans
2 WORDTAG O comparison
6 WORDTAG O families
2 WORDTAG O avenged
3 WORDTAG O raid
10 WORDTAG O additional
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
1 WORDTAG O depopulated
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Southland
8 WORDTAG O became
1 WORDTAG O evades
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tando
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pam
10 WORDTAG O Note
2 WORDTAG O 1.50
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Gorleben
1 WORDTAG O Economic
2 WORDTAG O Imports
1 WORDTAG I-PER Josh
4 WORDTAG O Tries
1 WORDTAG O 49-year-old
5 WORDTAG O changing
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
2 WORDTAG I-PER Randriantefy
2 WORDTAG O 15.125
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Delmas
2 WORDTAG O gluten
1 WORDTAG O News
4 WORDTAG O Price
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wolk
23 WORDTAG O similar
2 WORDTAG O Detective
1 WORDTAG O apparatus
1 WORDTAG O tripped
2178 WORDTAG O "
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Aleksandrovac
1 WORDTAG O 3,905.7
1 WORDTAG O convertible
1 WORDTAG O 4:19.762
1 WORDTAG O slim
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
1 WORDTAG I-PER Carey
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Fund
1 WORDTAG O walloped
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
8 WORDTAG O elect
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
5 WORDTAG O sheet
1 WORDTAG O shunt
1 WORDTAG O heifers
2 WORDTAG O 0.79
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Molde
5 WORDTAG O sexual
2 WORDTAG O 1:04.541
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
3 WORDTAG O Tomorrow
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Moengo
5 WORDTAG O shed
3 WORDTAG O faults
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican-controlled
1 WORDTAG O deaf
1 WORDTAG I-PER McGeechan
25 WORDTAG O problem
1 WORDTAG O best-selling
1 WORDTAG O offensive
1 WORDTAG O Reliever
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Cultural
2 WORDTAG O inquiries
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Juniors
1 WORDTAG O dont
10 WORDTAG O loan
7 WORDTAG O assessment
1 WORDTAG O Peacekeepers
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
1 WORDTAG O Tourists
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lamonts
2 WORDTAG O seller
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Wah
2 WORDTAG O intentions
1 WORDTAG O 60.46
1 WORDTAG O *Note
1 WORDTAG O defined
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Miss
1 WORDTAG O sportsman
4 WORDTAG O conclusion
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Moneymarkets
1 WORDTAG O Inflows
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Aspiration
1 WORDTAG O shuffled
2 WORDTAG O subpoenas
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Pa
4 WORDTAG O approval
3 WORDTAG O incompetent
1 WORDTAG O 1:54.220
21 WORDTAG O cricket
3 WORDTAG O chamber
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bundesbank
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ayr
1 WORDTAG O Product
1 WORDTAG O .576
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Ffr
1 WORDTAG O endorsing
3 WORDTAG O detention
1 WORDTAG O franked
1 WORDTAG O upwards
1 WORDTAG O 2.24
2 WORDTAG O extrusion
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Second
1 WORDTAG O militarists
1 WORDTAG O godfather
3 WORDTAG O hostility
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
1 WORDTAG O adoring
1 WORDTAG O Week
1 WORDTAG I-PER Marushko
1 WORDTAG O E-mail
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoists
2 WORDTAG O ancestors
1 WORDTAG O assurances
2 WORDTAG O lengths
2 WORDTAG I-PER Tulio
10 WORDTAG O suffering
1 WORDTAG O amidst
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nicholas
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pooley
2 WORDTAG O 14.8
4 WORDTAG O manufacture
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ginola
3 WORDTAG O bones
4 WORDTAG I-PER Laurent
3 WORDTAG O scam
1 WORDTAG O ports
8 WORDTAG O Over
6 WORDTAG O understanding
1 WORDTAG O square-leg
1 WORDTAG O all-party
1 WORDTAG O presents
1 WORDTAG O retirees
5 WORDTAG O unbeaten
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Times-Stock
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mustapha
4 WORDTAG O lung
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Metals
2 WORDTAG O List
3 WORDTAG O emissions
3 WORDTAG O shotgun
9 WORDTAG O earned
1 WORDTAG O halfback
18 WORDTAG O believe
18 WORDTAG O hope
1 WORDTAG O 3-166
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Guineas
1 WORDTAG O batteries
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Atalanta
1 WORDTAG O depreciation
2 WORDTAG O robbing
1 WORDTAG O 135-9
2 WORDTAG O influx
2 WORDTAG O convictions
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Coritiba
1 WORDTAG I-PER Anatoly
3 WORDTAG O 18.0
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Company
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jessen-Petersen
1 WORDTAG O potentates
154 WORDTAG O more
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Gil
3 WORDTAG O privately
2 WORDTAG O notified
1 WORDTAG I-PER Basie
1 WORDTAG O straits
1 WORDTAG O 15.72
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Werder
1 WORDTAG O cop
1 WORDTAG O designate
2 WORDTAG I-PER Fatima
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Westminster
5 WORDTAG I-PER Albert
36 WORDTAG O 're
2 WORDTAG O 10.84
7 WORDTAG O successive
1 WORDTAG O rein
1 WORDTAG O 14-17
1 WORDTAG O adjustments
3 WORDTAG O defeating
1 WORDTAG O Chemical
1 WORDTAG O blaming
1 WORDTAG O 40-1
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gordana
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lambruschini
4 WORDTAG O 1.7
1 WORDTAG O accusations
1 WORDTAG O .561
2 WORDTAG O 17.8
1 WORDTAG I-PER Komen
3 WORDTAG I-PER Banda
1 WORDTAG I-PER Aime
11 WORDTAG O however
1 WORDTAG O golden
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ana
1 WORDTAG O punching
11 WORDTAG O mother
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
10 WORDTAG O billions
1 WORDTAG O 251/09
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
1 WORDTAG O seven-newspaper
1 WORDTAG O noteworthy
1 WORDTAG O lion
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hungary
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
1 WORDTAG O merit
1 WORDTAG O prosperity
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
3 WORDTAG O babies
3 WORDTAG O interior
2 WORDTAG I-PER Cruise
1 WORDTAG O delivers
6 WORDTAG O impossible
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Touchstone
2 WORDTAG O virtual
1 WORDTAG O economically
1 WORDTAG O stabilising
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Internet
1 WORDTAG O slows
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
1 WORDTAG O skying
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Banska
1 WORDTAG O 2/32
1 WORDTAG O bargain-hunting
1 WORDTAG O 524.2
5 WORDTAG O independent
1 WORDTAG O UP-AND-COMERS
1 WORDTAG O jumping
306 WORDTAG O they
3 WORDTAG O grip
4 WORDTAG O complaints
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jalabert
109 WORDTAG O President
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Carril
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ulsan
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Windhoek
19 WORDTAG O orders
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Loznica
1 WORDTAG O aloft
3 WORDTAG O luck
1 WORDTAG O 34-48
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Fac
1 WORDTAG O benched
2 WORDTAG O worker
1 WORDTAG O cash-related
8 WORDTAG O grade
1 WORDTAG O pessimistic
8 WORDTAG O shows
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
1 WORDTAG O pol
1 WORDTAG O unavailable
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dunajska
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Krpaco
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Alaska
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jimenez
1 WORDTAG O Fahrenheit
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jesus
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Conference
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Wycombe
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Free
3 WORDTAG O disqualification
3 WORDTAG O poised
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pedersen
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Suisse
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lamont
3 WORDTAG O Prior
4 WORDTAG O manufacturer
5 WORDTAG O restored
3 WORDTAG O Gross
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blank
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rika
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maigret
1 WORDTAG O disengagement
2 WORDTAG O tool
4 WORDTAG I-PER Danny
1 WORDTAG O No.1
111 WORDTAG O him
2 WORDTAG O distributing
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Haladas
40 WORDTAG O c
3 WORDTAG O scale
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Galatasaray
9 WORDTAG O preparing
2 WORDTAG O investing
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Croix
1 WORDTAG I-PER Murphy
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sawamatsu
37 WORDTAG O best
2 WORDTAG O Concern
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bratislava
2 WORDTAG O off-spinner
2 WORDTAG O hurts
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kandir
2 WORDTAG O five-hitter
1 WORDTAG O 4:16.141
1 WORDTAG O 50,000-seat
2 WORDTAG O thrusting
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rutter
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Industry
1 WORDTAG O dispatching
1 WORDTAG O set-piece
1 WORDTAG O laughing
2 WORDTAG O 1950s
1 WORDTAG I-PER Giuseppe
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Anhui
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Insurance
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gomez
75 WORDTAG O number
2 WORDTAG I-LOC )
3 WORDTAG I-PER Loren
1 WORDTAG O Finally
1 WORDTAG O detachment
1 WORDTAG O Black
4 WORDTAG I-PER Clarence
3 WORDTAG O timing
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Austria
7 WORDTAG O ca
25 WORDTAG O conditions
45 WORDTAG O work
4 WORDTAG O mph
1 WORDTAG O root
1 WORDTAG O sucessful
1 WORDTAG O 9:30
2 WORDTAG O romp
1 WORDTAG O roaring
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Oeste
3 WORDTAG O rewarded
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hansma
7 WORDTAG O copies
2 WORDTAG I-PER Henrietta
1 WORDTAG O 5-all
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mordechai
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hockey
1 WORDTAG I-PER Freeh
2 WORDTAG O umbrella
1 WORDTAG O optional-origin
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Servicenter
1 WORDTAG O sanitary
1 WORDTAG O baserunners
1 WORDTAG O amputee
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rouser
6 WORDTAG I-ORG India
1 WORDTAG O punished
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Ssangbangwool
3 WORDTAG O polling
1 WORDTAG O coverable
2 WORDTAG O 2.30
3 WORDTAG I-PER Susan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Spirlea
1 WORDTAG O oppositions
7 WORDTAG O asylum
1 WORDTAG O five-nation
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Salvation
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
8 WORDTAG O plus
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
1 WORDTAG O knife
1 WORDTAG O nine-year-old
2 WORDTAG I-PER Pukstys
2 WORDTAG I-PER Rudolf
2 WORDTAG O soymeal
1 WORDTAG O shaved
72 WORDTAG O foreign
1 WORDTAG O drained
1 WORDTAG I-PER Waterreus
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
2 WORDTAG O Father
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lance
1 WORDTAG O 3:54.57
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sivas
1 WORDTAG O cede
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fook
2 WORDTAG O spread
1 WORDTAG O father-of-three
1 WORDTAG O pantomime
3 WORDTAG O measure
1 WORDTAG O 8p
2 WORDTAG I-PER Eveningperformance
9 WORDTAG O knew
3 WORDTAG I-PER Springer
4 WORDTAG O agree
1 WORDTAG O colourful
1 WORDTAG O Conservative
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
9 WORDTAG O field
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Matthews
11 WORDTAG O attend
1 WORDTAG O revisited
1 WORDTAG O daubed
1 WORDTAG O femmes
1 WORDTAG O 3-33
1 WORDTAG O injected
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Philip
1 WORDTAG O foods
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
2 WORDTAG O productivity
2 WORDTAG O sacked
5 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Soviet
1 WORDTAG O repurchase
1 WORDTAG O booked
2 WORDTAG I-PER Frazier
1 WORDTAG O regain
2 WORDTAG O abstentions
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslems
3 WORDTAG O 3-7
1 WORDTAG O coordinate
10 WORDTAG O sprint
1 WORDTAG O outdid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Khaled
1 WORDTAG O Oldest
2 WORDTAG O achievement
2 WORDTAG O backs
1 WORDTAG O destocked
6 WORDTAG O award
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Kazakhstan
1 WORDTAG O misleading
1 WORDTAG O fertile
1 WORDTAG I-PER Burcin
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Tavria
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ganic
57 WORDTAG O make
1 WORDTAG O ideology
3 WORDTAG O dogs
48 WORDTAG O many
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Mentmore
1 WORDTAG O 5-3/4
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Lillestrom
2 WORDTAG O conferences
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ravanelli
10 WORDTAG O proposal
2 WORDTAG O Share
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
1 WORDTAG O amd
1 WORDTAG O afflicted
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Victor
1 WORDTAG I-PER Griffey
1 WORDTAG O fortune
11 WORDTAG O determine
6 WORDTAG O intended
1 WORDTAG O distributor
3 WORDTAG O 74th
15 WORDTAG O consumer
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Pole
1 WORDTAG O face-saving
1 WORDTAG O 170.4-175.0
3 WORDTAG I-PER Ikimi
1 WORDTAG O single-digits
3 WORDTAG I-PER Pablo
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Puerto
2 WORDTAG O No.2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cloete
1 WORDTAG O Remarkably
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
1 WORDTAG O prayed
2 WORDTAG O approaching
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Housecall
18 WORDTAG O bln
1 WORDTAG O sixth-ranked
2 WORDTAG O collected
25 WORDTAG O parties
1 WORDTAG I-ORG pour
4 WORDTAG O 8-15
1 WORDTAG O Nil
1 WORDTAG O ruler
19 WORDTAG O sign
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Petroleum
1 WORDTAG O hurdler
1 WORDTAG O rentals
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Freeport
4 WORDTAG O mosque
8 WORDTAG O extradition
2 WORDTAG I-PER Al
2 WORDTAG O guarantee
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Brentford
1 WORDTAG O tom
53 WORDTAG O agreed
1 WORDTAG O 5-12
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Malbak
1 WORDTAG O tankage
1 WORDTAG O 14.18
1 WORDTAG O nerves
2 WORDTAG I-ORG A.G.
1 WORDTAG O Govt.Fcast
1 WORDTAG O FORECAST-
4 WORDTAG O slowly
1 WORDTAG O Monsignor
1 WORDTAG O .594
3 WORDTAG O eighth-seeded
356 WORDTAG O --
1 WORDTAG O meanwhile
2 WORDTAG I-MISC S.AFRICAN
2 WORDTAG O celebrated
2 WORDTAG O models
2 WORDTAG O upgraded
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Rouge
1 WORDTAG O tranfers
2 WORDTAG O six-year
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blenkinsop
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AGF-IART
10 WORDTAG O Officials
1 WORDTAG O vice-chairmen
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
1 WORDTAG O 38.43
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pattaya
4 WORDTAG I-PER Dharmasena
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Torshina
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rainier
1 WORDTAG O 14.828
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Proposition
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Purdue
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sun
3 WORDTAG O funded
1 WORDTAG O mob
1 WORDTAG I-PER Victor
1 WORDTAG O 8.50
2 WORDTAG I-PER Franny
2 WORDTAG I-PER Sameh
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Independence
8 WORDTAG O hijacking
6 WORDTAG O operator
2 WORDTAG O legislation
1 WORDTAG O weekends
4 WORDTAG I-PER Museeuw
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
1 WORDTAG O 10.9
5 WORDTAG I-PER Prince
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mae
3 WORDTAG O carmaker
3 WORDTAG O decades
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maslowe
35 WORDTAG O overs
1 WORDTAG O divergent
1 WORDTAG O independence-joke
2 WORDTAG I-PER Prinosil
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vierklau
2 WORDTAG O explosion
1 WORDTAG O ubiquitious
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
6 WORDTAG O placings
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Brotherhood
86 WORDTAG O They
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Boston
1 WORDTAG O tenor
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gcaleka
1 WORDTAG O Lumber
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fatos
2 WORDTAG O three-party
2 WORDTAG O addressing
1 WORDTAG O exist
2 WORDTAG O degree
1 WORDTAG O 88-year-old
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kris
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
3 WORDTAG I-PER Castilla
21 WORDTAG O stocks
2 WORDTAG O 9-15
1 WORDTAG O writings
1 WORDTAG O closure
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
5 WORDTAG O Only
1 WORDTAG O 2.96
2 WORDTAG O televised
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
1 WORDTAG O counternarcotics
12 WORDTAG O income
2 WORDTAG O chip
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
1 WORDTAG O ski
16 WORDTAG O losses
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Altamira
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Kid
1 WORDTAG O reality
1 WORDTAG O ex-dividend
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Warszawa
1 WORDTAG O kids
2 WORDTAG O congressmen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Burks
12 WORDTAG O resume
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sacramento
1 WORDTAG O obstacles
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Assurance
1 WORDTAG O Saboteurs
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toubon
1 WORDTAG O 125.3
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Taiwanese
7 WORDTAG O popular
8 WORDTAG O mandate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nissan
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Itami
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sadiki
5 WORDTAG O 12th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG is
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rinaldi
1 WORDTAG O preside
4 WORDTAG O two-time
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ogunkoya
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Fiorentina
1 WORDTAG O elephants
3 WORDTAG O throwing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royal
4 WORDTAG O moves
1 WORDTAG O lodge
2 WORDTAG O bridge
1 WORDTAG O 4-4
2 WORDTAG O Production
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rewe
2 WORDTAG O longitudinal
9 WORDTAG O lose
3 WORDTAG O Newspapers
1 WORDTAG O twenty-second
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rosemary
3 WORDTAG O specify
3 WORDTAG I-PER Drummond
1 WORDTAG O 1:02.795
5 WORDTAG O owners
1 WORDTAG O value-added
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 11-13
2 WORDTAG O skipper
1 WORDTAG O 8.10
1 WORDTAG O hindered
1 WORDTAG O profession
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hengelo
1 WORDTAG O sinking
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agnes
1 WORDTAG O antibiotic
1 WORDTAG O mull
1 WORDTAG O veiled
2 WORDTAG O stationery
3 WORDTAG O seats
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Zimbabwean
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
3 WORDTAG O 17.
1 WORDTAG O Free
4 WORDTAG O sad
3 WORDTAG O Conversion
11 WORDTAG O tough
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Alkmaar
1 WORDTAG O 236-4
2 WORDTAG O stationed
3 WORDTAG O predicted
37 WORDTAG O club
2 WORDTAG O swimmer
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Highland
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
1 WORDTAG O exporters
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hatoyama
1 WORDTAG O encouraged
2 WORDTAG O placards
1 WORDTAG O 27.5
1 WORDTAG O overmatched
1 WORDTAG O marketings
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lyngby
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
1 WORDTAG O 1:07.258
1 WORDTAG O ravine
1 WORDTAG O bench
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Muzaffarabad
21 WORDTAG O black
8 WORDTAG O handling
1 WORDTAG O summarily
1 WORDTAG O mid-sea
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
1 WORDTAG O 5-18
14 WORDTAG O different
1 WORDTAG O W125
21 WORDTAG O sector
1 WORDTAG O Bread
3 WORDTAG O chilli
2 WORDTAG O door
1 WORDTAG O casinos
2 WORDTAG I-PER Thierry
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Republicans
3 WORDTAG I-PER Steven
1 WORDTAG O domiciled
1 WORDTAG O appropriations
7 WORDTAG O choice
4 WORDTAG O School
1 WORDTAG O talked
1 WORDTAG O 44.3
2 WORDTAG O keenness
1 WORDTAG O 55.99
1 WORDTAG O closely-watched
1 WORDTAG O misery
1 WORDTAG O Message
1 WORDTAG O Unseeded
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bunce
3 WORDTAG O restore
3 WORDTAG O gear
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
3 WORDTAG O 1970s
1 WORDTAG O insufficient
6 WORDTAG O renewed
122 WORDTAG O there
2 WORDTAG O throne
1 WORDTAG O pre-election
1 WORDTAG O Opinion
3 WORDTAG O marred
8 WORDTAG O none
1 WORDTAG O beta-1b
1 WORDTAG O rock-bottom
1 WORDTAG O penal
4 WORDTAG O weakened
2 WORDTAG I-PER Paes
1 WORDTAG O discussion
3 WORDTAG O facility
1 WORDTAG O guard
3 WORDTAG O rifle
43 WORDTAG O share
11 WORDTAG O spent
37 WORDTAG O available
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hanmer
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
1 WORDTAG O posed
1 WORDTAG O Provision
1 WORDTAG O 0*
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eusebio
1 WORDTAG O rationalised
3 WORDTAG O 12,700-12,800
98 WORDTAG O shares
1 WORDTAG O underwriting
1 WORDTAG O right-handed
1 WORDTAG O play-offs
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Torpedo
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Pacific
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sokoto
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
2 WORDTAG O 10-2
2 WORDTAG O downwards
5 WORDTAG O 59th
1 WORDTAG O 1,156.79
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Red
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ravenna
1 WORDTAG O swallow
1 WORDTAG O 2.93
2 WORDTAG O somewhat
1 WORDTAG O 8.54
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zuleeg
6 WORDTAG I-MISC serie
1 WORDTAG O 2.26
7 WORDTAG O camp
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yoka
1 WORDTAG I-PER Valdes
10 WORDTAG O research
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Trust
4 WORDTAG I-PER Games
1 WORDTAG O mobilised
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Glentoran
3 WORDTAG O 3.3
1 WORDTAG I-PER Idriss
13 WORDTAG O 11th
1 WORDTAG I-LOC AL-MUNTAR
2 WORDTAG I-PER Romano
1 WORDTAG O 32,900-33,000
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bells
1 WORDTAG O accessible
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pasok
1 WORDTAG O +34
5 WORDTAG O iron
2 WORDTAG O shirt
1 WORDTAG O continent
2 WORDTAG I-PER Tabarez
1 WORDTAG O 0.73
7 WORDTAG O true
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Pharamceutical
2 WORDTAG O reopening
6 WORDTAG O crop
1 WORDTAG O 48-1
1 WORDTAG O kero
1 WORDTAG O 22.53
1 WORDTAG O compromising
2 WORDTAG O pre-abnormals
4 WORDTAG I-PER Brundle
10 WORDTAG O Traders
1 WORDTAG O chain-smoking
1 WORDTAG O 61.44
1 WORDTAG O 9-0-41-1
1 WORDTAG O expectation
3 WORDTAG O 31st
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem-led
1 WORDTAG O Superior
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Nursing
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Moenchengladbach
1 WORDTAG O 111.50
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
13 WORDTAG O responsible
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Alsthom
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mavituna
1 WORDTAG O Named
1 WORDTAG O coerce
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lama
1 WORDTAG O mouse
5 WORDTAG O set-top
1 WORDTAG O needy
8 WORDTAG O century
2 WORDTAG O technologies
5 WORDTAG O dozens
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
1 WORDTAG O German-based
1 WORDTAG O referred
18 WORDTAG O range
1 WORDTAG O leaked
1 WORDTAG O noteworty
2 WORDTAG O viscose
2 WORDTAG I-PER Szymanski
8 WORDTAG O organised
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Foundation
1 WORDTAG O Bishop
1 WORDTAG O 1,294.5
4 WORDTAG O coastal
1 WORDTAG O comprised
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dier
2 WORDTAG O Refined
3 WORDTAG I-PER Louis
4 WORDTAG O royal
6 WORDTAG O highest
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wally
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Royal
3 WORDTAG O lowered
1 WORDTAG O Clean
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Seychelles
1 WORDTAG O rain-soaked
2 WORDTAG O breathing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
2 WORDTAG I-PER Privalova
10 WORDTAG O investigating
1 WORDTAG O insult
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Novorossiisk
1 WORDTAG O prone
1 WORDTAG O likes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bottomley
14 WORDTAG O seeking
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Zagreb
1 WORDTAG O taunt
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dadabhoy
1 WORDTAG O bodyguard
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Beautiful
2 WORDTAG O legislators
3 WORDTAG I-PER Wood
362 WORDTAG O $
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Arthur
1 WORDTAG O 1=.6421
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hafez
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bieszk
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lake
1 WORDTAG O soap
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vaas
3 WORDTAG O two-out
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbian
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Ham
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
1 WORDTAG O schillings
1 WORDTAG O hop
1 WORDTAG O parries
1 WORDTAG O fliers
1 WORDTAG O experiencing
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
5 WORDTAG O spying
2 WORDTAG O Budget
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
1 WORDTAG O minimal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Four
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
1 WORDTAG O 2,891.00
2 WORDTAG O contention
2 WORDTAG O cancel
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
3 WORDTAG O easing
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Tempelhof
7 WORDTAG O +301
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pecs
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pierce
2 WORDTAG O resorts
4 WORDTAG O mass
3 WORDTAG O blacks
1 WORDTAG O publicity
1 WORDTAG O 102-0
1 WORDTAG O 6.03
1 WORDTAG O 26.00
1 WORDTAG O Eco
40 WORDTAG O scored
92 WORDTAG O while
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
1 WORDTAG O Described
8 WORDTAG O station
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bethlehem
1 WORDTAG O retaining
1 WORDTAG O warehouse
1 WORDTAG O 38.4
1 WORDTAG O extracts
1 WORDTAG O 39.7
2 WORDTAG O rib
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kamyshin
1 WORDTAG O battles
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Emeraud
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Indies
2 WORDTAG O 23.
1 WORDTAG O Medical
1 WORDTAG O changeup
1 WORDTAG I-MISC F.A.
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hove
2 WORDTAG O shoes
19 WORDTAG O farmers
1 WORDTAG I-PER McLeod
7 WORDTAG I-PER Liam
4 WORDTAG O participation
1 WORDTAG O unfruitful
1 WORDTAG O casualty
1 WORDTAG O rapists
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kemp
1 WORDTAG I-PER Podkopayeva
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Xamax
3 WORDTAG O lb-4
1 WORDTAG O 18.40
4 WORDTAG I-PER Glyn
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kasparkova
1 WORDTAG O Pakistnn
3 WORDTAG O hijackings
5 WORDTAG O youth
20 WORDTAG O votes
4 WORDTAG O extraordinary
2 WORDTAG O compares
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ceske
3 WORDTAG O battered
1 WORDTAG I-PER Claude
1 WORDTAG O 3-0-17-0
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Jenrette
1 WORDTAG O forecaster
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hunte
1 WORDTAG O purchaser
2 WORDTAG I-PER Mirhunisa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Claudio
16 WORDTAG O recently
1 WORDTAG O good-natured
4 WORDTAG O sixth-inning
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Kekkila
36 WORDTAG O ban
2 WORDTAG I-PER Radka
4 WORDTAG O 51st
1 WORDTAG O ex-captain
1 WORDTAG O 54.13
1 WORDTAG O scoured
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
1 WORDTAG O code
58 WORDTAG O deal
1 WORDTAG O Organisations
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Carbondale
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tranmere
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Council
2 WORDTAG I-PER Vaughn
1 WORDTAG O short-dated
1 WORDTAG O flashlight
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tuan
2 WORDTAG O sudden
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
1 WORDTAG O 340.00
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
1 WORDTAG O pima
1 WORDTAG I-MISC France-Juppe
17 WORDTAG O output
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Putra
2 WORDTAG O deep
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
1 WORDTAG O breath
2 WORDTAG I-PER Erdmann
330 WORDTAG O would
1 WORDTAG O ostensibly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Zhang
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
2 WORDTAG O 204.74
1 WORDTAG O robberies
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Arch
3 WORDTAG O resolved
3 WORDTAG O shook
1 WORDTAG I-PER Leoni
3 WORDTAG I-PER Hooper
3 WORDTAG I-PER Boutros-Ghali
56 WORDTAG O pct
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rafael
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Buducnost
3 WORDTAG O 210.00
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Grasshopper
1 WORDTAG O ousting
2 WORDTAG I-PER DeJesus
1 WORDTAG O obligation
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Exploitation
1 WORDTAG O 5:17
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrat
291 WORDTAG O out
1 WORDTAG O interpretations
9 WORDTAG O inflation
3 WORDTAG O simply
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Setubal
1 WORDTAG O 310.00
5 WORDTAG O merely
3 WORDTAG O sandwich
3 WORDTAG O solvent
3 WORDTAG O Until
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bou
78 WORDTAG O should
1 WORDTAG O steamrollered
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Valletta
5 WORDTAG O grew
1 WORDTAG O lb-1
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Pokka
1 WORDTAG I-PER Basler
3 WORDTAG I-PER Samokhalova
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boutoille
3 WORDTAG O predictions
2 WORDTAG O 13-15
3 WORDTAG I-PER Rene
1 WORDTAG O quashed
1 WORDTAG O prospector
2 WORDTAG O saline
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Electoral
1 WORDTAG O beverage
1 WORDTAG O viable
1 WORDTAG O administer
1 WORDTAG O complicated
1 WORDTAG I-PER Miyaga
3 WORDTAG O spirits
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mangala
1 WORDTAG O 7.85
2 WORDTAG O explicit
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Refugees
3 WORDTAG O brokered
1 WORDTAG I-PER Douati
11 WORDTAG O first-half
9 WORDTAG O rating
2 WORDTAG O natural
1 WORDTAG O 45.21
1 WORDTAG I-PER Liano
2 WORDTAG O high-profile
1 WORDTAG O defy
1 WORDTAG O conquered
1 WORDTAG O oversight
1 WORDTAG O recaptured
4 WORDTAG O competitive
2 WORDTAG O 42.5
3 WORDTAG O help-wanted
1 WORDTAG O 0.30
6 WORDTAG O Also
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gehrig
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Stabaek
1 WORDTAG O 97.34
4 WORDTAG I-PER Coulthard
3 WORDTAG O Farm
1 WORDTAG O non-core
1 WORDTAG O rubble
8 WORDTAG O abortion
1 WORDTAG O 9.050
66 WORDTAG O left
11 WORDTAG O above
1 WORDTAG O intermittent
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zarak
1 WORDTAG O sunbed
1 WORDTAG I-MISC U.N.-sponsored
1 WORDTAG O Supercoppa
34 WORDTAG O planned
2 WORDTAG O ringing
5 WORDTAG O contest
1 WORDTAG O pruned
1 WORDTAG O arid
3 WORDTAG O .406
2 WORDTAG O post-match
1 WORDTAG O 391-seat
4 WORDTAG I-PER Conte
1 WORDTAG O hovercraft
1 WORDTAG O publishers
1 WORDTAG O urges
1 WORDTAG O 9.82
1 WORDTAG O unification
1 WORDTAG O 12:01
3 WORDTAG I-PER Okuda
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warburg
12 WORDTAG O progress
2 WORDTAG O concept
2 WORDTAG I-PER Nastase
1 WORDTAG O dollar-buying
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
1 WORDTAG O sternly
1 WORDTAG O widely-reported
1 WORDTAG O part-finance
1 WORDTAG O passion
7 WORDTAG O closes
1 WORDTAG O 29/89
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gente
1 WORDTAG O 400-strong
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mugabe
2 WORDTAG O theme
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Tarmac
1 WORDTAG O 93.2
2 WORDTAG O install
2 WORDTAG O latter
1 WORDTAG O 123.89
1 WORDTAG O Divisionn
1 WORDTAG O 2.60
1 WORDTAG I-PER Easley
1 WORDTAG O laboured
1 WORDTAG O 49.6
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Sen
15 WORDTAG O figure
57 WORDTAG O cents
4 WORDTAG I-PER Rashid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barnes
2 WORDTAG I-PER Barros
1 WORDTAG O Deutsche
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bobic
1 WORDTAG O 95/96
1 WORDTAG O 05:53
2 WORDTAG O lagging
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Moslem-Croat
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gingrich
1 WORDTAG O baked
1 WORDTAG O Sterling
2 WORDTAG O 8.29
5 WORDTAG O portfolio
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rouxel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mines
1 WORDTAG O 60.33
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interpol
1 WORDTAG O Commanders
3 WORDTAG O hundred
2 WORDTAG O seminar
1 WORDTAG O dismissing
2 WORDTAG O stubborn
16 WORDTAG O programme
1 WORDTAG I-PER Symcox
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
1 WORDTAG O behave
7 WORDTAG O stadium
2 WORDTAG O Leaders
38 WORDTAG O strike
4 WORDTAG O collective
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Wronki
368 WORDTAG O been
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
1 WORDTAG O 16th-century
2 WORDTAG O brighter
1 WORDTAG I-PER Todor
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Ecu
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dieter
7 WORDTAG O cup
1 WORDTAG I-PER Remigino
1 WORDTAG O .403
18 WORDTAG O voting
1 WORDTAG O slaying
1 WORDTAG O 13.1
1 WORDTAG O middle-distance
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bournemouth
1 WORDTAG O second-ranking
1 WORDTAG O sheets
1 WORDTAG O tuscan
4 WORDTAG O landless
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hradec
1 WORDTAG O 96/04
389 WORDTAG O but
1 WORDTAG O kidding
3 WORDTAG O combat
1 WORDTAG O suppose
1 WORDTAG O 0.39
1 WORDTAG O defects
5 WORDTAG O aboard
3 WORDTAG O bizarre
3 WORDTAG I-PER Goldman
1 WORDTAG O cameras
9 WORDTAG O nor
1 WORDTAG O Beachcomber
1 WORDTAG O 2,341.5
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dahlan
7 WORDTAG O stabbed
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
1 WORDTAG O Grade
1 WORDTAG O 1:05.219
1 WORDTAG O lateral
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
1 WORDTAG O Cholera
2 WORDTAG O missile
1 WORDTAG O 115.1
8 WORDTAG O wrist
1 WORDTAG O cane
2 WORDTAG O w-7
3 WORDTAG O combined
1 WORDTAG O patches
37 WORDTAG O ministry
4 WORDTAG O frequent
4 WORDTAG O broker
1 WORDTAG O Source
3 WORDTAG O Investigators
1 WORDTAG O gunshot
1 WORDTAG O volleyed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tanny
5 WORDTAG I-PER Healy
2 WORDTAG O reorganisation
10 WORDTAG O carry
5 WORDTAG O searched
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Westerners
1 WORDTAG O 1.4789
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Editorial
1 WORDTAG O protestors
1 WORDTAG O 50-year
1 WORDTAG O sun-baked
2 WORDTAG O filmed
9 WORDTAG O consumers
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Arabia
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Hutu
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interior
1 WORDTAG I-PER Strunz
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
1 WORDTAG O 8.20-8.50
1 WORDTAG O 77.79
1 WORDTAG O Last-minute
1 WORDTAG O +9.8
1 WORDTAG O 733.75
1 WORDTAG O publicists
2 WORDTAG O likened
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mutawakel
2 WORDTAG I-LOC M3
6 WORDTAG O loaded
1 WORDTAG O RABN.CN
1 WORDTAG O Work
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Agdam
1 WORDTAG O irresponsible
3 WORDTAG O deter
1 WORDTAG O 1,421.90
2 WORDTAG O 11.12
8 WORDTAG I-PER Bourlet
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Chornomorets
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gumy
1 WORDTAG I-MISC France
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Maccabi
1 WORDTAG O teething
1 WORDTAG O forbidden
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
2 WORDTAG O 50-75
1 WORDTAG O sightseers
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fedoruk
3 WORDTAG O Mr
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
1 WORDTAG O Contrary
2 WORDTAG O frame
3 WORDTAG O long-time
1 WORDTAG O loophole
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Blake
1 WORDTAG O favourable
4 WORDTAG I-PER Juergen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cor
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Tibetan
1 WORDTAG O 2-141
6 WORDTAG O slight
1 WORDTAG O 7.4
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bailard
1 WORDTAG O abdomen
1 WORDTAG O passionate
1 WORDTAG O co-producer
3 WORDTAG O testify
2 WORDTAG O Aircraft
1 WORDTAG O represents
7 WORDTAG I-PER Eriksson
7 WORDTAG O missed
1 WORDTAG O NovDec
1 WORDTAG O 705M
3 WORDTAG O 15-3
1 WORDTAG O barricaded
1 WORDTAG O 353.24
1 WORDTAG I-PER Niclas
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jennifer
1 WORDTAG O distracting
4 WORDTAG O Jan-April
4 WORDTAG O reference
3 WORDTAG I-PER Omar
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Keane
2 WORDTAG O monopoly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Siraj
1 WORDTAG O fault
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
2 WORDTAG O .522
5 WORDTAG O procedure
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Ottawa
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Domestic
1 WORDTAG O bearing
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Jews
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Fairmont
4 WORDTAG O bowling
4 WORDTAG I-PER Dubnicoff
1 WORDTAG O statesman
1 WORDTAG O squeezed
1 WORDTAG O 6.93
1 WORDTAG O 1,466.1
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Costa
1 WORDTAG O 6-26
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Alkhan-Yurt
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Curitiba
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gabriela
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Laboratories
2 WORDTAG O preference
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lees
1 WORDTAG O exposed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Tijjani
1 WORDTAG O branding
1 WORDTAG O knocking
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Anatolian
1 WORDTAG I-MISC All-Ordinaries
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Stansted
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
17 WORDTAG O adding
1 WORDTAG O head-butting
1 WORDTAG O waterworks
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Kigali
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
1 WORDTAG O 58-year-old
10 WORDTAG O pitch
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Brighton
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bristol
9 WORDTAG O fine
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Finns
1 WORDTAG O 10.19
1 WORDTAG O 1:51.960
1 WORDTAG O soaring
25 WORDTAG O full
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Dakar
1 WORDTAG O divided
5 WORDTAG O congress
4 WORDTAG O 18.
6 WORDTAG O midday
1 WORDTAG O 4:11.114
1 WORDTAG O thoughts
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Lockhart
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
1 WORDTAG O mismanagement
1 WORDTAG O listing
1 WORDTAG I-PER Menendez
1 WORDTAG O landmines
4 WORDTAG O tankan
2 WORDTAG O introduce
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Vnukovo
2 WORDTAG O misfortune
1 WORDTAG O rebelled
1 WORDTAG O neutralise
1 WORDTAG O disperse
45 WORDTAG O whether
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Shanghai
2 WORDTAG O unsettled
6 WORDTAG O reach
3 WORDTAG O pension
1 WORDTAG O divisions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lumir
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sexual
29 WORDTAG O action
2 WORDTAG I-PER Marc-Vivien
2 WORDTAG I-PER Roche
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Heart
1 WORDTAG I-PER Bath
1 WORDTAG O Acclaimed
9 WORDTAG O let
1 WORDTAG O feeding
8 WORDTAG O slipped
1 WORDTAG O swoop
4 WORDTAG O newly
2 WORDTAG O 5.06
3 WORDTAG O praying
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Cometra
1 WORDTAG O nationally
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jari
1 WORDTAG I-PER Paula
1 WORDTAG O happier
10 WORDTAG O begun
1 WORDTAG O blessed
53 WORDTAG O price
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Welsh
2 WORDTAG O builders
2 WORDTAG O structured
2 WORDTAG O 2.3
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
5 WORDTAG O Trade
1 WORDTAG I-PER Baltasar
5 WORDTAG O spinal
17 WORDTAG O survey
5 WORDTAG O representing
8 WORDTAG O struggle
1 WORDTAG O item
2 WORDTAG O 4.75
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
6 WORDTAG O beating
1 WORDTAG O energies
1 WORDTAG O multinational
1 WORDTAG I-PER Malin
1 WORDTAG O squeeze
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Watford
2 WORDTAG O vice-president
1 WORDTAG O nb-16
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fanton
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Defence
2 WORDTAG O gunfire
1 WORDTAG I-PER Humayun
2 WORDTAG O reshuffle
2 WORDTAG O +6
1 WORDTAG O bitterness
1 WORDTAG O Volumes
1 WORDTAG O uranium
1 WORDTAG I-PER Maase
1 WORDTAG O paparazzi
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
2 WORDTAG I-PER Kschwendt
3 WORDTAG O substituted
1 WORDTAG O garnered
1 WORDTAG O Referring
1 WORDTAG O 1:53.067
1 WORDTAG O provider
1 WORDTAG O limp
1 WORDTAG I-PER Camdzic
1 WORDTAG O half-century
1 WORDTAG O 36.0
1 WORDTAG O empty-handed
3 WORDTAG O 53rd
1 WORDTAG O cigarette
1 WORDTAG O Absolute
5 WORDTAG O racing
1 WORDTAG I-PER McKenzie-Potter
1 WORDTAG O 15:04.94
1 WORDTAG O photocopies
3 WORDTAG O male
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pittsburgh
2 WORDTAG O 5.1
1 WORDTAG O relinquish
1 WORDTAG O durum
4 WORDTAG O sixes
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
2 WORDTAG I-PER Baeron
1 WORDTAG O 31.0
1 WORDTAG O 3.27
1 WORDTAG O revellers
1 WORDTAG O dump
1 WORDTAG O alleges
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jean-Claude
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sobral
1 WORDTAG O patrolling
4 WORDTAG O disciplinary
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lihir
3 WORDTAG O strengthen
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Skhirat
1 WORDTAG O three-pointer
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
12 WORDTAG O democracy
2 WORDTAG O consolidation
12 WORDTAG O sheep
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Confederation
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
1 WORDTAG O tip-off
1 WORDTAG O clouds
1 WORDTAG O gaps
1 WORDTAG O orchestrated
8 WORDTAG O Sale
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sierra
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mallinckrodt
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Collingwood
2 WORDTAG O demonstrations
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kinshasa
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Christopher
7 WORDTAG O nations
1 WORDTAG O telephoned
2 WORDTAG O anxieties
2 WORDTAG O ought
7 WORDTAG O strikers
6 WORDTAG O dn
3 WORDTAG O 11.4
1 WORDTAG O 28.2
2 WORDTAG O translator
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gajadhar
5 WORDTAG I-PER Patricia
1 WORDTAG O 91.05
2 WORDTAG O grouping
1 WORDTAG O 12,855.7
7 WORDTAG O attacked
105 WORDTAG O statement
1 WORDTAG O machinegun
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Havana
10 WORDTAG O New
2 WORDTAG O rouble
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchnage
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
2 WORDTAG O drowned
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
2 WORDTAG O Op
1 WORDTAG O fulfilment
22 WORDTAG O far
26 WORDTAG O senior
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Romanian
1 WORDTAG O souls
1 WORDTAG O 15.0
2 WORDTAG O .526
1 WORDTAG O Fans
1 WORDTAG I-PER Lila
1 WORDTAG O regards
2 WORDTAG I-PER Key
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Stung
5 WORDTAG O baby
2 WORDTAG O sporting
5 WORDTAG O diesel
1 WORDTAG O performing
1 WORDTAG O 3-186
4 WORDTAG I-PER Crohn
6 WORDTAG O motion
1 WORDTAG O grey-haired
1 WORDTAG O mention
3 WORDTAG O infected
2 WORDTAG O hinterland
2 WORDTAG I-PER Narciso
1 WORDTAG O 25.8
14 WORDTAG O threatened
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sobotzik
1 WORDTAG O organizers
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pascolo
2 WORDTAG O topple
1 WORDTAG O 31.5
1 WORDTAG O apparel
2 WORDTAG O 8.05
1 WORDTAG O longer-term
1 WORDTAG I-PER Zeyer
1 WORDTAG O pro-rated
3 WORDTAG O cruised
6 WORDTAG O leftist
3 WORDTAG O sensitive
6 WORDTAG O intent
1 WORDTAG I-PER Frederick
4 WORDTAG I-PER Martina
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Antioquia
1 WORDTAG O codename
1 WORDTAG I-MISC ,
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
6 WORDTAG O governments
1 WORDTAG I-PER Veggerby
1 WORDTAG O neat
21 WORDTAG O municipal
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
19 WORDTAG O sets
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Transvaal
51 WORDTAG O refugees
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rutherford
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
1 WORDTAG O 4000.00
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
1 WORDTAG O perceived
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pietro
1 WORDTAG O intrusions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Margret
1 WORDTAG O condos
1 WORDTAG O 6-0-29-1
2 WORDTAG I-PER Melanie
3 WORDTAG O humans
4 WORDTAG O Today
22 WORDTAG O province
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dariusz
2 WORDTAG O praising
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nilsson
1 WORDTAG O breakout
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
2 WORDTAG O integrated
1 WORDTAG O 2.00-2.25
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nonferrous
1 WORDTAG I-PER Amina
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bari
1 WORDTAG O 941-434319
1 WORDTAG O teargas
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Karachi
1 WORDTAG O JulAug
538 WORDTAG O his
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
2 WORDTAG I-ORG She'an
3 WORDTAG O athletics
1 WORDTAG O pros
2 WORDTAG O desire
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
1 WORDTAG O inlaid
2 WORDTAG O dense
1 WORDTAG O fouled
1 WORDTAG O 100-2
1 WORDTAG I-PER Borg
2 WORDTAG O speeding
1 WORDTAG O Museum
1 WORDTAG O Management
92 WORDTAG O any
1 WORDTAG O 31.6
137 WORDTAG O We
1 WORDTAG O Premiership
6 WORDTAG O Operating
2 WORDTAG I-PER Trulsen
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reuf
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Prima
4 WORDTAG O choose
31 WORDTAG O opening
1 WORDTAG O selecting
2 WORDTAG O Education
1 WORDTAG I-PER Caminiti
9 WORDTAG O three-game
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Burmese
1 WORDTAG I-PER Rasheed
1 WORDTAG O defused
1 WORDTAG O escaping
3 WORDTAG O accounted
2 WORDTAG I-PER Edwin
4 WORDTAG O indices
1 WORDTAG O 8-1
1 WORDTAG O posters
2 WORDTAG O tourism
1 WORDTAG I-PER Farrelly
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vieira
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Chaser
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sloga
1 WORDTAG O questioning
1 WORDTAG O soup
5 WORDTAG O therapy
1 WORDTAG O 14.0
1 WORDTAG O finalising
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Canberra
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nothstein
1 WORDTAG O subversive
12 WORDTAG O First
1 WORDTAG O 0.17
1 WORDTAG O pavilion
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Daughters
1 WORDTAG O co-operative
1 WORDTAG O bolts
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jacob
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
1 WORDTAG O airbase
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Tromso
1 WORDTAG O invalidated
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Air
1 WORDTAG O .439
2 WORDTAG O widened
3 WORDTAG O reject
1 WORDTAG O outs
2 WORDTAG O boundary
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fletcher
1 WORDTAG O expel
1 WORDTAG O dumping
2 WORDTAG O pride
3 WORDTAG O H2
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ondruska
1 WORDTAG I-PER Barkho
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arthur
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ishwari
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
1 WORDTAG O assailants
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ackerman
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Liege
1 WORDTAG O .595
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Hong
1 WORDTAG O differs
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Building
1 WORDTAG O falsified
1 WORDTAG O BBB+
2 WORDTAG I-PER Belim
3 WORDTAG O workforce
4 WORDTAG O launching
6 WORDTAG O legislature
2 WORDTAG O enemies
3 WORDTAG I-PER Gogele
4 WORDTAG O pick
29 WORDTAG O groups
1 WORDTAG O 0:06
1 WORDTAG O 2,342.0
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Longyearbyen
4 WORDTAG I-PER Talabani
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Islam
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
2 WORDTAG O outdueled
1 WORDTAG O spontaneous
1 WORDTAG O shoe
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostselmash
10 WORDTAG O danger
8 WORDTAG O postponed
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Brasov
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Nairobi
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
5 WORDTAG O Among
1 WORDTAG O shake
4 WORDTAG O +5
3 WORDTAG O momentum
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
1 WORDTAG O boosting
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Cabinet
2 WORDTAG O unlucky
2 WORDTAG O 1998/99
2 WORDTAG O restrict
1 WORDTAG O anticipated
2 WORDTAG O outgoing
34 WORDTAG O Aug
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
1 WORDTAG O 13.66
1 WORDTAG I-ORG al-Watani
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Akron
1 WORDTAG O 89.40
21 WORDTAG O profits
2 WORDTAG O procure
9 WORDTAG O population
1 WORDTAG O dearest
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Zaire
1 WORDTAG I-PER Konga
1 WORDTAG O splitting
2 WORDTAG I-PER Schneider
2 WORDTAG O ill-fated
7 WORDTAG O margin
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Duluth
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rawandouz
19 WORDTAG O member
1 WORDTAG O consciences
3 WORDTAG O photograph
1 WORDTAG O 10-1-54-0
4 WORDTAG O 63rd
1 WORDTAG I-PER Stefka
12 WORDTAG O spending
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Aston
1 WORDTAG O coasted
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Vavuniya
3 WORDTAG I-PER Botha
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pignon
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hasely
1 WORDTAG O Yeah
1 WORDTAG O panes
2 WORDTAG O 000s
1 WORDTAG I-PER Chabora
1 WORDTAG O 15.5
3 WORDTAG O excited
1 WORDTAG O calculated
1 WORDTAG O co-chairman
5 WORDTAG O destitute
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Atagi
1 WORDTAG O outmaneuvering
3 WORDTAG O bars
1 WORDTAG O flood
1 WORDTAG B-MISC T-72
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
28 WORDTAG O analysts
1 WORDTAG I-MISC n't
28 WORDTAG O exports
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ottoz
21 WORDTAG O appeal
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toldo
1 WORDTAG O wigs
2 WORDTAG O nevertheless
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Boo-nee-OL
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Ashoknagar
6 WORDTAG O supporting
1 WORDTAG O renegotiation
1 WORDTAG O stumped
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Bohemians
1 WORDTAG O gloom-stricken
2 WORDTAG I-PER Shabana
136 WORDTAG O between
1 WORDTAG O credibility
71 WORDTAG O international
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympiad
1 WORDTAG O illicit
1 WORDTAG O 28:42.26
1 WORDTAG I-PER Greste
121 WORDTAG O Minister
2 WORDTAG O hinted
24 WORDTAG O Net
3 WORDTAG O Revised
1 WORDTAG O 7-1-29-1
4 WORDTAG I-PER Demel
1 WORDTAG O shave
44 WORDTAG O higher
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Peace
1 WORDTAG I-PER Gaissmayer
2 WORDTAG O Open
4 WORDTAG O seeds
7 WORDTAG O policies
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
1 WORDTAG O bodyguards
3 WORDTAG I-PER VanLandingham
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nasser
1 WORDTAG O disposals
1 WORDTAG O matured
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hinckley
1 WORDTAG O 18-14
16 WORDTAG O states
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicester
1 WORDTAG O bag
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Rudar
3 WORDTAG O nb-3
2 WORDTAG O tonight
2 WORDTAG O manual
2 WORDTAG I-PER Horvath
1 WORDTAG O 251/01
32 WORDTAG O possible
2 WORDTAG O academics
1 WORDTAG O ignored
1 WORDTAG O appearing
2 WORDTAG O punches
1 WORDTAG O substantially
4 WORDTAG O pesos
7 WORDTAG O age
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Biblical
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
1 WORDTAG O labor
1 WORDTAG O 24-km
2 WORDTAG O +22
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Adelaide
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
4 WORDTAG I-PER Reneberg
3 WORDTAG I-PER Cimicchi
3 WORDTAG O Hijacked
8 WORDTAG O comments
3 WORDTAG O tap
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
1 WORDTAG O whisk
6 WORDTAG O .504
1 WORDTAG O 1:50.727
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sharman
2 WORDTAG O 0.63
1 WORDTAG O moult
1 WORDTAG I-PER Shamay
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pamire
1 WORDTAG O interpreted
16 WORDTAG O seventh
1 WORDTAG O bureaucrats
1 WORDTAG O 273-5
2 WORDTAG O wreckage
1 WORDTAG O 93.12
1 WORDTAG I-ORG One
1 WORDTAG O weaken
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Duessseldorf
2 WORDTAG O Passengers
4 WORDTAG O scorer
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dahl
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Universe
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
1 WORDTAG O fast-moving
1 WORDTAG I-PER Trueman
1 WORDTAG O 26-29
2 WORDTAG O lists
1 WORDTAG O 133.82
3 WORDTAG I-PER T.
1 WORDTAG O w-9
1 WORDTAG O wallets
2 WORDTAG O erratically
106 WORDTAG O did
53 WORDTAG O get
4 WORDTAG I-PER Moada
1 WORDTAG O automotive
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Mladost
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kandarr
1 WORDTAG O arguing
3 WORDTAG O pensions
1 WORDTAG O footpath
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Shanghai-Ek
1 WORDTAG I-PER Reiziger
3 WORDTAG O fundamental
2 WORDTAG O comeback
2 WORDTAG O refuel
2 WORDTAG I-PER Torrence
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ballanger
1 WORDTAG O tendencies
1 WORDTAG O participated
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Golden
7 WORDTAG O else
1 WORDTAG O refining
8 WORDTAG O calling
3 WORDTAG O nb-8
1 WORDTAG O 6-1-23-2
2 WORDTAG O Elsewhere
1 WORDTAG O 9-1-49-0
2 WORDTAG O fully
8 WORDTAG O envoy
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazprom
9 WORDTAG O delegates
1 WORDTAG O lashed
8 WORDTAG O formal
2 WORDTAG O prerequisite
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Disney
1 WORDTAG I-PER Madhusudan
1 WORDTAG O holy
1 WORDTAG O electorate
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nizigama
15 WORDTAG O serious
1 WORDTAG O 1.5497
16 WORDTAG O community
40 WORDTAG O current
2 WORDTAG I-PER Lyman
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Yosu
18 WORDTAG O jail
9 WORDTAG O suicide
3 WORDTAG O revealed
1 WORDTAG O shrank
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Dm
1 WORDTAG I-PER Firmin
167 WORDTAG O 1996-08-28
8 WORDTAG I-PER Charles
3 WORDTAG I-PER Kamio
1 WORDTAG I-PER Howe
2 WORDTAG O 13-year
4 WORDTAG I-PER Hekmatyar
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Estudiantes
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
1 WORDTAG O two-tiered
1 WORDTAG O Official
1 WORDTAG I-PER Makarov
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pizzichini
6 WORDTAG O blame
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kiernan
1 WORDTAG I-PER Alina
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hector
1 WORDTAG O cantons
1 WORDTAG O 1,119.0
2 WORDTAG O principle
5 WORDTAG O contacts
1 WORDTAG O 020-504-5040
1 WORDTAG O ring
1 WORDTAG O 7-1-24-0
1 WORDTAG O 2.78
2 WORDTAG O Presidential
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fallahiyan
2 WORDTAG O invaded
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Sicily
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agyepong
4 WORDTAG O nervousness
2 WORDTAG O occur
97 WORDTAG O n't
5 WORDTAG O negotiated
3 WORDTAG I-PER Moya
2 WORDTAG O advising
25 WORDTAG O attacks
1 WORDTAG I-PER Martyn
2 WORDTAG O protein
1 WORDTAG O eavesdrop
2 WORDTAG I-ORG AL-WATAN
1 WORDTAG O Bomb
1 WORDTAG O 0.21
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hansa
199 WORDTAG O told
1 WORDTAG O voice
1 WORDTAG O +0.7
1 WORDTAG O 11.959
4 WORDTAG I-PER I.
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bratislava
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Career
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Commonwealth
1 WORDTAG O anchored
4 WORDTAG I-PER Toure
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardinals
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Brno
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nelson
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Figaro
1 WORDTAG I-PER Baia
3 WORDTAG I-PER Bucaram
2 WORDTAG O Information
1 WORDTAG O 49.31
1 WORDTAG O sometime
1 WORDTAG O windfall
1 WORDTAG O ignorance
1 WORDTAG O 19,734.70
2 WORDTAG O Everyone
2 WORDTAG I-PER Frenz
7 WORDTAG O fled
1 WORDTAG O 15.09
1 WORDTAG I-PER Edmonds
11 WORDTAG O training
11 WORDTAG O born
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nano
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hoogma
4 WORDTAG O migration
2 WORDTAG O interrogated
2 WORDTAG O capitalisation
2 WORDTAG I-PER Davids
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
3 WORDTAG O Jan-May
1 WORDTAG O stabbings
2 WORDTAG O orderly
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chester
2 WORDTAG O writers
1 WORDTAG O 179.5p
1 WORDTAG I-PER Brenden
5 WORDTAG O Not
1 WORDTAG O mount
7 WORDTAG O politics
2 WORDTAG O saved
10 WORDTAG O hotel
1 WORDTAG O sectoral
1 WORDTAG I-PER Yannos
1 WORDTAG O aegis
1 WORDTAG O 8.45
1 WORDTAG O exculpated
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
1 WORDTAG O 2.50-3.0
1 WORDTAG O 212-859-1610
2 WORDTAG O whistle-stop
1 WORDTAG O parred
11 WORDTAG O subject
1 WORDTAG O nighttime
1 WORDTAG O lasts
2 WORDTAG O 4.38
2 WORDTAG O 76.6
3 WORDTAG O Spaniards
2 WORDTAG O excessive
5 WORDTAG O autumn
1 WORDTAG O witchdoctor
1 WORDTAG O 3.334
3 WORDTAG O mid-August
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Venray
2 WORDTAG O ploughed
4 WORDTAG O insurer
1 WORDTAG O oilfields
1 WORDTAG I-PER Andres
25 WORDTAG I-PER Bill
2 WORDTAG O superbike
1 WORDTAG O composite
5 WORDTAG O detective
1 WORDTAG I-PER Ferdy
1 WORDTAG O poetic
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
2 WORDTAG I-PER Adelt
57 WORDTAG O race
1 WORDTAG O 369.00
1 WORDTAG O bartender
1 WORDTAG O requests
3 WORDTAG I-PER Jordi
1 WORDTAG O Producers
1 WORDTAG O ripped
1 WORDTAG O baggage
3 WORDTAG O exchanged
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Churches
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Poznan
6 WORDTAG O m
1 WORDTAG O contraction
1 WORDTAG O hurling
1 WORDTAG O motorists
23 WORDTAG I-MISC Sudanese
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Matin
1 WORDTAG O seem
4 WORDTAG O softer
4 WORDTAG O 28th
1 WORDTAG O barbarity
1 WORDTAG O handguns
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rohren
2 WORDTAG I-PER Richter
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Palermo
5 WORDTAG O palace
1 WORDTAG O 11.60
1 WORDTAG O 196.8
1 WORDTAG O Undersecretary-General
1 WORDTAG O stamp
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb-held
1 WORDTAG O 15-hour
1 WORDTAG O deployment
1 WORDTAG O 218.50
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Udinese
2 WORDTAG O Highs
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mohajir
1 WORDTAG I-PER Endrio
10 WORDTAG O crude
1 WORDTAG O reinsurance
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
1 WORDTAG O 1:05.406
1 WORDTAG O Social-Democratic
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ipswich
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanwha
1 WORDTAG O ostracism
1 WORDTAG O run-off
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
1 WORDTAG I-PER Kostadinova
1 WORDTAG I-PER Double
9 WORDTAG O rises
1 WORDTAG O stimulant
3 WORDTAG I-PER Marty
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nanda
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Welspun
525 WORDTAG O be
2 WORDTAG I-PER Silvio
9 WORDTAG O base
8 WORDTAG O lives
1 WORDTAG I-PER Jerzy
1 WORDTAG O 12,750-12,950
1 WORDTAG O umpire
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Dist
1 WORDTAG O Lt.
1 WORDTAG O anxious
1 WORDTAG O messed
5 WORDTAG O links
2 WORDTAG O Maturity
1 WORDTAG O 5-1/3
1 WORDTAG O inexorable
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sourav
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Grande
3 WORDTAG O Almost
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Football
1 WORDTAG O .434
1 WORDTAG I-PER Galarraga
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Caufield
1 WORDTAG I-PER Eugene
1 WORDTAG O artist
1 WORDTAG O Shutdown
1 WORDTAG O personally
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Platignum
1 WORDTAG O Consumer
5 WORDTAG O artillery
1 WORDTAG O 61st
1 WORDTAG O historically
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Houston
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sa
1 WORDTAG I-PER Hollandsworth
1 WORDTAG O 8.20
1 WORDTAG O willingness
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Iran
5 WORDTAG O nurses
2 WORDTAG O infectious
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
1 WORDTAG O dipping
1 WORDTAG O Twenty-five
3 WORDTAG O triumph
1 WORDTAG O 408-8787
2 WORDTAG O soyoil
4 WORDTAG O singled
1 WORDTAG O gaining
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Zealander
50 WORDTAG O economic
1 WORDTAG O 235-6745
3 WORDTAG O 7th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Flour
4 WORDTAG O poisoning
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pearson
52 WORDTAG O agency
10 WORDTAG O appointed
2 WORDTAG O corporations
1 WORDTAG O iscovered
1 WORDTAG O knock-on
1 WORDTAG O locks
3 WORDTAG O run-scoring
1 WORDTAG O Oil
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Jewish
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Life
1 WORDTAG O dancing
2 WORDTAG I-PER Whitlinger
6 WORDTAG O displayed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Arias
2 WORDTAG O worry
1 WORDTAG O overreacted
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Huracan-Corrientes
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
4 WORDTAG O initial
4 WORDTAG O liberal
8 WORDTAG O names
4 WORDTAG O ankle
2 WORDTAG O drilled
2 WORDTAG O mill
2 WORDTAG O encephalopathy
2 WORDTAG O actively
4 WORDTAG O spots
1 WORDTAG O attacking
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
1 WORDTAG O equality
24 WORDTAG O source
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Guide
1 WORDTAG O 0.98
335 WORDTAG O beat
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Implats
1 WORDTAG O sky
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Bessemer
1 WORDTAG O shipload
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sawy
3 WORDTAG O physical
1 WORDTAG O 1:55.281
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Voie
7 WORDTAG O catch
1 WORDTAG O cost-effective
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Boca
2 WORDTAG O 2-1-4-0
1 WORDTAG O 3.72
1 WORDTAG O technicalities
4 WORDTAG I-PER al-Kabariti
2 WORDTAG O assertions
1 WORDTAG I-PER Fondriest
5 WORDTAG O civilian
1 WORDTAG I-PER Mazzolari
24 WORDTAG O big
1 WORDTAG I-PER Underwood
6 WORDTAG O operate
1 WORDTAG O 27:18.84
6 WORDTAG O except
8 WORDTAG O happened
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Sud-PTT
1 WORDTAG I-PER Dominique
1 WORDTAG O jittery
1 WORDTAG O 49.06
12 WORDTAG O contact
1 WORDTAG O sheltering
2 WORDTAG I-PER Steeb
117 WORDTAG O four
1 WORDTAG O selector
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
1 WORDTAG O shake-up
1 WORDTAG O alien-led
1 WORDTAG O pinch-hits
2 WORDTAG O temperature
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
1 WORDTAG I-PER Florian
2 WORDTAG O Postponed
1 WORDTAG O letdowns
1 WORDTAG O 12-1
3 WORDTAG O qualify
2 WORDTAG O 20.19
1 WORDTAG O hides
1 WORDTAG O solved
1 WORDTAG O DAY--COMPANY----PERIOD--CONSENSUS----RANGE-------PVS
1 WORDTAG O 3.01
4 WORDTAG O seeing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG a.s.
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
1 WORDTAG O judgement
2 WORDTAG O adoptive
26 WORDTAG O One
2 WORDTAG O catches
1 WORDTAG O Fifth-seed
2 WORDTAG O Higher
1 WORDTAG I-PER Pas
7 WORDTAG O bullish
1 WORDTAG O issuance
57 WORDTAG O goals
1 WORDTAG O 3/1/90
3 WORDTAG I-PER Axworthy
3 WORDTAG O indeed
5 WORDTAG I-PER Herbert
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Congo
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
1 WORDTAG O objection
4 WORDTAG O checked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Booy
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesian
1 WORDTAG I-PER Agota
